- so then the guy says
to the housekeeper,
"make sure she's dead."
Stop me if you heard
this one before.	|Pierce Group
- would have been nice to have
that option 27 minutes ago.	|Jeff Britta
- the housekeeper says
to the guy,
"we don't have a pool."
And the guy says...	|Pierce Group
- good morning, greendale!
Just a reminder,
Our debate team will bring home
The championship tomorrow
versus city college.
Go, human beings!	|Dean All
- great. now i got to start
the whole joke over again.
Okay, so this guy--	|Pierce All
- no!
I've got one for you.
A doddering old fool
Walks into a bar,
tells a stupid joke,
And i crush his windpipe
with my three-ring binder.	|Britta Pierce
i don't get it.	|Shirley Britta
- britta's trying
to give up cigarettes.	|Jeff Shirley
- don't tell them my business.
I will slap
that smug look
Right off your pointy face.	|Britta Jeff
- britta, i'm saying this
Because i care about you
And you're my friend.
You need
to start smoking again.	|Jeff Britta
- i really think you should.	|Shirley Britta
- absolutely.	|Annie Britta
- they say it makes you lose
weight, and your skin looks
Really great
when you do smoke.	|Shirley Britta
- guys, i really appreciate
your support,
But i've got to quit this time.	|Britta Group
- have you thought
about hypnotherapy?
I know
a dynamite hypnotherapist.	|Pierce Britta
- ten-to-one says it's him.	|Jeff Britta
- his name is pierce hawthorne.
And i'm very effective.	|Pierce Britta
- can you help me
block out people's voices
I find extremely annoying?	|Jeff Pierce
Jeff, she's right there.	|Pierce Jeff
- pierce, i would be grateful
for your help.	|Britta Pierce
- you would?
super. i'll set it up.	|Pierce Britta
- what?
i feel bad for him.
Plus, i just yelled at him.	|Britta Jeff
- you yelled at me too.	|Jeff Britta
- oh, did i hurt your feelings,
pointy face?	|Britta Jeff
- wow. wow.	|Jeff Britta
- have you seen the film
department's web site?	|Troy Jeff
- what do you think?	|Jeff Troy
All of abed's films
are about us.	|Troy Group
- what?	|Shirley Troy
- check it out.	|Troy Group
- what else is new?	|JeffActor GroupActor
- Jeff.	|GroupActor JeffActor
- hola.	|JeffActor GroupActor
- jeff, stop being so relaxed.
we need to talk to you about...	|BrittaActor JeffActor
- we know you're living
out of your car.
Why, on lord's good earth,
Are you living
out of your car, boy?	|ShirleyActor JeffActor
- those people look
just like us.
That's eerie.	|Britta Group
- fine, it's true.
I'm living out of my car.
And i don't want anyone's help.	|JeffActor GroupActor
- we had almost that
exact conversation last week.	|Britta Group
- yeah, but abed posted
this video two weeks ago.	|Troy Britta
that boy's a soothsayer.	|Shirley Troy
- this is wrinkling my brain.	|Troy Group
- this is wrinkling my brain.	|TroyActor PierceActor
- that's wrinkling my brain.	|Troy Group
- get a load
of these wrinkles.	|PierceActor TroyActor
who's that old guy?	|Pierce Group
- hi, i'm pierce hawthorne.	|PierceActor JeffActor
- oh, come on!	|Pierce Group
- there he is.	|Annie Dean Whitman
- oh, mr. winger...
Mr. winger, did you happen
to hear
My announcement this morning?	|Dean Jeff
- i hang on every word.	|Jeff Dean
- i'm gonna assume
that's sarcasm.	|Dean Jeff
- correct.	|Jeff Dean
- so you didn't hear
my announcement?	|Dean Jeff
- i'm barely listening now.	|Jeff Dean
- oh.	|Dean Jeff
- my debate partner dropped out,
And we need you to fill in for
him at the championship tonight.	|Annie Jeff
- jeffrey, as debate coach,
I am offering you
an opportunity
To spend the night
drinking from the cup of life
Rather than romancing
your nether regions
In front of the e! channel.	|Whitman Jeff
- come on, jeff.
I mean, who better
than a former lawyer
To really stick it
to those city college snobs
And their star debater
Simmons?	|Dean Jeff
- mm, pass.	|Jeff Dean
- okay. no, no.
Okay, wait. wait.
okay, no, no. look.
Listen, jerkwad--
i'm sorry.
That got heated.
Greendale needs a win.
The best compliment
our sports program gets
Is that our basketball team
is really gay,
So what's it gonna take?
You know,
a plum parking space,
Free meals,
A night of companionship
if you know what i mean.	|Dean Jeff
- i'll do it
for the parking space.
And if you promise
not to tell me what you mean.	|Jeff Dean
- okay.	|Dean Whitman Dean
- pierce, thank you.
I really appreciate
you helping me out.	|Britta Pierce
- and i appreciate
the opportunity.
You know,
sometimes, i think
People don't take me seriously.	|Pierce Britta
- so what are you gonna do?
Wave a pocket watch
in front of my face
And tell me i'm getting
very sleepy?	|Britta Pierce
Just checking the time.
Now close your eyes.
Keep them closed
at all times.
And listen to the soothing sound
of my voice.
The only word
that will bring you out
Is gorilla.
Okay, now focus
on the rhythm
Of your own breathing.
And when you feel the desire
To light up a cigarette,
You will associate these urges
With things in your life
that disgust you.
Bad-tasting food.
Sex with men.
Wearing attractive clothing.
And soon...
Oh, god, i think
i really hurt myself!	|Pierce Britta
Somebody help me.	|Pierce All
Oh, britta, wake up!
Why'd i put you under
so well?
Damn my talent.	|Pierce Britta
- topic for debate is "are
people inherently good or evil?"
So when do you want
to get together to strategize?	|Annie Jeff
- annie, i was a lawyer.
I was a debater for money.
I think i can handle this.	|Jeff Annie
How was hypnotherapy?	|Jeff Britta
- he fell down
and screamed in pain
While i laid there
with my eyes closed
To make him feel
like a good hypnotherapist.	|Britta Jeff
- you realize
this will never end.	|Jeff Britta
- it's already done.
He just wants one more session.	|Britta Jeff
- * wa-wa *	|Jeff Britta
- where's abed?
I need to talk to him
about his films.	|Troy Group
- that boy's flat-out prescient.
He can read our minds.	|Shirley Group
- i know
what you're gonna say.
You watched my movies
on the website.	|Abed Group
- he's a witch!	|Shirley Group
- get him!	|Troy Group
- no, i'm not a witch.
I'm a student
of human character.
I know you guys all so well
I can predict your behavior.
like shirley.	|Abed Group
I know you're a sweet,
christian, generous person.
oh, that's nice.	|Abed Shirley
oh, that's nice.	|Shirley Abed
- i also know you have
thinly veiled rage issues.	|Abed Shirley
careful, boy.	|Shirley Abed
careful, boy.	|Abed Shirley
- oh.	|Shirley Abed
- here. check this out.
May i?	|Abed Group
- yeah.	|Troy Abed
- jeff's character acts
Like nothing around here
affects him.
But things bother him
more than he lets on.	|Abed Group
- hey, i'm top of the class.	|PierceActor All
- gah!	|JeffActor
- he's also very vain.	|Abed Group
- ridiculous.	|Jeff Abed
oh.	|All
- why am i crying?
what, i accidentally listen
to come sail away by styx again?	|Troy Abed
- you don't have to worry,
troy.
It's just a movie.
I can't predict the future.	|Abed Troy
- my leg.
i hurt my leg. aah!	|PierceActor
- what up, happy people?	|Pierce All
- you tell me my future
right now, you evil wizard!	|Shirley Abed
- by the way, jeff,
i think your shirt's trying
To get out of your pants.	|Pierce Jeff
as golding's lord of the flies
demonstrates, man,
When left to his own devices,
Will descend into chaos
and evil.	|Annie Debate
- whoo!
And now, from city college,
Jeremy simmons.	|Dean All
- there were 23,000...
Kidney donations
in america last year.
Man is good.
The average life expectancy
For a man in a community
Is 23 years longer
than a man alone.
Man is good.
And just ten minutes ago,
A bald, bespectacled man
held the door
For a man in a wheelchair.	|Simmons Debate
- oh.	|Dean
- man is good.	|Simmons Debate
- oh.
I hate this guy.	|Dean
- by the end
of this debate,
I will prove with facts
And data
that man is inherently good.	|Simmons Debate
- old trick for achieving
the proper competitive mindset,
I always envision my opponent
having aggressive sex
With my mother.	|Whitman Jeff
This feels so formal.
Let's just talk.
People are evil.
They can't help it.	|Jeff Debate
I didn't catch
your name.	|Jeff Jean
- it's jean.	|Jean Jeff
- take jean here.
She spent a lot of time
this morning
Making herself
look so lovely.	|Jeff Debate
Tell me, jean.
How many people bothered
to tell you
How great you look today?	|Jeff Jean
- none.	|Jean Jeff
- man is evil.	|Jeff Debate
- but you just said
how great i looked.	|Jean Jeff
- for my own selfish purposes.
The fact is,
as hot as you look,
And it is quite hot,
I wouldn't have said anything.	|Jeff Jean
When i talk
about people being evil,
I could cite quotes
or dig up statistics,
But those are just words
and numbers.
I think we could have
a little more fun
If i express myself
in song.
* evil woman *
- * ba na na na na *
- * evil woman *
I knew you could do it.
That's my time,
everybody.
Thank you very much.
Yeah!	|Jeff Debate
- at the end of round one,
City college: 50,
Greendale: 8.	|Jean Debate
- i only got 8?	|Jeff Jean
- she got 8. you got 0.
it's a debate.
not american idol.	|Jean Jeff
- nice work, l.a. law.
All sizzle, no steak.	|Simmons Jeff
- i don't care, dude.
I'm doing this
for a parking space.	|Jeff Simmons
- let's go, boys.
come on, let's go.
I want to see some hustlers
out here.
Let's go.	|BasketballCoach All
- by zeus, what sort
of jackassery is this?
We're in the middle
of a championship debate.	|Whitman BasketballCoach
- we reserved the gym
For practice.	|BasketballCoach Whitman
- uh, yep.
they reserved it.
Okay, they've got us
by the short ones.
The debate is suspended
until tomorrow.	|Dean All
Hopefully, by then,
we can get our act together.	|Dean Jeff
- oh, great try, bruce!
great try.	|BasketballCoach Extra
- jeff, wait,
when are we getting together
To prepare for tomorrow?	|Annie Jeff
- never, because it's stupid,
and i don't care.	|Jeff Annie
Bite me.	|Jeff HumanBeing
- maybe simmons is right.
You really are
all sizzle and no steak.
You probably couldn't beat him
if you tried.	|Annie Jeff
- what do you mean
i can't beat him?
You and i are gonna
study harder
Than we've ever
studied before
And beat city college
tomorrow.	|Jeff Annie
- really?	|Annie Jeff
- no, who am i, iCarly?	|Jeff Annie
- abed is right.
You act like things
don't bother you, but they do.	|Annie Jeff
- look, six months ago,
i was a lawyer.
I wore suits.
I used to say stuff like,
"objection" and "sidebar."
Now i'm losing
a community college debate
To Jeremy "Soul Patch" Simmons.	|Jeff Annie
- hey, winger.
You like to sing?
I like to sing too.
* zero for winger *
* ba na na na na na *	|Simmons Jeff
Kick that.	|Simmons Extra
* was a big shot lawyer *
* ba na na na na na na *
* now he's
a lo-ooooo-ser *	|Simmons Jeff
- lay off, simmons.
Jeff didn't understand
the rules.	|Annie Simmons
- yeah?
What's your excuse,
eight points?	|Simmons Annie
- dude, leave her
out of this.	|Jeff Simmons
- * little annie adderall *
* was an outcast
in high school *	|Simmons Annie
- that's it.
dude, we are gonna debate
The living crap out of you.	|Jeff Simmons
We've got some preparing
to do.	|Jeff Annie
- i liked you better
when you were smoking.	|Troy Britta
- i'm so sorry.	|Britta Troy
- no, you're right.
My feet are long
and stupid.
You can't unring that bell.	|Troy Britta
- oh, no.	|Shirley
- that's my newspaper.	|Abed Shirley
- what do you need
a paper for?
You knew what was gonna
happen yesterday,
You middle-eastern
magic eight ball.
Pierce hurt his leg,
Britta made troy cry.
What's my destiny?
Am i gonna die
in a car?
Is it gonna happen soon?	|Shirley Abed
- shirley, i have
no psychic abilities.
I'm just an entertainer.
But if it'll make you feel
any better,
Here, let me show you
what i'm working on.	|Abed Shirley
- i'm sorry. is that me being
chased down by a werewolf?	|Shirley Abed
- yeah. and that's how you'd
behave in that situation, no?	|Abed Shirley
- the situation being me being
chased down by a werewolf.	|Shirley Abed
- mm-hmm.	|Abed Shirley
- and that's jeff locking lips
with annie.	|Shirley Abed
- mm-hmm. yeah.	|Abed Shirley
- you're a fool.	|Shirley Abed
- so, in the experiment,
stanford students were divided
Into prisoners and guards.
The guards immediately started--	|Annie Jeff
- uh!	|Jeff Annie
- what's wrong?	|Annie Jeff
- i have this weird pain
right above my eyebrow.	|Jeff Annie
- it's called a stress headache.
I got my first one
when i was four.	|Annie Jeff
- i hate it.	|Jeff Annie
- well, get used to it.
You're knee-deep in it now,
brother.
This is debate.
If you want to win,
You need to prepare.	|Annie Jeff
- well, agreed,
but if you want to win,
You need to loosen up.
Go off book, robot debater.	|Jeff Annie
- oh, my gosh.
You're right.
Simmons is so good at using
his inherent magnetism
To sell his points,
and here i am,
Like a spinster librarian
with my hair pulled back.	|Annie Jeff
- yeah.	|Jeff Annie
What do you think?	|Annie Jeff
- thanks.	|Annie Jeff
- be careful. abed thinks
you two are gonna kiss.
ridiculous.	|Shirley Jeff Annie
- us.
Kissing.
That is ridiculous.	|Jeff Annie
- totally.
We should get back
to work.	|Annie Jeff
- yes. um, okay.
The people are inherently evil.	|Jeff Annie
- ooh, we can use
this hobbes quote.
"man is a collection
"of base animal urges.
"to act on them
and experience
"sinful pleasure would be
morally no different
Than taking a breath."
That's poignant, right?	|Annie Jeff
- yeah.
You know,
maybe we should study alone.	|Jeff Annie
- yeah.	|Annie Jeff
- separately.	|Jeff Annie
- uh-huh.
That way we can be more
reproductive--productive!	|Annie Jeff
Bye!	|Jeff Annie
Bye!
- oh, you forgot your phone.	|Annie Jeff
- well, i can get another one.	|Jeff Annie
- the next time
you even see a cigarette,
You will think
of things that disgust you.
And while you're under so deep,
You'll find yourself attracted
To slightly older men.
Perhaps,
some barrel-chested stud
With just enough tummy to love.
You'll want to buy him dinner,
Then go back to his hot tub.
Perhaps, you'll invite
one of your friends
To join us for a three-way.
Maybe someone
with low self-esteem
And slightly larger breasts.	|Pierce Britta
- go to hell,
you disgusting pig.	|Britta Pierce
- a-ha!	|Pierce Britta
- pierce, i was awake
the whole time.
I was faking it.	|Britta Pierce
- i know.
I saw you.
What do you think i am,
some kind of a joke?	|Pierce Britta
- no.
No, i was trying
to make you
Feel better about yourself.	|Britta Pierce
- how dare you pity me?
I may be a little older,
My ideas may seem weird,
And my fashion sense
may cause envy.
But i have a lot to offer.
And i will not be pitied.
Do not help me up.	|Pierce Britta
- and as german poet
franz wickmeyer once wrote...
"snow falls
from the heavens pure.
"we cannot blame the snow
for being...
Soiled by the earth."
Man is good.	|Simmons Debate
What?
that dude gets it.	|Troy Abed
- jeff winger will now offer
a two-minute rebuttal.	|Jean Debate
- hey, sizzle.
What are you gonna sing tonight?
I'm in the mood
for some sade.	|Simmons Jeff
- in the stanford
prison experiment,
21 out of 21 students,
when given absolute power,
Abused and tortured
their fellow students.
My competitor likens people
to pure, falling snow.
I would respond,
"there is none righteous.
No, not one."
Now i realize mr. simmons' quote
Was from the great
franz wickmeyer.
Mine was just
from a simple desert handyman
Named jesus.	|Jeff Debate
- oh, that's nice!	|Shirley Jeff
- survival of the fittest wires
an impulse to eliminate people
Into our hearts.	|Annie Debate
- counterpoint.	|Whitman Debate
- mother teresa.
joan of arc.	|Simmons Debate
- rebuttal.	|Whitman Debate
- nuclear bombs.	|Annie Debate
- nuclear families.	|Simmons Debate
- abu ghraib.	|Jeff Debate
- apu from the simpsons.	|Simmons Debate
- double rejoinder.	|Whitman Debate
- telemarketers.	|Annie Debate
- organ donors.	|Simmons Debate
- hate crimes.	|Jeff Debate
- executions.	|Annie Debate
- ketchup is a vegetable.	|Jeff Debate
This is a real barn-burner.
God, did i just say
cross-burner?	|Pierce Shirley
- no, you did not.	|Shirley Pierce
- oh, good.	|Pierce Shirley
- we make an amazing team.	|Annie Jeff
- i know. we're so in sync.
It's like a perfect duet
or great s...	|Jeff Annie
Hey, professor whitman.	|Jeff Whitman
- jeffrey.
Your preparation was impeccable.
You remind me of a young me
With slightly worse hair.	|Whitman Jeff
- i just checked
with the judges.
They'll need a miracle
to win in rebuttal.
Simmons is finished.	|Dean Jeff Annie
- this is too much for me.	|Britta Group
- whoa, whoa, whoa.
He's going off book.	|Annie Dean Jeff
- why is he ripping up
the cards?
Doesn't he need the cards?	|Shirley Group
- it's a gambit.	|Abed Group
- he hates me.
Yet he caught me.	|Simmons Debate
- ooh.	|Jeff
- man is good.	|Simmons Debate
- abed, abed.	|Shirley Abed
- he was horny.
So he dropped him.
Man is evil.	|Annie Debate
- greendale wins.	|Jean Debate
- huzzah!	|Whitman
- eat that, simmons.	|Dean Simmons
- that off-book enough
for ya?	|Annie Jeff
- simmons got robbed.	|Troy Abed Shirley
- they kissed.
You do have powers.
I'm gonna die by werewolf.	|Shirley Abed
- shirley, i don't have powers.
trust me.
In my next film, we discover
that pierce is an actual genius.	|Abed Shirley
- well, that's not gonna happen.	|Shirley Abed
- no, it's not.	|Abed Shirley
- pierce,
I can't smoke
a cigarette
Without thinking of a three-way
in your hot tub.
You did it.	|Britta Pierce
- yes.
i did?	|Pierce Britta
- you're a genius.	|Britta Pierce
- ah! who's the third?	|Pierce Britta
- you did great in there!	|Dean HumanBeing
- let's take
this bacchanalia outside.	|Whitman Dean
Full moon tonight.	|Whitman Abed
- whoo!	|Dean
- shirley.	|Abed
- well, i'm going this way,
so...	|Annie Jeff
- well, um, congratulations,
buddy.	|Jeff Annie
- thanks, pal.
Just pat me.	|Annie Jeff
- donde esta la biblioteca?
me llamo t-bone,
la arana discoteca.	|TroyActor
- discoteca, muneca,
la biblioteca es en bigote
grande, perro, manteca.	|AbedActor
- manteca, bigote, gigante--	|TroyActor
- cut, cut.
Let me ask you a question.
do you hate this?
Do you hate doing this?
Do you?	|Troy TroyActor AbedActor
Let me talk to you.
can i talk to you for a second?	|Troy Abed
Just hold on.	|Troy TroyActor AbedActor
what is this?	|Troy Abed
- i don't know.
They're just trying to do
what they're gonna do.	|Abed Troy
Uh, just have fun with it.
Take 36.	|Abed TroyActor AbedActor