So from now on,
we'll refer to each other
by our Spanish nombres.
It will be...	|Chang All	|01
Buenos dias, Winger.	|Chang Jeff	|01
Class dismissed.	|Chang All	|01
Look, I'm Annie's backpack.	|Troy Annie	|02
Stop it, Troy.	|Annie Troy	|02
Say there are two friends
and they're in the same class
and one wants to ask the other one
out on a date.
Like a grown-up date,
but within biking distance
of his parents' house.	|Troy Annie	|02
They could do something on campus.
Tomorrow there's a picnic
with live music on the East lawn.
They're calling it
"A night under the stars".	|Annie Troy	|02
Cool. I bet Randi
would love that type of thing.	|Troy Annie	|02
Randi?
I thought...	|Annie Troy	|02
You thought...
Can't believe
I misled you like that.
Listen...
Randi can be the name
of a guy or a girl.
And in this case,
it is definitely a girl.
Thanks for your help.	|Troy Annie	|02
You're welcome.
And I hate you.
And I want to have your children.	|Annie Troy	|02
Damn, I picked the wrong couple
to follow out of class this morning.
Jeff and Britta are dead air.	|Shirley	|03
Are you okay? It looks like
you have actual bed head this morning.	|Britta Jeff	|04
In fashion,
I'm what's known as a tastemaker.	|Jeff Britta	|04
And you missed an entire side
of your face shaving.	|Britta Jeff	|04
And next month,
so will Gwen Stefani.
Here comes vaughan. Bye.	|Jeff Britta	|04
- Crap.	|Britta Jeff	|04
- vaughan?
The guy with the tiny nipples
you did it with.	|Pierce Britta	|04
Hi, vaughan.
Can we talk sometime?
I'm sorry about how things ended.	|Britta vaughan	|05
I'm sorry I can't accept your apology
'cause you're toxic, Britta.
You're like the exact opposite
of an antioxidant.
- I got band practice. Lates.	|vaughan Britta	|05
- Can't we still be friends?
And isn't the word "later"
already short enough?	|Britta vaughan	|05
Let me talk to him for you.
Man-to-man is better.
We won't think about our chubby thighs
or whether or not we can have babies.	|Pierce Britta	|06
Don't talk to vaughan.	|Britta Pierce	|06
- Your hormones are clouding your...	|Pierce Britta	|06
- Don't talk to vaughan.	|Britta Pierce	|06
That is "girl" for "talk to vaughan".	|Pierce	|06
You sure you don't want
a piece of that?	|Shirley Britta	|07
What is he doing?	|Britta Shirley	|07
I know exactly what he's doing.
My ex-husband
spent four weeks doing that
after his "innocent mistake"
of calling me Valerie.
That boy's living in his car.	|Shirley Britta	|07
I lived in my car
for a stretch in the '70s.
Nothing like bedding a woman
on the vinyl backseat of a Skylark.
Of course, we didn't have the same
safety standards back then so...
No condoms.
I tell you, before aids,
sex was like shaking hands.	|Pierce Group	|07
Hence aids.	|Abed Pierce	|07
Brittles, I forgot to tell you,
I went and talked to vaughan.
The bad news is
I could not patch up things between you.
You really did a number on him.
Good news is
I'm the new keyboardist in his band.	|Pierce Britta	|06
So I asked you not to talk to him
and you completely ignored me.	|Britta Pierce	|06
You're missing the headline.
I'm in a rock band!	|Pierce Britta	|06
I'd like to be there
when the band finds out.	|Jeff Pierce	|06
Hi Jeff. We were just talking
about how in today's economy...	|Britta Jeff	|07
Living in your car.
You are living in your car.
I'm sorry,
I'm not good at being coy.	|Shirley Jeff	|07
I'm not living in my car.
I'm just sleeping in it
for a couple of days
while I work at some problems
with my condo.
It's a very temporary issue.
I've got to pay some meaningless fees
and then they'll put my locks
back on the door and that'll be that.	|Jeff Shirley Britta	|07
How you'll get the money?	|Britta Jeff	|07
Believe me, kitten,
Winger's got moves.	|Jeff Britta	|07
- Do you need a place to stay?	|Shirley Jeff	|07
- I'd offer but my dad's kind of racist.	|Jeff Troy	|07
Stay with me.
My room has a bunk bed, which is
a misnomer because it's the real deal.	|Abed Jeff	|07
The next person
that offers me charity or pity
will be mentioned by name
in my suicide note.	|Jeff Group	|07
Annie. Annie. Thanks for your advice
about "a night under the stars".	|Troy Annie	|08
Of course. Anytime. Ever.	|Annie Troy	|08
I got to figure out
what to bring to the picnic.
This is my first college girl
so I really want to impress her.
Would you mind helping me
shop for this stuff?	|Troy Annie	|08
- I'd love to.	|Annie Troy	|08
- Really?
Thanks. Later.	|Troy Annie	|08
Wanna see my place?	|Jeff Britta	|09
I can see it.
Two girls are making out on the hood.	|Britta Jeff	|09
No, my real place.
The condo board's trying to bluff me
by listing my place as available.
Look at those faucets.
Handcrafted in Italy.
100% expensive.	|Jeff Britta	|09
Those faucets are beautiful.
You know what they would
go great with: a home,
which you no longer have.
- You need to move on with your life.	|Britta Jeff	|09
- Yeah. Move on with my life.
"Shmove shmon shmith shmy shmife. "
This condo is all that's left of me.
Every part of it is a part
of who I am.	|Jeff Britta	|09
- Is that a bidet?	|Britta Jeff	|09
- That part's for resale value.
And Saturday afternoons.	|Jeff Britta	|09
You know, downgrading your lifestyle
is your chance to grow as a person.
Maybe even become one.
The less you have, the more you can be.
You know what I'm saying?	|Britta Jeff	|09
There's a silver lining here,
isn't there?
- You're attracted to bums.	|Jeff Britta	|09
- Good night.	|Britta Jeff	|09
Come on. Why don't you have
dinner at my place?
I got a hot plate
that plugs into a cigarette lighter.	|Jeff Britta	|09
Yeah, but your kitchen's
being towed.	|Britta Jeff	|09
Stop! That's my house!	|Jeff Britta	|09
Can I live with you?	|Jeff Abed	|10
Yeah. Cool.
You want the top or the bottom bunk?	|Abed Jeff	|10
Top.	|Jeff Abed	|10
Me too. Race you for it
I win.	|Abed Jeff	|10
Look, I really need
to liquidate some assets.
It's an emergency situation.
What kind of an offer is that?
These are mint condition issues.
The premise alone is priceless.
The guy has the powers
and strength of a spider.
No, your incredulity
perplexes me, nerd.	|Jeff Extra	|11
Jeff, did I say anything in my sleep
about farm animals or Brian Williams?	|Abed Jeff	|12
I don't think so.	|Jeff Abed	|12
Cool. Cool cool cool.
- Lucky charms?	|Abed Jeff	|12
- How are you so satisfied all the time?
Don't you ever want
anything more out of life than cereal?	|Jeff Abed	|12
Sometimes I like to pour
hot cocoa mix into cold milk
and drink like it
like a cold hot chocolate.
I call it "special drink".	|Abed Jeff	|12
And some day you will know it
by its true name, "diabetes. "	|Jeff Abed	|12
You're Goldie Hawn, Jeff.	|Abed Jeff	|12
- I'm sorry?	|Jeff Abed	|12
- You're Goldie Hawn.	|Abed Jeff	|12
Is it the lips?	|Jeff Abed	|12
No. In overboard, she was just like you.
Wealthy, assertive, arrogant.
Got manicures all the time.
But she fell off her boat,
good thing for her because,
she realized she was happier being poor
and rising four boys with Kurt Russell.	|Abed Jeff	|12
Can I not be Kurt Russell?	|Jeff Abed	|12
Do whatever you want.
You just have to know what that is.
For me, it's Lucky Charms...
and tv.	|Abed Jeff	|12
I could use a break.	|Jeff Abed	|12
A picnic blanket.
Genius.
I was gonna lay down on newspaper.	|Troy Annie	|13
It's the blanket my grandmother used
to court my grandfather.	|Annie Troy	|13
Yeah? That's pretty hot.
Thanks.	|Troy Annie	|13
Tell that boy how you feel!	|Shirley Annie	|14
It's scary.
If he's not interested,
I could lose the friendship too.	|Annie Shirley	|14
You could.
Love is a gamble always.
But waiting won't change the dice.
You either roll them or lose your turn.	|Shirley Annie	|14
I'm going to roll them.
I am. I just...
I need a few more shakes.	|Annie Shirley	|14
Shake 'em in your mind, okay?
Excuse me, Pierce's band is playing
and I want to record
the train wreck.
Kind of hoping
for a Michael Richards situation.	|Shirley Annie	|14
Oh! They're pretty good.
This isn't weird for you?	|Shirley Britta	|15
No. Just want to show vaughan some support
to help smooth things over.	|Britta Shirley	|15
Saying good-bye to Britta
was the hardest thing to do.
But when someone's
a bitch and a liar,
there ain't nothing left to woo.
I'm getting rid of Britta.
What am I doing?
- I'm getting rid of the b.	|vaughan All	|16
- She's a no-good b.	|Pierce All	|16
I'm getting rid of Britta,
- I'm getting rid of the b.	|vaughan All	|16
- She's a gdb.	|Pierce All	|16
Really great to have somebody
to watch stuff with.
My dad never wanted to watch anything
so I was kind of raised by tv.	|Abed Jeff	|17
Tv's the best dad there is.
Tv never came home drunk.
Tv never forgot me at the zoo.
Tv never abused and insulted me,
unless you count Cop Rock.	|Jeff Abed	|17
Cop Rock.
- That sounds cool.	|Abed Jeff	|17
- Doesn't it?	|Jeff Abed	|17
Wow, you guys are really
dorming it up in here, huh?	|Britta Jeff	|18
In the last two days,
I spent a quarter.	|Jeff Britta	|18
- We're having the time of our lives.	|Abed Britta	|18
- See?
Who needs platinum faucets?
Do you guys even have
faucets in here?	|Britta Jeff	|18
There's a communal bathroom
down the hallway.
It actually helped me come to terms
with losing my condo.
You don't sit on a toilet like that
until you've left the material world.	|Jeff Britta	|18
- Pavel!	|Abed Pavel	|18
- Hey, bros.	|Pavel Jeff Abed	|18
This is Pavel. He lives next door.
He's from Poland.	|Jeff Britta	|18
Britta	|Abed Pavel	|18
Britta!
I'm getting rid of Britta,
getting rid of the b.	|Pavel Jeff Abed	|18
Excuse me,
I have a future murder victim to visit.	|Britta Jeff Abed	|18
Cool.	|Jeff Abed	|18
Cool.	|Abed Jeff	|18
Cool cool cool.	|Jeff Abed	|18
Guys, what the hell!
"Getting rid of Britta"?
That song was disrespectful to me
and to the definition of "rhyme scheme".	|Britta vaughan Pierce	|19
If you don't like my song,
you don't have to listen, all right?
I'm an artist
and I write what I feel.
And I feel that you suck.	|vaughan Britta	|19
All right, hold on here.
Can I have a word with you?
Could you come here, please,
for a second?
What'd you say?	|Pierce vaughan	|19
I know Britta's your friend,
but my song is more important.	|vaughan Pierce	|19
Your song.
We wrote it together.
- Are you trying to Garfunkel me?	|Pierce vaughan	|19
- Maybe.
Assuming to "Garfunkel" someone
is to keep putting up with them
even though they're a fat, lazy cat
who hogs the spotlight and eats lasagna.	|vaughan Pierce	|19
I get it. You're jealous.	|Pierce vaughan	|19
- What? Why?	|vaughan Pierce	|19
- I don't know.
Because when I were these skinny jeans,
my ass looks like a baby pumpkin.
Or because I'm not a small-nippled,
credit-hogging jag
who only knows three power cords.	|Pierce vaughan	|19
My band, my song!
You want that?
How you like that?	|vaughan Pierce	|19
You get on that horse.	|Pierce vaughan	|19
Did you just defend my honor?	|Britta Pierce	|20
Oh, yeah, totally.	|Pierce Britta	|20
And you'll light the candles.
And you'll take a bite.
And she'll take a bite.
And you'll laugh.
And you'll offer her
your letter jacket
after you notice this funny way
she shakes when she gets cold.
And she'll feel like
the luckiest girl in the world.	|Annie Troy	|21
Right.
I couldn't have done this
without your help.
You're really nice.
We should've hung out more
in high school.	|Troy Annie	|21
Remember when you pretended
to be my backpack?	|Annie Troy	|21
Oh ho, yeah. yeah.I'm funny.
All right.
I got to go get ready.	|Troy Annie	|21
Troy, wait!
I have to tell you...
- My appendix is bursting.	|Annie Troy	|21
- What?	|Troy Annie	|21
My appendix is bursting.	|Annie Troy	|21
Okay. Two young students.
Think I've been
to this dance before.
You guys are sexual partners, right?	|Nurse Troy Annie	|22
Us? No.
He's my very good friend.
And I have appendicitis.	|Annie Nurse	|22
Thanks for bringing me here.
Guess I ruined your date, huh?	|Annie Troy	|22
Doesn't seem to be
anything wrong with you.	|Nurse Annie	|22
Cool. I'll see you.	|Troy Annie	|22
- Where does it hurt?	|Nurse Annie	|22
- Everywhere.	|Annie Nurse	|22
Okay, we have to quarantine you.
We got to get you to a safe distance.	|Nurse Annie	|22
- My date's on the east lawn.	|Troy Nurse	|22
- East lawn. Perfect.
This a date?
You'll need these.	|Nurse Troy	|22
Nice. I'll be thinking of you.	|Troy Annie	|22
Okay, I need to go.	|Annie Troy	|22
No, we...
We have to observe you overnight.
It's policy.
We don't want another
"Vanessa Parsons" on our hand.
She was the "typhoid mary"
of herpes.
I'm kind of the hawkeye
around here so it's kind of a...
Are you seeing anybody?	|Nurse Annie	|22
- You guys weren't in spanish class.	|Britta Abed Jeff	|23
- Knight Rider marathon.	|Jeff Britta	|23
Shadowy flight into the world of a man
who does not exist.
Britta, may I have a word?	|Abed Britta	|23
- Has this always been here?	|Jeff Extra	|23
- You need to take Jeff back.	|Abed Britta	|24
Never had him. Don't want him.
Especially now.
He's got a real Phil Spector vibe going.	|Britta Abed	|24
He's like E.T.
He crashed in my place.
And we're friends now,
it's great for me, but it's bad for him.
- He needs to get back.	|Abed Britta	|24
- What am I supposed to do about that?	|Britta Abed	|24
Use your lady parts.	|Abed Britta	|24
Abed!	|Britta Abed	|24
Don't be naive. The charge between you
was keeping him going.
Tell him you'll make love to him
if he takes a shower
and finds a nice place to live.	|Abed Britta	|24
I'm heading back.
Pavel's making babka.	|Jeff Abed	|24
Do it. Seduce him.
Draw the tapeworm of Jeff out of him
with your sexuality.	|Abed Britta	|24
No.	|Britta Abed	|23
Then say good-bye to E.T.	|Abed Britta	|24
Abed, it's open!	|Jeff Abed	|25
What are you doing?
That was the Jeffersons, honky.	|Jeff Britta	|25
I was wrong, okay?
Material possessions are important.
Think how much happier
the Jeffersons were
than that family on good times.	|Britta Jeff	|25
- But they had good times.	|Jeff Britta	|25
- Well, do good times really matter?
What about good cars, good lobster?
What about that...
That sport where the British people
ride the horses
with the really long hammers?	|Britta Jeff	|25
Jeez, you are way out
of your element here.	|Jeff Britta	|25
Yes, and I do not believe a single word
I am saying for me.
But for you, maybe you're one
of those rare people
with nothing underneath the surface.
Maybe if you put
stain remover on a turd,
you don't get a diamond.
You just get a turd
with less direction in life.	|Britta Jeff	|25
Thanks, coach.
Can you turn the tv back on?	|Jeff Britta	|25
- Faucets.	|Britta Jeff	|25
- Italian faucets, handcrafted.
These look like...
Wait...
I made this notch to indicate
optimal cleansing temperature
for combination skin.
These were mine?	|Jeff Britta	|25
For a fancy condo,
you've got awful security.
Install those in a new apartment
so that every day,
when you're spending
way too much time on your hair,
you can look down and think,
"I was a huge phony before.
I can do it again!"	|Britta Jeff	|25
- You're into me.	|Jeff Britta	|25
- I beg your unbelievable pardon.	|Britta Jeff	|25
Look at all this work you're doing
just to have me around again.
You were may more attracted to me
than you were willing to admit.	|Jeff Britta	|25
I was doing this all for Abed.
You are the worst.	|Britta Jeff	|25
Yeah. Clearly.	|Jeff Britta	|25
vaughan, I just want you to know,
I haven't changed my mind.
I am out.
Also, do me a favor,
will you lay off Britta?
She may walk like
she just got off a horse,
but underneath
all that clown makeup,
she's a good kid.	|Pierce vaughan	|26
No worries, man.
I've moved on.
- Lates!	|vaughan Pierce	|26
- Lates. Okay.
Snakes. What?	|Pierce vaughan	|26
Pierce, I don't need you in my band.
I don't need your heart
or your hand.
I am my own person,
and, Pierce, you're a b.
Yeah, you heard me say it.
Pierce, you're a b.	|vaughan All	|26
No! Before you two proceed,
I have one thing to say...	|Annie Troy Brandi	|27
Did you... say it already?	|Troy Annie	|27
I want nana's blanket back.
Do you guys mind?
Could you scoot over?
It's an heirloom.
I want it back.
Thank you.
Have a nice date.	|Annie Troy Brandi	|27
I don't care what you think.
For me, that was huge.	|Annie Shirley	|28
I know, sweetie.
Let's go find you some pants.	|Shirley Annie	|28
This song's for Pierce
'cause he's so old
His body made of wrinkles and folds.
Stupid and ugly,
he smell like a fart,
the poo-poo in his pants
and poo-poo in my heart.	|Rapper All	|29
Hey, look who the cat
dragged out and licked clean.	|Britta Jeff	|30
I saw how much you missed me,
and smelled what happens
to Pavel on cabbage night,
and realized the world
was better off with me in it.
Thanks...
For, uh...
Caring.	|Jeff Britta	|30
You look like you moved out.	|Abed Jeff	|31
I checked into a motel
and I'm looking for apartments.
You would've been fine with me
staying there forever?	|Jeff Abed	|31
Yep.	|Abed Jeff	|31
- You're pretty cool, Abed.	|Jeff Abed	|31
- You're a huge nerd.	|Abed Jeff	|31
Thanks.	|Jeff Abed	|31
I'm Pierce.
Yeah. Song's about me.	|Pierce All	|32
East side, west side,
North side, south
vaughan's breath is so bad,
His butts mad at his mouth
This rap is by Pierce,
vaughan is dumb
He wears diapers to bed,
And sucks his mothers thumb
And when he wakes up,
Stupid wishing he was me
He has a big poop breakfast,
With a glass of pee
Then he goes to school,
Where he's stupid again
And everybody hates him,
Even all his friends
When you come after Pierce,
Then the battle is on
So this rap goes out,
To stupid vaughan	|Rapper Pierce	|33
Well payed Pierce.
This isn't over.	|vaughan Pierce	|33