Good afternoon,
Greendale community college.
I am your dean with a few corrections
to the fall class catalog.
Cosmology should be cosmetology,
astrology should be astronomy,
and the students on the cover
should be smiling,
but I suppose that's a matter of opinion.
Whoever is growing a small patch of cannabis
behind the gymnasium,
congratulations.
You have won a cruise.
Report to security
to claim your tickets.
In order to increase
awareness of homelessness,
security has been given binoculars.
In campus news,
the debate over our library's PA system
continues
with some students
suggesting its volume be lowered,
while others
question its very purpose.
More on that story as it unfolds.	|Dean
- That dude makes a lot of announcements.	|Troy Group
- I like it,
it makes every ten minutes
feel like the beginning of a new scene of a tv show.
Of course, the illusion only lasts until someone says
something they'd never say on tv
like, how much their life is like tv.
There, it's gone.	|Abed Group
I guess Jeff's running late again.	|Annie Group
Oh, What a shame.
Maybe we should get started...	|Britta Group
I think we should wait for Jeff
before we start studying.	|Shirley Group
But maybe when Jeff gets here,
we could talk to him as a group
about his tardiness.	|Annie Britta
Don't use that word around Abed.
In any case, if you want me to have a chat with Jeff,
I'd be happy to do it.
We've got a bond going, kind of.
Sorta like brothers.	|Pierce Group
I hope your mom didn't make you take baths together
'cause one of you would've been like, 30.	|Troy Pierce
That's funny.
You know, Jeff probably comes late
so he doesn't have to sit through all of your tardiness.	|Pierce Troy
Sorry, Abed.	|Pierce Abed
Will you guys have some self-respect?
You're obsessing over someone
who does not give you a second thought.
Meanwhile, in Guatemala, journalists are being killed
by their own government.	|Britta Group
Baby, you, uh, jumped a column there.
What's happening in Guatemala?	|Shirley Britta
- Nothing.	|Britta Shirley
- Journalists are being murdered?	|Annie Britta
Believe me, every day in that country,
people are being killed for speaking out.
and the worst part of it is,
when it's all over...	|Britta Annie Shirley
- Spoilers.	|Abed Britta
- It's gonna be as if it never even happened.	|Britta Annie Shirley
Real stories...
They don't have spoilers.
You understand that TV and life
are different, right?	|Britta Annie
- My Lady.	|Jeff Annie
- My Lord.	|Annie Jeff
- Hey, Baby.	|Jeff Shirley
- Hi, Sweetie.	|Shirley Jeff
- You smell nice. Vitamin P.	|Jeff Pierce
- Morning, Jeffrey.
People were jazzed to see me too.	|Pierce Jeff
- Word 'em up.	|Troy Jeff
- Word 'em everywhere.	|Jeff Troy
- Good entrance.	|Abed Jeff
- That was for you.	|Jeff Abed
I think there's something that the
group would like to talk to you about.	|Britta Jeff
Actually, there's nothing...	|Abed Jeff
If you're gonna study with people,
it would be cool of you to show up on time.	|Britta Jeff
Oh. Were you waiting?
talking about your interesting personal lives
and your cool emotional problems.
I just feel like I never
have anything to offer.
Truth is my life is emptier
than this three-ring binder.	|Jeff Group
Annie, Do you have any Spanish notes
that might fit in there?
Double-spaced. Thank you.	|Jeff Annie
So what's a guy got to do
to get a "C" around here?	|Jeff Group
One-liner.	|Troy Group
Good studying.
See you later. Bye.	|Abed Group
You know what today is?
The two-week anniversary
of my horrible first impression.	|Jeff Britta
- There's a card for that?	|Britta Jeff
- Not specifically,
but if you think of grandsons
as a metaphor for friendship,
I think you'll agree
with this transformer here
that it's time for ours
to become a man.
By reading from the Torah.	|Jeff Britta
Look, Jeff. You're harmless enough to me
cause a life full of ups and downs
has given me douche-ray vision,
but those are good people in there,
and they trust and respect you.
Watching you exploit them, kinda bums me out.	|Britta Jeff
- Exploit them? They're my friends.	|Jeff Britta
- You want me to bring your car around, Jeff?	|Abed Jeff
No, Abed, I don't want you
to bring my car around.
I'll bring yours around, good guy.
You get going, all right.	|Jeff Abed
You're cute,
but selfish and narcissistic
to the point of near delusion.	|Britta Jeff
She said I was cute.	|Jeff Britta
Tell you what, you take her.
I have less to prove.
You can't pursue people
so desperately.
It starts to creep them out.
Why don't we go get a beer?
I'll give you some advice,
and we can have what the
kids are calling a sausage fest.	|Pierce Jeff
I'm not much of a sausage guy, Pierce.
Maybe next time.	|Jeff Pierce
Next time, then.	|Pierce Jeff
- Will you tell us more about Guatemala?	|Annie Britta
- I never went to a real college.	|Shirley Britta
You should discover that stuff
on your own.	|Britta Annie Shirley
But we need your help.
We've been living
on the wrong side of the looking glass.
You're like Jodie Foster
or Susan Sarandon.
- You'd rather keep it real than be likeable.	|Annie Britta
- Can you at least tell us what to google?	|Shirley Britta
You could start
with this journalist Chacata-Panecos.
He wrote an article critical
of the government, and they killed him.	|Britta Annie Shirley
- That's horrible.	|Annie Britta
- Can we have a protest?
- I want to protest the hell out of something.	|Shirley Britta
- We could have a candlelight vigil
- like lesbians have on the news.	|Annie Shirley
- I could make brownies.	|Shirley Annie
Brownies?	|Britta Shirley
Every once in a while,
a student come up to me and ask,
Why do you teach Spanish?"
They say it just like that.
"Why do you teach
Spanish?"
"Why you?"
Why not math?
Why not photography?
Why not martial arts?
I mean, surely
it must be in my nature
to instruct you in something
that's ancient and secret
like building a wall
that you can see from outer space.
Well, I'll tell you
why I teach Spanish.
It is none of your business, okay?
Now, I don't want to have
any conversations
about what a mysterious
and inscrutable man I am.
I am a Spanish genius!
In espanol, my nickname is
"El tigre chino"!
'Cause my knowledge
will bite her face off!
So don't question Senor Chang
or you'll get bit.
Ya bit.
Ya bit!
Friday Mañana, we'll be having conversations
with the rest of the class
using some of the phrases
we learned in unit one.
You'll be partnering up
in pairs of dos.
If you look under your desk,
you'll find a card with either a picture
or a word on it.
For ejemplo, blondie aqui
has a card
with a picture of a house on it.
So that means the person with the card
with the word casa on it, is her partner.
Comprende, Star-burns?
See you Friday.
Find your partners. Have a great day.
And what do we say
at the end of every class?
Come on, hands...
90 percent of Spanish.	|Chang All
You want to trade cards?
- I'll give you 20 bucks.	|Jeff Abed
- No.	|Abed Jeff
- 50 bucks.	|Jeff Abed
- I don't want your money. I want your shirt.	|Abed Jeff
- What?	|Jeff Abed
- I've had my eye on it since registration day.	|Abed Jeff
- All right, fine. Give me your card.	|Jeff Abed
-  I don't think you understand. I want to wear it out of here.	|Abed Jeff
What are the odds?	|Jeff Britta
Are you sure
you didn't adjust the odds?
I know Abed's been eyeing that shirt
for three weeks.
It's almost like you gave it to him
so he would switch cards.	|Britta Jeff
I gave Abed my shirt
because I'm not selfish,
which is something I guess you'll finally
discover while we are working on this.
Tomorrow night?
Dinner, drinks.	|Jeff Britta
I think that's something
we should discuss with our partners.
Oh, see, I did switch cards.	|Britta Jeff
Can you believe this?
What are the odds?	|Pierce Jeff
-That's a nice shirt. Want to sell it?	|Pierce Jeff
-Yes.	|Jeff Pierce
What's the moist towelette
industry like?
Believe me,
it's nothing like the product.
Nah. It's a hard, dry, large business.
Destroyed all my marriages.
- Of course it didn't help any that
I can't have children. I'm not sterile.
In fact, it's a rare condition
they call "hyper-virility".
Apparently my sperm
shoot through the egg like bullets.
- Can you believe that?	|Pierce Jeff
- I can't.
But you can, so that's fine.
So, the assignment is
to,uh, write a Spanish conversation
using those five phrases.	|Jeff Pierce
Hemingway's Lemonade.	|Pierce Jeff
- We don't need to make this a long evening. We can just..	|Jeff Pierce
- Am I a piece of garbage to you?	|Pierce Jeff
What? No!	|Jeff Pierce
Got ya.
Let's have one drink before we work.
To the "empowerage" of words.	|Pierce Jeff
To the irony of that sentence.	|Jeff Pierce
So what's up with you, Jeffrey?
It seems like you got a burr up your ass or something.	|Pierce Jeff
Well, I guess that it's...
- I think it's Britta.	|Jeff Pierce
- Forget Britta.
...you have to know is her name.
What is she, a water filter?
She's ugly.	|Pierce Jeff
- Why don't we start with me saying...	|Jeff Pierce
- What are you doing?	|Pierce Jeff
Our assignment.	|Jeff Pierce
Oh no no no. This is the first time people are gonna
see Winger and Hawthorne together.
We are gonna show them
we're a force to be reckoned with.
Come on,
let's brainstorm some story ideas.
Better yet, before we do that,
let's ask ourselves...
- What is a story?	|Pierce Jeff
- Oh, My God in heaven.	|Jeff Pierce
If you like that brownie,
you'll gonna hate what's going up on in Guatemala.
Google it.	|Shirley Extra
Raise the truth.	|Shirley Britta
Once it gets dark,
I hand out the candles and we do
what's called "a speechless protest".
We put the tape over our mouths,
and gather hand-in-hand
in a sea of outraged silence.	|Annie Britta
184.5
Starburns, no.	|Britta Starburns
- What's gotten into you?	|Annie Britta
- This is not how you do this.	|Britta Annie Shirley
We know it's not how you do it
cause we're doing everything.	|Annie Britta
But this is tacky and lame.
I didn't mean that.
I'm sorry.
What I meant to say
is that this cause
is really personal to me.	|Britta Annie Shirley
Are you saying
that we're not allowed to protest?
- Britta, you sound like Guatemala.	|Annie Britta
- Sounds like somebody has the case of
"likes to use French politics
to make themselves special,
"but doesn't actually ever want to do
anything-itis."	|Shirley Britta
-No. I do things.
I went to...
I don't do anything.
What can I do?	|Britta Shirley Annie
You can hang the Chacata-Panecos pinata.	|Annie Britta
You guys realize
he was beaten to death, right?	|Britta Shirley Annie
That's where we got the idea from.	|Shirley Britta
Poignant.	|Annie Shirley
- Alright, tell me what I've got so far.	|Pierce Jeff
- What we have so far?
We have something incredibly long,
and very confusing,
and a little homophobic.
And really, really, specifically,
surprisingly,
and gratuitously critical of Israel.
And it's called "two conquistadors",
should probably be "dos".
I mean, it is a Spanish class.
Oh, which reminds me,
the only thing not included in this epic
are the five phrases required
to get me a passing grade.	|Jeff Pierce
You're right.
Needs more work.	|Pierce Jeff
- What are you guys doing?	|Abed Jeff Pierce
- I have no idea.	|Jeff Abed
- Well, we're headed to the demonstration.	|Troy Jeff Pierce
- What, Hippies?	|Pierce Abed
- Some cause Britta's into.	|Troy Pierce Jeff
- It's a silent protest. Lots of candles.
Gets the ladies in the mood for social
change. If you know what I mean.
- Good chance to put some miles on this shirt.	|Abed Pierce Jeff
- You realize these conversations are due in the morning.
- Don't you?	|Pierce Troy Abed
Right.
What do you want to do?	|Troy Abed
Hola, mi llamo Abed	|Abed Troy
Hola, mi llamo Troy	|Troy Abed
Donde esta la biblioteca?	|Abed Troy
La biblioteca esta en la ciudad	|Troy Abed
Gracias	|Abed Troy
Hacks.	|Pierce Abed Troy
Okay What do we do about the ending of act two?	|Pierce Jeff
I'll tell you what we're gonna do.
We're gonna take this, and we're gonna
put it in a museum for crazy people.
And then we're gonna take this,
and memorize five phrases from it
tomorrow morning before class.
- Good night.	|Jeff Pierce
- Wait a minute, Wait a minute, Wait a minute.
You're bailing on our first sausage fest?
This is your definition of friendship?	|Pierce Jeff
No. This is my definition
of you trying way too hard,
and me finding it harder
and harder to stay polite.
Now this was a fine enough way
to spend an evening, devoid of hope,
but a woman I kind of like
is out there in the moonlight
caring about something stupid,
and this is my chance to show her that
I care enough to act like I care about it too.	|Jeff Pierce
- That's all you had to say, Jeff.	|Pierce Jeff
- That was it?
That would've been great
if I had done that two hours ago!	|Jeff Pierce
Nice sign.	|Britta Jeff
Thanks.
I like what you've done
with the place.	|Jeff Britta
I think I was a little
too harsh on you.
I'm not perfect.	|Britta Jeff
I am.
I'd be happy to show you the ropes.	|Jeff Britta
Awesome!
Look at awesome Jeffrey Winger.
Too awesome for old Pierce
with your hip shirts,
and your gelled hair,
and your cool
tape over your mouth.	|Pierce Jeff
Why is everybody wearing
tape over their mouth?	|Pierce All
It's a protest, Pierce.	|Jeff Pierce
Oh, good.
Cause I know
what I'd like to protest...
How much you hurt me.	|Pierce Jeff
Conflicts like these will ultimately
bring us together as an unlikely family.	|Abed Troy
- You have horrible breath right now.	|Troy Abed
- First, you constantly blow me off,
then you want me to do your homework,
then you tell me I'm trying too hard
to be your friend so you have to go.
You have to come out here to pretend
to care about the stupid
stuff she cares about.	|Pierce Jeff
- His words, not mine.	|Pierce Britta
- He is paraphrasing.	|Jeff Britta
Pierce, I got an idea.
Why don't you go
get a cup of coffee,
and hold some waitress hostage
with a monologue about your sperm.	|Jeff Pierce
I'll show you some sperm, buddy.
Was this your idea?
What the hell? Fire.	|Pierce Jeff
I'm not ready to die.	|Pierce All
He's jumped in the fountain.
He's fine.	|Jeff Britta
- Have you seen it?	|Annie Britta
- We did it, girl... Page three.
Its uh, mostly about Pierce,
but listen to that last paragraph.	|Shirley Britta
"The incident occurred during a protest
regarding events in Guatemala."
- Awareness!	|Annie Britta
- And this isn't the school paper, by the way.
This is a real damn paper,
there's a marmaduke in there.	|Shirley Britta
Well, it's more than
I ever accomplished.	|Britta Shirley Annie
Did you guys know about
the ethnic cleansing in Burma?	|Annie Shirley
Need to bust out that brownie mix.	|Shirley Annie
Morning.	|Jeff Britta
Morning.	|Britta Jeff
Oh. no, I get it.
Garfield's wishing me a happy Arbor Day,
- And you'd like a fresh start.	|Britta Jeff
- Nice try.
It's actually secretary's day, and it says
that I'm sorry about crashing your protest
with that drunken,
self-immolating baby boomer.	|Jeff Britta
We don't blame you, sweetie.
Pierce has always been on my watch list.	|Shirley Jeff
That dude is crazy...
He told me girls have two pee holes.	|Troy Jeff
I sang Christmas carols
at a nursing home once.
I've seen the face of dementia,
and last night I saw it again.	|Annie Jeff
You know what he did
that's really crazy?
He offered me $100
to switch cards with him
just so he could be
partners with Jeff.
I think he thought getting closer to Jeff
would bring him respect in the group.
I think he spent his whole life
looking out for himself
and he would trade it all
for a shot at some kind of family.	|Britta Group
Hola, class.
Time for our presentations.
First up was supposed to be
Jeff and Pierce,
but Pierce explained the situation.
Apparently there was a falling out,
things were said, people were betrayed.	|Chang All
Jeff, having heard
Pierce's side of the story,
I think the only humane thing to do
would be to give you a "C"
and let Pierce do his presentation alone,
if that sounds fair to you.	|Chang Jeff
That doesn't sound fair
to me at all.	|Jeff Chang
Pierce, I understand that
if you don't want to be my friend,
but this thing we've created...
It is bigger than the both of us,
and it deserves to be done right.	|Jeff Pierce
All right.	|Pierce Jeff
Okay, guys? Why are there costumes involved?
These are short conversations,
- they're not supposed to take...	|Chang Jeff
- Your breath away?
Well, tough.	|Jeff Chang
You ready, amigo?	|Jeff Pierce
Si.	|Pierce Jeff
F.	|Chang Jeff
F-minus.	|Chang Pierce
What?
Did you say S?	|Pierce Chang
So.
That was one of the worst things
I have ever seen,
which I guess makes being a part
of it, a pretty selfless act,
so I'm impressed.	|Britta Jeff
Well, how do you know I didn't do it
just to get another shot at you?	|Jeff Britta
Cause a smart guy like you
would know that
no woman in that class would be able
to look at you as a sexually viable candidate
ever again.	|Britta Jeff
No, I know.
I thought of that.	|Jeff Britta
She looked back.	|Jeff
- You did an all right job
up there, my friend.
Thanks Pierce	|Jeff Pierce
A couple of notes
You got this thing you do with your face
when you're trying to be funny
that forces people to think
about how cool you think you are.	|Pierce Jeff
Donde, está, la biblioteca. Me llamo T-Bone, la araña discoteca.	|Troy
Discoteca, muñeca, la biblioteca. Está en bigotes grandes, el perro, manteca	|Abed
Manteca, bigotes, gigante, pequeño, la cabeza es nieve, cerveza es bueno.	|Troy
Buenos dias, me gusta papas frías, los bigotes de la cabra es Cameron Diaz!	|Abed
Yeah boy. Boy.	|Abed
Yeah	|Troy
What? It's 2009.	|Abed
Word.	|Troy