Before we start,
I'd like to have a preliminary powwow,
or prelimi-wow, about what I'm calling
our library's backdoor conundrum.
Sounds like a porno with Kate Winslet.
Abed, ew.
The door on that side
is locked after 5:00,
which means that most of us
have to walk all the way around.
Now, if we were to move
our meetings to 4:30...
- No.
I have a regular class at that time.
It's like math or
other regular classes.
I have something unimportant
that can't ever move.
Well, maybe one of us
could stand by the back door
and let the rest in?
- I nominate Pierce.
- Where is he?
I have not seen him around all day.
I haven't either.
- Well, has anyone called him?
- I did.
Several times, actually,
but he never returned my calls.
Oh, no!
Oh, the last thing
I said to him was "suck it".
- Me too.
- Good morning.
- Oh!
- Yes!
Thank God.
You thought I was dead, didn't you?
No...
I did.
You people have any idea
how emasculating that is?
I'm not Mickey Rooney.
You don't have to cross your
fingers to see if I'll show up.
You know, when I was 30,
people used to wish that
I was dead to my face!
That's called respect.
Who is the lucky brunette?
Last name Beeswax,
first name none-a-ya.
Oh, my third wife was biracial.
- Stop it!
- I am just trying to help
keep you out of trouble.
What if the next girl saw these?
Well, then she would know it was hers.
Jeff!
You're sleeping with a woman
you already slept with?
Can't I be the friend in the group
whose trademark is his
well-defined boundaries,
like privacy smurf, discreet bear or...
confidentiality spice?
But if you like her,
why would you want to
keep her a secret?
Don't you want us to meet her?
We have an agreement
to keep it low-key.
That's ridiculous.
Obviously, it's a guy.
You're wrong, Pierce.
It's two guys.
Sometimes I do wish you were dead.
[Chuckles]
Thank you.
Sync by honeybunny - Corrected by 4be1
www.addic7ed.com
[rap music]
What's up, bro?
[Snaps] [Shrilly]
Boo!
Hey, what's up, J-Dog?
Woof, woof, woof, woof!
Yeah!
[Laughs]
How you doing?
* We're too gangsta for TV *
* That's why you don't see us *
* But they still wanna be us *
[rap music fades, on Broadway plays]
Sorry I'm late.
Professor Slater, quick question.
You know the answer, Mr. Winger.
I don't date students,
even if you are no longer
in my statistics class.
I'm actually kind of
seeing someone right now,
- thank you very much.
- Really? How's that going?
Fine for now. She's smart and pretty.
But sometimes I feel like
she's just waiting for me
to stop talking and take off my pants.
[Door thuds]
She is.
I've never been someone's
dirty little secret.
I've never had a dirty little secret.
It's so unprofessional.
But the sneaking does
make the sex 38% hotter.
Wow, you do like statistics,
don't you?
[Knocking on door]
Hey, midterms and whatever.
Chalk.
Professor Slater,
there's that transcript you wanted.
Jeff, I didn't expect to see you here.
Hopefully, I'm not... interrupting.
[Laughter]
You know, we laugh... but the fact is,
student/teacher relationships
do happen,
and they are a magnet for lawsuits.
So we do stay vigilant.
In fact, physically attractive
students and faculty
are actually placed on a watch list
and are ranked by their potential
to incite fraternization.
You rank people by how hot they are?
You got it... number two.
- Dean Pelton.
- Yes, Professor Seven...
- Uh, Slater.
- I'll return this tomorrow.
Okay, then.
You guys be extra careful now.
Two people of your rankings
in this small a room...
with this type of lighting
and his upper body
and what her heels and
hemline are doing
to enhance what were already
quite a few favors from God...
it's all the more important
to keep it tasteful.
[Laughs]
[Door closes]
- I think he might have ruined...
- It's dead.
[Jazzy music plays]
[music stops]
Oh, I can't wait for the recital.
You are all wonderful,
especially you, Troy.
Thank you, madame leclair.
And if any of you mention
my dancing outside of class,
I will break off your legs
and use them to smash
in your friends' cars.
- Oh!
- Huh!
[Both laughing]
Oh, my God!
Troy, since when have you
taken modern dance?
Since last semester.
Coach told me it would
help with my coordination,
and I fell in love with it,
in a very straight way.
I know it's tempting to sneak a peek,
but I'm gonna need for you
to keep your eyes up here!
God, I should have never
dismissed you as a shallow jock.
Then again, we haven't really
spent that much time together.
That's because you don't play football
or have fun.
I have fun tap-dancing.
I started last semester too.
It was always something
that I wanted to do,
but it was too embarrassing,
so I never told anyone.
Same here. Britta...
- Nobody can know about this.
- Troy, who are we kidding?
Look at how much time
and energy we're putting
into hiding something that
we're passionate about.
We are leading a double life.
I am spending a lot of
money on breakaway clothing.
We should look at this as
an opportunity to come clean.
Are you saying we tell
the group, together?
We could invite them to
the dance recital on Friday.
[Scoffs]
Man, I don't know.
Let me think about it.
Okay, let's do this.
- Ahem!
- Sorry.
Mr. Winger.
Would you come to my office?
We never finished our intercourse.
I have study group right now,
and nobody uses intercourse to
mean anything other than sex.
[chuckles]
This is a wall of windows.
My study group's behind it.
I know.
As soon as we touch,
the blinds will open,
and six annoying but loveable misfits
will be staring at us.
[Whispering]
Come on, what are the odds?
Fine.
- Now, was that so bad?
- Mm-mm.
[Shouting]
Hey!
Could you open the back door?
You all remember Michelle Slater,
my professor from last semester?
As most of you may realize by now,
she's the woman
I've been seeing lately.
Why are they looking at me
like I'm a zoo animal?
Well, Jeff acts as sort
of the dad of the group,
so emotionally this is
kind of like being told
that you're our new mom.
But you know it's
nothing like that, right?
Absolutely. Do you cook macaroni?
- I have.
- Macaroni's my favorite.
The important thing
is we all understand
Professor Slater and
I need this to be our little secret.
Everyone understand that?
- Yeah.
- Yes. I do like macaroni.
[overlapping agreement]
Sure.
[Overlapping chatter]
See? All good.
Well, thank you, everyone.
I appreciate it.
I should get going.
- Ooh!
- Ooh...
- Bye.
Well, Jeff,
you've taken a big step in
knocking down the barriers
between students and teachers...
- Just like Rosa Parks.
- I don't think it's like that.
No, it's just like that.
I feel if you need to explain it,
it's not just like that.
Is your heart gonna be okay with this?
I will try to find
the tools to survive.
Okay.
Hey, everybody, speaking of secrets,
Troy and I have something that
we would like to announce.
[shrilly] - Oh!
- No. No.
There's a dance recital on Friday,
and I would be honored
if you guys would attend,
because since last semester, I...
have been taking a tap class.
[Laughter]
That's... f... funny.
Well, I don't know how funny it is.
Come on... we're not making fun of you.
But obviously, you kept it a secret
- because you saw the irony too.
- Irony?
Well, you're not a typically
vulnerable or feminine person,
and the act of dancing is considered
- both vulnerable and feminine.
- I disagree.
What about fred Astaire?
What about Baryshnikov?
Yeah, I guess.
There are exceptions to the rule,
but even when Jerry Rice went on
dancing with the stars...
Jerry Rice?
Oh, God. I liked him.
Troy?
What... what's your secret?
Um...
M... my secret...
is that...
I knew Britta's secret.
[gasps]
Yeah.
I saw her in her dance outfit,
and she looked ridiculous.
So I helped her protect her shame.
You know, I'm just glad she's out now.
- Bravo, Britta.
- Thanks.
Mr. Winger, there you are.
Just got word of your relationship
with Professor Slater.
I'd like to see both of you
in my office in half an hour.
What the... none of you left the room.
How is that even possible?
Well, for one thing,
it's all over Twitter.
Britta in a tutu... Can you imagine?
Hey. What the hell?
I thought we were supposed to
come out to the group together.
Yeah. I changed my mind.
Well, they're gonna find out
that you dance at the recital.
I'm not gonna be in the recital.
- I'm dropping the class.
- Oh, my God.
How can you do this?
I'm so disappointed in you.
Hey, you don't get to
talk to me like that.
You are not Shirley!
And Shirley's not my mom.
Britta, it's not like we
were in the same boat.
Girls are supposed to dance.
That's why God gave them
parts that jiggle.
But I'd be going from
starting quarterback
to a guy that twirls around in tights.
I've got way more to lose
getting up on that stage
because I'm a man.
Well, guess what?
A real man doesn't bail on his friends
or on himself.
You're a dancer, Troy.
It's who you are.
Not anymore.
Excuse me.
Upset about Jeff?
No. I am upset about...
something I can't talk about.
We can talk about anything...
politics, medicine, Jeff.
Okay. Uh, did you hear
that the shroud of turin...
Here's the thing about Jeff.
Wow.
Chasing after you
made him a better person
because you always
called him on his stuff.
All this time,
you've been warming him up
and stirring in sweetener
and making him just right.
And, sure, you weren't ready
to take a sip yet,
but that didn't mean you want somebody
to snatch him off the counter
and guzzle him down
right in front of you.
Shirley, I did not warm Jeff up.
Nobody ever will.
Do you think Professor Slater
is getting flowers right now?
Do you think that they are
gonna go to the movies
and hold hands, visit her parents?
No. The only thing keeping them going
was the thrill of the secrecy,
and now that it is out,
it is over, believe me.
Can... can I just ask
as a divorced black housewife...
What part of being a
single white slacker
makes you people so jaded?
Ooh! You people?
What do you mean, you people?
I cannot believe I got to say that.
It's the little things, isn't it?
Okay, well, now that your
secret is out there,
I'm just gonna talk you
through this teacher/student
relationship form,
and then we can get you two
on your very attractive way.
We haven't even admitted
to being a couple.
In fact, this is all based on hearsay,
worse than hearsay.
Pierce's Twitter account,
in which he says he's 47
and teaches a women'
s-only pilates class.
Jeff, it's okay. It's out.
And you know what?
It doesn't bother me.
I'm happy.
Sweet.
Well... [chuckles]
First question.
"How long have you been doing it?"
Oh! [Laughs]
Not it.
I mean this... dating.
- A few weeks.
- Mm-hmm.
And... how long have you been doing it?
We don't have to answer that.
Oh, it... hmm?
Now... this is just hypothetical.
Might you ever consider
spending the night with a third person?
- That's not on there!
- Well...
Wow, it's on there.
Just exploring your options, obviously.
[Laughs]
No agenda.
I'll put "TBD".
Would you describe yourself
as boyfriend and girlfriend?
- Yes.
- Eh...
- What?
- Oh, boy.
It's semantics, really, isn't it?
[Laughs]
We've slept together
every night for the last three weeks.
How would you describe me?
The best friend ever.
Ooh.
Well, uh...
I guess I've had the
wrong idea about us.
But you know what? This is good.
I'd be better off dating,
um... an adult.
See you around.
- Michelle.
- Mm. Rarr!
I'll get the break-up form.
I got freaked out by
that boyfriend label.
I'm...
afraid of commitment.
How original.
Look, the biggest
truths aren't original.
Truth is ketchup. It's Jim Belushi.
Its job isn't to blow our minds.
It's to be within reach,
so the truth is...
I get claustrophobic
when things get official.
You're acting like I'm a Venus flytrap.
I didn't want or need more
than what we were doing.
Let's get back to it.
Should I get the door?
I can't now, because you
went to the friend place.
That's you getting official, not me,
because unless there's
something I need to know
about the lunch lady or that
blonde in your Spanish class
with the infinite supply
of leather jackets,
somewhere between our 9th
and 11th slumber party,
statistically speaking,
most people would call
us more than pals.
Yeah, but soon as you say it,
it can get complicated and messy.
- How?
- Because when you say it,
later on, you might have to un-say it.
Whoopee flippin' ding, Winger.
It happens 50 million times a day.
It's the Jim Belushi
of sexual commitments.
It barely means anything,
and it grows on what's there over time.
Boy, that guy's
really taking a pounding
in this conversation.
I'll see you around, Jeff.
[Papers rustling]
I really liked what we were doing.
And if the ratio of work to pleasure
can really stay at that same level,
I don't care what it's called.
I'll do it. Let's do it.
Okay.
Oh, that's a big crowd out there.
Abed's really good at inviting people.
We're all here to support you.
Jeff even brought his girlfriend.
Oh. She's his girlfriend now?
Can't wait till he hears about it.
Oh, he knows.
They even had to file
paperwork with the Dean.
It's pretty serious.
Our little Jeff's growing up!
[Giggling]
Oh!
Break a leg, Britta.
I have no idea
how someone could do
what you're about to do.
[Background chatter]
I brought goobers.
Anybody want a goober?
Get them while they're gooby!
[Applause]
[Tea for two plays on piano]
Well, this is already ridiculous.
Shh!
Tea for two?
There... there're five people.
Shh!
Good Lord.
Is she a water pot or a tea kettle?
Shh!
Don't you think the flowers
are dying from the tea?
- Shh!
- Shh, shh!
Everyone can hear you.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh!
[Music continues]
[whispering]
Britta.
[Piano repeating]
[whispering]
Water it!
What's going on?
So embarrassing.
[Piano repeating, audience murmuring]
Oh!
Ooh! Plot twist.
Easy, girl.
There we go.
Play something modern.
What are you doing here?
Being a friend and a man.
Oh!
[Jazzy music plays]
Culturally, it's unacceptable,
but it's theatrical dynamite!
[Jazzy music continues]
[End chords]
[Cheers and applause]
- Whoo!
- Bravo!
[Cheering]
Yeah, all right!
Bring it! Woof, woof, woof, woof!
Greendale!
Hi, guys. That was really cool.
I wish I knew how to tap-dance.
Well, thanks, Abed.
It takes a lot of hard work,
but you could always take a class.
Mm, pass.
Hey, Troy.
Thank you.
[Laughs]
No, thank you.
I mean, you looked so pathetic,
you made going up there
the most masculine option.
Troy!
[Chuckles]
What you did up there really took guts.
I'm impressed.
- Thanks, Pierce.
- Yeah.
And such a creative way to
tell the world you're gay.
- Good job up there.
- Thank you.
Where's your date?
Didn't she want to get my autograph?
Oh, she's getting a
permission slip from the Dean
to allow us to drive home together.
I heard you guys are official now.
Yeah, I guess.
You actually had a big part in that.
I mean, if I can handle
having a girl for a friend,
who's to say I'm not
ready for a girlfriend?
Makes perfect sense. Break a leg.
- Flowers.
- Yeah.
Is that... that's what
people do, right?
I was gonna throw them up on stage,
but I thought they might catch fire.
No, this is... this is good.
You can hand them to me. Thank you.
See you Monday.
[Kate nash's merry happy plays]
* Dancin' at discos,
eatin' cheese on toast *
* Yeah, you make me merry,
make me very, very happy *
* But you obviously *
* You didn't want to stick around *
* So I learnt from you *
* Do do do *
* Dah-do do-do-do-do *
* Dah-do do *
Good night, everybody.
Five letters... Broadway musical.
- Annie.
- Uh, six letters... to puncture.
Pierce.
A water filter that starts with "B".
- Brita.
- Okay.
Here's a tough one, though.
- Uh, Helen of...
- Troy.
- Oh, damn, you're good.
- Thank you.
I never even heard of that last one.
One of the two brother actors.
Bridges. Four letters.
Hmm.
I know. Bridges.
- I don't know.
- Come on, guys.
Can't you see the pattern there?
Can you see it? It's Beau... Beau Bridges!
These are all things
you can see on TV...
Except for Pierce... That's a misdirect.
- Oh.
- Hmm.
- I love misdirects.
- I love The Big Lebowski.
Sync by honeybunny - Corrected by 4be1
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net