- hey, man.
my name's Jeff.
I'm trying to lock down
the rest of my schedule
Before the deadline.
I heard this class
was a cakewalk.
Are you passing it?
Do you like dane cook?	|Jeff Extra	|99
- yeah, he's awesome.	|Extra Jeff	|99
- so far so good.	|Jeff Extra	|99
- death...
So-called...
Is a thing
that makes men weep.
And yet a third of life
is spent
In sleep.
Open your textbooks
to page 37.
Now...close them
and throw them away.
Throw it away!
For those of you
who are new,
The motto of this class:
carpe diem.
"seize the day!"
No tests! no papers.
You want an "a"?
Live in...
The moment.	|Whitman All	|01
- jackpot.	|Jeff	|01
- take off your shoes.
Quick. take off your shoes.
everyone, take your shoes off.
Throw them away.
Throw them across the room
over there.
Today, we learn to walk!
Get up and walk out the door!
This day could be your last!	|Whitman All	|01
You could die in your sleep.	|Whitman Extra	|01
You could get hit by a bus.	|Whitman Extra	|01
You, that mole is raised
and dark.	|Whitman Extra	|01
It's not a good combo.	|Whitman Extra	|01
You are new.	|Whitman Jeff	|01
- yes, i'm new.
But i'll be old too soon.
Carpe diem, sir.
carpe diem!	|Jeff Whitman	|01
- i like it!	|Whitman Jeff	|01
- voice command.
Voice command.
Voice command!
Voice com--	|Pierce	|02
- would you please use
the buttons?	|Britta Pierce	|02
- okay, grandpa.	|Pierce Britta	|02
- oh, god bless you, dear.	|Shirley Troy	|02
- what's so funny?	|Troy Group	|02
- you guys, i found it.
the ultimate blow-off class.
Professor Whitman.
he thinks
he's in dead poets society.
There's no tests.
there's no work.
It's just "day seizing."
The deadline to enroll
is tomorrow.
I suggest you all do it.	|Jeff Group	|02
- well, some of us are here
to actually learn things.	|Annie Jeff	|02
- i'm in.	|Troy Jeff	|02
- me too. it sounds educational.	|Annie Troy	|02
- i'll do it.
i love robin williams.	|Shirley Annie Jeff	|02
- abed?	|Jeff Abed	|02
- not a fan.
In every movie,
there's an authority figure
That gets mad at him
for making people laugh.	|Abed Jeff	|02
- no, are--are you going
to take the class?	|Jeff Abed	|02
- oh, can't.	|Abed Jeff	|02
My dad will only pay
for classes
That will help me run
the family restaurant.
It's been struggling
since 2001.
9/11 was pretty much the 9/11
of the falafel business.	|Abed Group	|02
- so your dad has your whole
life planned out for you?
Are you even interested
in falafel?	|Britta Abed	|02
- i'm interested
in making movies.
But my dad says
all media's western propaganda
That negatively stereotypes
arabs.	|Abed Britta	|02
- then he should see aladdin.
jafar was a bad-ass.	|Troy Group	|02
- yes, he was.	|Abed Troy	|02
- abed.	|Britta Abed	|02
- mm.	|Abed Britta	|02
- how much
does a film class cost?	|Britta Abed	|02
- $70.	|Abed Britta	|02
- Britta.	|Jeff Britta	|02
- Jeff.	|Britta Jeff	|02
- isn't abed's dad
a hardcore muslim?
They're not as understanding
as christians.
You can get your head cut off
with a salami sword.	|Shirley Britta	|02
- Shirley!
That's the most racist thing
i've ever heard.	|Annie Shirley	|02
- Pierce will beat that
in one minute.	|Jeff Annie	|02
- this is really nice of you.	|Abed Britta	|02
the memo says "for dreams."	|Abed Group	|02
- oh!	|Group Abed	|02
- you guys, are we going
to study spanish
Or keep getting involved
in each other's personal lives?	|Jeff Group	|02
- hey, Troy sneezes like a girl.	|Jeff Troy	|02
- and how about i pound you
like a boy?
That didn't come out right.	|Troy Jeff	|02
- why don't you all
just leave him alone
With his cute little
baby sneezes.	|Shirley Group	|02
- you're not my mother.	|Troy Shirley	|02
- she's not?	|Pierce Troy	|02
- 29 seconds.	|Jeff Group	|02
- what's your name?	|Whitman Shirley	|03
- my name is Shirley Bennett.	|Shirley Whitman	|03
- Shirley, you get an "a"...	|Whitman Shirley	|03
- oh.	|Shirley Whitman	|03
- if you can tell me
why you are here at greendale.	|Whitman Shirley	|03
- what'd i tell you?
Okay, but, uh,
never again.	|Jeff Troy	|04
- Shirley?	|Whitman Shirley	|03
- to get a degree in business
So i can sell my baked goods
and whatnot on the internet.	|Shirley Whitman	|03
- why...are you here?	|Whitman Shirley	|03
- to get a degree
in business
So i can sell my baked goods
and whatnot on the internet.	|Shirley Whitman	|03
- why are you here?	|Whitman Shirley	|03
- because i wasted 15 years
of my life on a man
Who left me with nothing
but stretch marks
And a foggy memory
of two bland orgasms.
And now it's time to get
what's mine.	|Shirley Whitman	|03
- day seized.
Only when we stop
stopping our lives
Can we begin to start
starting them.
Ms. Edison here, for example,
would rather write
About what happens
to other people
Than live
what is happening to her.	|Whitman All	|03
- i thought there might be
a quiz.	|Annie Whitman	|05
- well, here's a quiz for you.
Why did the pretty young girl
die alone
Surrounded
by sweater-wearing cats
Who are trained to use
human toilets?	|Whitman Annie	|05
Get up on your desk.
Come on.
stand on your desk.
Up on your desk.
She made it!
ha ha!
Everyone stand
on your desks!
Up, up, up, up, up!
come on.
Rise, rise, rise
above the programming.
All your lives you were told
don't stand on your desks.
Well, why not?	|Whitman All	|05
- ooh! ooh! oh, heaven.
My.	|Shirley Extra	|05
- she's okay.
Go to the nurse.
seize the day.	|Whitman All	|05
- you know, i was really moved
by your honesty earlier.
Particularly the part
about your husband
Not being able,
you know...	|Pierce Shirley	|06
- your homework. ah.
I want you to swim in a lake
And tell ten people
that you love them.	|Whitman All	|05
Mr. winger,
can i have a word, please?	|Whitman Jeff	|05
- are you okay.	|Annie Extra	|05
- oh, maybe i'm not.	|Extra Annie	|05
- hi.
Mr. winger, i like to think
that every life
That passes through this class
is changed.
But every year, there's always
one cocky opportunist
Who's just here to coast
and grab an easy "a."	|Whitman Jeff	|07
- oh, yeah.
his name's Pierce.
I-i can talk to him
for you.	|Jeff Whitman	|07
- It's actually you,
mr. winger.
You have no intention
of seizing the day.	|Whitman Jeff	|07
- what? listen,
i-i have never lived
Until i met you.
I-i love you.
Oh, there's one down.
nine to go.
Not that i need the grade
or even want it!	|Jeff Whitman	|07
- well, i'm glad to hear it.
Because if you don't genuinely
seize the day
Before the end of the week,
Then you will be seizing an "f"
for the semester.	|Whitman Jeff	|07
- you...
This is no way
to teach accounting!	|Jeff Whitman	|07
- i have to plan
in advance
How to prove that i live
in the moment.
I mean, i'd rather take
an actual class,
But now it's too late
to drop or add.	|Jeff Britta	|08
- it is not fair how hard it is
for you to cheat here.	|Britta Jeff	|08
hey, how's it going?
How's your film class,
buddy?	|Britta Abed	|09
- it's cool. our first
assignment is a documentary.
They're like real movies,
but with ugly people.
I'm learning a lot.	|Abed Britta	|09
- that is so wonderful.
Some people don't like
getting involved
In other's lives.
I think it's great.	|Britta Abed Jeff	|09
- hey, if you're making
a documentary
About Britta patting herself
on the back,
You're gonna need
a backup battery.	|Jeff Abed Britta	|09
- actually, i'm doing a movie
about my dad.	|Abed Jeff	|09
- that is brilliant.
How did he react to you
signing up for the film class?
- that part hasn't happened yet.
here he comes.	|Britta Jeff	|09
- hey! you want to get involved
in my family's business?	|AbedDAD	|09
- holy...war.	|Jeff	|09
- where do i find mr. Britta?	|AbedDAD Jeff	|09
- i'm mr. Britta.
That's right.
i'm a woman with rights.
And you can see
my whole face.	|Britta AbedDAD	|09
- oh, i get it!
Because i'm arab,
i must hate women.
Let me tell you something,
i love women.
But i'm getting a major
b-word vibe from you.	|AbedDAD Britta	|09
- wow, i can't believe
i missed out
On getting involved
in this.	|Jeff AbedDAD	|09
- you go host american idol
And you stop messing
with my son.
He's a special boy.
I raise him, okay?
you don't raise him.	|AbedDAD Britta	|09
- raising him means letting him
follow his dreams.	|Britta AbedDAD	|09
- dreams are for sleeping.	|AbedDAD Britta	|09
- you don't know that.	|Britta AbedDAD	|09
- it's clinically proven.	|AbedDAD Britta	|09
- so's polio.	|Britta AbedDAD	|09
- you lost me!	|AbedDAD Britta	|09
- abed wants to study film.	|Britta AbedDAD	|09
- wait, what is he saying?	|Britta Abed	|09
- he says "we're leaving."	|Abed Britta	|09
- tell him that you want
to stay and study film.	|Britta Abed	|09
- i don't think i'm really
in the scene.	|Abed Britta	|09
- see, it was hard enough
to talk to him before.
Now we have this between us!	|AbedDAD Britta Jeff Abed	|09
Let's go!	|AbedDAD Abed	|09
- hey! hey!	|Britta AbedDAD	|09
- hey, don't touch me!	|AbedDAD Britta	|09
- guys, guys, stop it.
stop it.	|Jeff Britta AbedDAD	|09
- you don't touch me!	|AbedDAD Britta	|09
- Britta back up. stop.	|Jeff Britta	|09
Sir, you have a right
to your faith
And your family's privacy.
But abed is an adult
and a u.s. citizen.	|Jeff AbedDAD	|09
Right?	|Jeff Abed	|09
- yeah.	|Abed Jeff	|09
- and he has the right
to stay.	|Jeff AbedDAD	|09
- fine. you want to raise him,
you raise him.
I'm out!	|AbedDAD Jeff	|09
- wait, what?	|Jeff AbedDAD	|09
- you know, i had a father
like you.
And the day i finally
cut myself loose
is the day
i finally started being happy.	|Britta AbedDAD	|09
- well, that went well.	|Jeff Abed	|09
- i'll have to make
some adjustments to my film.
Jeff, i think you should play
the role of my father.	|Abed Jeff	|09
- i don't want to be
your father.	|Jeff Abed	|09
- that's perfect.
you already know your lines.	|Abed Jeff	|09
What?
Why are you dressed
like an '80s rapist?	|Britta Jeff	|10
- professor Whitman
comes by here every morning
And i need him to see me
celebrating life.
What's all that?	|Jeff Britta	|10
- i am calculating
abed's expenses
For the semester.
You know, there's books.
there's meals.
He's renting that camera.
And, you know, he needs
a little spending money.	|Britta Jeff	|10
- um, all money
is spending money.	|Jeff Britta	|10
- Britta, um, it's amazing
what you're doing for abed.
I mean, a lot of people talk
a good game.
But you, you follow through.
love you.	|Shirley Britta	|10
- Shirley, thank you.
Bet that doesn't happen
to you a lot.	|Britta Shirley	|10
- happened yesterday.
Shirley's just doing
her homework.	|Jeff Britta	|10
- hillary, thank you
for getting people coffee.
I love you.	|Shirley Extra	|10
- abed,
how's it going, buddy?	|Britta Abed	|11
- good. my film
is coming together.	|Abed Britta	|11
Cool tie, Jeff.
Are you wearing that
Because you're playing
the role of my dad,
Or is it really christmas?	|Abed Jeff	|11
- definitely christmas.	|Jeff Abed	|11
- is that a new camera?	|Britta Abed	|11
- yeah.	|Abed Britta	|11
It's more expensive,
But it lets me adjust really specific settings
That most people don't notice or think about.	|Abed Britta	|11
Hi, i would like a latte.	|Abed Extra	|11
And, Jeff, let me get you something.	|Abed Jeff	|11
- i'm okay.	|Jeff Abed	|11
- oh, come on. i got you.	|Abed Jeff	|11
- no, really. i don't need anything.	|Jeff Abed	|11
- no, really. you're insulting me.
Look at all this cash.	|Abed Jeff	|11
- okay, i will get a small, black coffee.	|Jeff Abed	|12
- boo. an ordinary coffee for an ordinary life.	|Whitman Jeff	|12
- good morning, professor Whitman.	|Jeff Whitman	|12
- sorry, mr. winger, these won't cut it.	|Whitman Jeff	|12
- shazbot!	|Jeff	|12
- i shall have...
A birthday cake!	|Whitman Extra	|12
- i've seen men
in your situation, Troy.
No, those are both for me.
You were
on top of the world before
And now no one
gives a rat's ass.
I can help you
with your image.
First, lose the jacket.
You look
like a high school bitch.
But more importantly,
it's your sneeze.
When i was a ceo,
I had an array
of masculine sneezes
That asserted dominance.
You know, like,
the explosive,
Shock-the-room-into-silence
sneeze.
Or the draw-them-in sneeze.
You know...
And maybe i wouldn't sneeze
because i'm in control.
You could even use a sneeze
to drive home a point even.
Like, i think--
i think the cubs
Are going to win it all
this year.
What do you think?	|Pierce Troy	|13
- tell me more.	|Troy Pierce	|13
- it's showtime.	|Jeff	|14
Hey, everybody.
good morning.
Good morning, sir.
Good morning, greendale!
hi! good morning!
Watch the kite.
uh-oh.
Mind if i get a chance?
oh!
Look at this.
one foot.
Thanks, you guys.
bring it in here.
Nice. thank you so much,
you guys.
That was really fun.	|Jeff All	|14
- sloppy.
And considering the age
of these girls,
Unwittingly creepy.	|Whitman Jeff	|14
- damn it.	|Jeff Whitman	|14
Beat it.	|Jeff Extra	|14
Professor, will you look
at the amount of work
That i'm putting into this?
I mean, throw me a bone!	|Jeff Whitman	|14
- had i not already cried
at the sunrise this morning,
I would be weeping right now.	|Whitman Jeff	|14
- what does that mean?	|Jeff Whitman	|14
- what do you mean, Jeff?
What does your life mean?
How long does it take you
in the morning
To--to make it look
like you have bed head?
How many sweat pants,
sport jacket combos did you try
Before you found the one
that said "i don't care"?
Seize the day, Jeff,
for real.
Go running naked
in a hailstorm,
Kiss a girl in the middle
of the day,
Fly a kite,
but do it for yourself.
Or you won't just fail
my class,
You'll fail life.	|Whitman Jeff	|14
- thank you.	|Britta Whitman	|14
That guy's
really got your number.	|Britta Jeff	|15
- drop the flower.	|Jeff Britta	|15
- look, i really need
to talk to you about abed.
I went by his film class today.
he wasn't there.
He's cutting.
I want to know why he would do
something like that.	|Britta Jeff	|15
- ask him.	|Jeff Britta	|15
- every time i try to ask him
about it,
He just keeps filming me
and telling me
That i'm playing the role
of his mother.	|Britta Jeff	|15
- abed is not normal.
That's what you bought
When you intentionally tangled
yourself in his life.	|Jeff Britta	|15
- look, will you just--
will you please talk to him?	|Britta Jeff	|15
- i've got problems of my own!
I'm out here trying
to seize a day!	|Jeff Britta	|15
What in the hell?
Is he gonna kill us?	|Jeff Britta	|15
- thanks for the pizza, abed.
i was starving.	|Troy Abed	|16
- yeah, it's nice.
like a--like a picnic.	|Shirley Abed	|16
- or a family dinner.	|Pierce Abed	|16
- it's a study group
and a pizza.
Let's not get carried away.	|Jeff Group	|16
- so, abed,
how's film class?	|Jeff Abed	|16
- good.	|Abed Jeff	|16
- yeah? did you go
to class today?	|Jeff Abed	|16
- not really.	|Abed Jeff	|16
- not really.
Well, Britta's paying
for those classes.
Don't you think
maybe you should go?	|Jeff Abed	|16
- i was shooting my movie.	|Abed Jeff	|16
- yeah, but your movie's
for class.	|Britta Abed	|16
- my movie's more important.	|Abed Britta	|16
- well, ooh la la.	|Britta Abed	|16
- someone order
seven lattes?	|Extra Group	|16
- i got that.	|Abed Extra	|16
- no, you don't got it.
I got it, abed.
i got everything.
What is wrong with you?
All i want to do
is take care of you.
I know you're not stupid.
are you doing this on purpose?
Why won't you answer me?	|Britta Extra	|16
- 'cause this is the scene
where you leave.	|Abed Britta	|16
- you better believe it.	|Britta Abed	|16
- Britta.	|Jeff Abed	|16
- what do you think, dad?	|Abed Jeff	|16
- i think you are
really weird, abed.
And i think the wrong person
just left.	|Jeff Abed	|16
- perfect.
that's a wrap.	|Abed Group	|16
- that guy was your dad?	|Extra Abed	|16
- hey.	|Jeff Britta	|17
- hey.
You don't really have tickets
for ravi shankar, do you?	|Britta Jeff	|17
- i lied to get you here
Because it's time
to communicate.	|Jeff Britta	|17
- communicate.
have you met abed?	|Britta Jeff	|17
- it's not the two of you
that need to talk.	|Jeff Britta	|17
- hey, wait a minute,
where's weezer?	|AbedDAD Jeff	|17
- they're coming.	|Jeff AbedDAD	|17
All right, now,
the only reason
Why this whole mess
got started
Is because both of you wanted
the best for abed.
And i think the lesson
we can all take away from this
Is that everyone
should always do
Whatever they want
and leave each other out of it.	|Jeff AbedDAD Britta	|17
- is that your take?
let me give you mine.
You and your pillow-lipped
girlfriend
Got all up in my stuff
because you wanted to be cowboys
And then you turned chicken
when you found out
It will take more than speeches
and guided missiles.	|AbedDAD Jeff Britta	|17
- interesting. hadn't seen
the iraq metaphor, but--	|Jeff AbedDAD	|17
- what iraq metaphor?
I am talking
about your speeches
And her guided--	|AbedDAD Jeff	|17
- got it!	|Jeff AbedDAD	|17
The point is is that Britta
is sorry, right?	|Jeff Britta	|17
- wrong.	|Britta Jeff	|17
- crap.	|Jeff	|17
- abed may not be
a great filmmaker,
But that doesn't mean
that he wants to make falafel.
You need to let him make
his own decisions.	|Britta AbedDAD	|17
- make his own decisions?
Have you met abed?
you know who he is?	|AbedDAD Britta	|17
- guys.	|Jeff Britta AbedDAD	|17
- yes.	|Britta AbedDAD	|17
- guys!	|Jeff Britta AbedDAD	|17
- he loves--	|AbedDAD Britta	|17
- i'm finished.	|Abed Jeff Britta AbedDAD	|18
Britta, Jeff, dad.	|Abed Jeff Britta AbedDAD	|18
- how's it going, buddy?	|Britta Abed	|18
- i don't want to be
your father.
I think
you are weird, abed.	|Jeff Abed	|18
- okay, look, i need to talk
to you about abed.	|Britta Jeff	|18
- he's not normal.	|Jeff Britta	|18
- what is wrong with you?
All i want to do
is take care of you.
Why will you not answer me?	|Britta Abed	|18
- what do you think, dad?	|Abed Jeff	|18
- i think you are weird,
abed.
And i think the wrong person
just left.	|Jeff Abed	|18
- it's not exactly
citizen kane.	|Jeff Britta	|18
- i feel a little out
of the loop here.	|Britta Jeff	|18
- that feeling is called
the joy of freedom.	|Jeff Britta	|18
- my son is hard
to understand.
If making movies help him
be understood,
Then i pay for the class.	|AbedDAD Jeff Britta	|18
i made this all happen.	|Britta Jeff	|18
- with falafel as a fallback.	|AbedDAD Jeff Britta	|18
- abed.	|Britta Abed	|19
- yeah.	|Abed Britta	|19
- did you do all of that
to me on purpose?
That's not a very nice way
to treat your friends.	|Britta Abed	|19
- well, Britta, it isn't called
friend business,
It's called show business.	|Abed Britta	|19
- he's smoking.	|Britta Jeff	|19
- honey, let him leave
the nest.	|Jeff Britta	|19
- get your hand off my knee.	|Britta Jeff	|19
- sorry.	|Jeff Britta	|19
- god--god bless you.
god bless you.	|Shirley Troy	|20
- thank you.	|Troy Shirley	|20
- for someone who doesn't like
getting involved,
Well, i owe you.	|Britta Jeff	|21
- you owe me.
That cannot be comfortable
for you.	|Jeff Britta	|21
- hey, um, you should kiss me
right now.	|Britta Jeff	|21
- day seized!	|Whitman Jeff	|21
- we're even.	|Britta Jeff	|21
"a" plus, winger.
I know a life-changing kiss
when i see one.
Wowee! ha ha!	|Whitman Jeff	|21
- yeah. fooled you.	|Jeff Britta	|21
- am I krumping?	|Abed Troy	|22
- no.	|Troy Abed	|22
- am I krumping now?	|Abed Troy	|22
No!
This is krumping.	|Abed Troy	|22
We are krumping.	|Troy Jeff	|22
No you are not	|Jeff Troy	|22