Good morning.
How do we turn this off? Mother, you think
you can come and help me turn it off?
How do we turn this off?
Can you help me with this?
Oh, thank you, thank you so much.
I didn't mean to snap.
- uh, good morning.
Many of you
are halfway through
Your first week here
at greendale
And as your dean,
i thought i would
Share a few thoughts
of wisdom and inspiration.
What is community college?
Well, you've heard
all kinds of things.
You've heard it's
"loser college
For remedial teens,
20-something dropouts,
Middle-age divorcees,
And old people keeping
their minds active
As they circle
the drain of eternity."
That's what you heard.
However, i wish you luck!
Okay, you know--
uh-oh.
Okay, there's more
to this speech.
There's actually a middle card
that is missing.
Can we all look around our
immediate areas,
'cause i really wanted to--	|Dean
- i'm only half-arabic,
actually.
My dad is palestinian.
he's a u.s. citizen.
He's not a threat to national
security or anything.
A lot of people want to know
that after they meet him,
Because he has
an angry energy.
But not, like,
angry at america.
Just angry at my mom
for leaving him.
Although she did leave
because he was angry
And he was angry
because she's american.
My name's abed,
by the way.	|Abed Jeff
- abed, nice to know you and
then meet you in that order.
Now about that question
that i had--	|Jeff Abed
- oh, uh...
5 after 11:00
when you asked.	|Abed Jeff
- abed?	|Jeff Abed
- yeah?	|Abed Jeff
- what's the deal with
the hot girl from spanish class?
I can't find a road
in there.	|Jeff Abed
- well, i only talked
to her once
While she was borrowing
a pencil, but...
Her name is britta, she's 28,
birthday in october,
She has two older brothers
and one of 'em
Works with children
who have a disorder
I might want to look up.
Oh, and she thinks
she's gonna flunk
Tomorrow's test,
so she really needs to focus
So she's sorry
if that makes her seem cold.	|Abed Jeff
- holy crap.
Abed...
I see your value now.	|Jeff Abed
- that's the nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me.	|Abed Jeff
Absolutely not.	|Duncan
If these guys knew you like I did
they would have given you a small office.	|Jeff Duncan
- jeff winger!
Genius at law.	|Duncan Jeff
- you got to stop saying that.	|Jeff Duncan
- i will never do that. sit down
I still cannot figure out how you
gonna join
September the 11th with my DUI,
that alone, why that helped.	|Duncan Jeff
Well, 2002 was a simple time.	|Jeff Duncan
So what is my lawyer
doing here?	|Duncan Jeff
- i'm a student.	|Jeff Duncan
- well, that cannot be
an inspiring journey.	|Duncan Jeff
- uh, i am in a bit
of a jam.	|Jeff Duncan
The state bar has
suspended my license.	|Jeff Ducnan
They found out my college degree
Was less than legitimate.	|Jeff Duncan
- i thought you had a bachelor's
from columbia.	|Duncan Jeff
- now i have to get one
from america.	|Jeff Duncan
- and it can't be
an email attachment.	|Jeff Duncan
- well, you've picked
a fine school.	|Duncan Jeff
- yes, and i'm hoping
that our friendship
Will yield certain advantages.
You know, academic guidance...	|Jeff Duncan
- yes.	|Duncan Jeff
- moral support,
Every answer
to every test
For every one of the classes
that i'm taking.
Here's my schedule.	|Jeff Duncan
- no. Now, jeff, just by asking that,
You have insulted the integrity
of this entire institution.	|Duncan Jeff
Waster!
not a bathroom!
Not a bathroom.	|Duncan
- okay. Duncan, you...
did seem less into integrity
The day that i convinced
12 of yours peers that when you made
that u-turn on the freeway
And tried to order chalupas
from the emergency call box,
That your only real crime
was loving america.	|Jeff Duncan
Well, I do love America, I do love it,
very much.
I love chalupas.
But...
- i'll look into it. 	|Duncan Jeff
- thank you.
Duncan, you are a good man.	|Jeff Duncan
- jeff, are you familiar with the adage,
"cheaters never prosper"?	|Duncan Jeff
No...
and if i wanted to learn something,
I wouldn't have come to community college.	|Jeff Duncan
- oh, hey! spanish.	|Jeff Britta
- uh, don't hit on me, okay?	|Britta Jeff
- whoa.
I wouldn't dream of it.
I just wanted to let you know
about my spanish study group.	|Jeff Britta
the guy who's playing bejeweled
on his iphone all class has a study group?
Um, can i sign up twice?	|Britta Jeff
- i'm taking the class as an easy credit.
I'm actually a spanish tutor.	|Jeff Britta
- Board certified.	|Jeff Britta
- can you say that in spanish now?	|Britta Jeff
- i really need help with spanish.	|Britta Jeff
- yeah, i was willing to bet.. i'm jeff.
Or "Jefe".
- We meet at the library at 4:00.	|Jeff Britta
- yeah, britta. thanks.	|Britta Jeff
You gonna be there?
Un po' di piu'.
That means "See you there".	|Jeff Britta
Shouldn't be too hard to fake
a study group, right?
Oh, geez, I'm sorry... I...
I was raised on TV and I was conditioned
to believe that every...
Black woman over 50 is a cosmic mentor..	|Jeff Extra
Were you conditioned to pay
for your damn taco, Sanfield?	|Extra Jeff
Yes, I'm so sorry.
It's Seinfeld.	|Jeff Extra
Bienvenido.	|Jeff
Bienvenuto!
Hey, all right,
come on in.
- I got the whole table. Welcome.	|Jeff Britta
- Yeah.
- We have the whole room.	|Britta Jeff
- Yeah, here's the, uh...
contact sheet.
Just put your stuff there.
Man.
Rest of the group
is running late.
But you and i can
get acquainted.	|Jeff Britta
- you may have noticed this morning,
Not so good at the small talk.	|Britta Jeff
- yeah, i like big talk.
what's your deal?	|Jeff Britta
- that's not small talk?	|Britta Jeff
- what's your deal and is god dead?	|Jeff Britta
- all right, you want
to know my deal?
I dropped out of high-school because
I thought for some reason
it would impress Radiohead.	|Britta Jeff
You'd be surprised what gets back
to these guys.	|Jeff Britta
I joined the peace corp.
I did a little foot modelling,
I got tear gased in a World Trade Rally...	|Britta Jeff
Marry me.	|Jeff Britta
And I think, Jeff, my deal is above all else,
honesty.	|Britta Jeff
- honesty?	|Jeff Britta
- yeah.
You tell me the truth,
i will like you.
You lie to me, i will never talk to you again.
That's my deal.	|Britta Jeff
- ah, that's a good deal.	|Jeff Britta
- So what's your deal?	|Britta Jeff
- uh, i would have to go--
I would have to say,
um, honesty,
Because...
I would say anything
to get what i want.
And i want you
to like me. So, uh..	|Jeff Britta
- wow.
that's a very honest answer.
All right,
now i like you fine.	|Britta Jeff
- really? Wow. you're easy.	|Jeff Britta
- hell yeah.	|Britta Jeff
Abed in the house!	|Britta Abed
- why?	|Jeff Abed
- britta invited me. is that cool?	|Abed Jeff
- oh, i can't think
of a single logical reason why not.	|Jeff Abed
- cool.	|Abed Jeff
- there you go.
Oh, hey, here. Put your contact info down
right there.
That's right.	|Jeff Abed
- cool, cool, cool.
Cool, cool, cool.
hey, this is kind of like
breakfast club, huh?	|Abed Jeff Britta
- we are in a library.	|Britta Abed
- yeah.
i'm sure we've each got an issue balled up inside of us
that would make us cry if we talked about it.	|Abed Jeff Britta
- do you have something
balled up inside of you?	|Britta Abed
- well, i got a little doozy
in the chamber if things get emotional.	|Abed Jeff
Oh.
hey, text message.
- Let's give this bad boy a read.	|Abed Jeff Britta
- it's probably just for your eyes.	|Jeff Abed
- I've never got one of these	|Abed Jeff Britta
- Well, it's jut.. You probably...
- it's probably just for your eyes.	|Jeff Abed
- "say you have to pee. i need to talk to you."	|Abed Jeff Britta
"say you have to pee."	|Abed Britta
- that is weird.	|Britta Abed
- "say you have to pee. I need to talk to you."	|Abed Jeff
- do you have to pee?	|Jeff Abed
- no.	|Abed Jeff
- hmm.	|Jeff Abed
- that's so weird.	|Abed Jeff
- well, i'm stumped. That's very creepy.
That's very creepy.	|Jeff Abed
- does it say you have to pee?	|Abed Jeff
- no, it's just someone
With a misguided grasp
of abbreviation.	|Jeff Abed
I just need five minutes, you guys,
So go ahead and study
all the verbs...in spanish.	|Jeff Abed Britta
- Abed...	|Britta Abed
- Yeah?	|Abed Britta
What's your read on that guy?	|Britta Abed
You look like Elisabeth Shue.	|Abed Britta
Act natural, pretend you are watching
the athletic proceedings.	|Duncan Jeff
I couldn't stop watching them.
There's a guy going for the track, that's older
than the game of poker.
He's kinda cracking.	|Jeff Duncan
- suppose i was to say to you
It was possible to get those test answers?	|Duncan Jeff
- i would say, "go for that,"
And could have said so in a text.	|Jeff Duncan
- i'm asking you if you know the difference
Between right and wrong.	|Duncan Jeff
- i discovered at a very early age
That if i talk long enough,
I could make anything
right or wrong.
So either i'm god
or truth is relative.
And in either case,
booyah.	|Jeff Duncan
- oh, interesting. It's just the average person has
a much harder time saying,
"booyah,"
to moral relativism.	|Duncan Jeff
- duncan, you don't have to play shrink
To protect your pride.
I accept.
you're chicken.	|Jeff Duncan
Are you trying to use reverse psychology
on a psychologist?	|Duncan Jeff
No, I'm just using regular psychology
on a spineless, British twit.	|Jeff Duncan
- i'm a professor.
you can't talk to me that way.	|Duncan Jeff
- a six-year-old girl could talk to you that way.	|Jeff Duncan
- yes, because that would be adorable!	|Duncan Jeff
- No, because you're a five-year-old girl
And there's a pecking order.	|Jeff Duncan
- fine! i'll do it!	|Duncan Jeff
- thank you.	|Jeff Duncan
- yeah, pleasure.
Bye!
Yes!
good!
Why am i still shouting?
I'm drawing attention
to myself.	|Duncan Jeff
- you guys aren't gonna believe this,
But the rest of the group...
Is here.	|Jeff Britta Abed
- are you
the board-certified tutor?	|Pierce Jeff
- that means you do my homework,
right, Seacrest?	|Troy Jeff
- i need to call my babysitter
If we're gon' be later than 10:00.	|Shirley Jeff
- what board certifies
a tutor?	|Annie Jeff
- where's britta?	|Jeff Abed
- not sure.
But i invited more people
from spanish class. Is that cool? 	|Abed Jeff
- it's the coolest.	|Jeff Abed
I'm gonna go
to the bathroom
And bring my jacket,
wallet,
and keys with me
In case there's a fire.	|Jeff Group
- should we go with him?	|Shirley Group
- i'm leaving my homework with
slumdog millionaire over here.	|Troy Group
- that's borderline racist,
i think.	|Shirley Troy
- and busted.	|Britta Jeff
- uh, listen.	|Jeff Britta
- now you know. I'm a smoker.	|Britta Jeff
- yeah, but they're filtered,
so that makes them safe.	|Jeff Britta
- you ready to get started?
Looks like the rest of your group showed up.	|Britta Jeff
- yeah, not mine, actually.
I think abed took out a page on craigslist.
And i was trained never
to say this,
But i think that group
may be untutorable.	|Jeff Britta
- oh, really?	|Britta Jeff
- so why don't you and i
go study over--	|Jeff Britta
- dinner?	|Britta Jeff
- or drinks.	|Jeff Britta
- i think, actually,
we should prioritize here
And study first
and then go to dinner.
And if they really prove
to be untutorable, we'll slip out early.	|Britta Jeff
- oh...they will be...
untutorable.	|Jeff
- all right.
Look at this crew.
All ready to study all night.	|Jeff Group
- well, i can stay
at least till 10:00.	|Shirley Group
- but who studies
with strangers, right?
My name is jeff.	|Jeff Group
- jeff, it's a pleasure.
My name is pierce hawthorne
and, yes,
That is hawthorne as in hawthorne wipes,
The award-winning moist towellete.	|Pierce Jeff
- i was just going to ask.	|Jeff Pierce
- i'm also a toast master, so perhaps
I should do the introductions.	|Pierce Group
- definitely!	|Jeff Pierce
- all right, you already know brittles.	|Pierce Jeff
- britta.	|Britta Pierce
- abed. Abed the arab.
Is that inappropriate?	|Pierce Jeff
- sure.	|Abed Pierce
- roy. roy the wonder boy.	|Pierce Jeff
- "Troy".	|Troy Pierce
- little princess elizabeth.	|Pierce Jeff
- "Annie".	|Annie Pierce
- and finally, this beautiful
creature is named shirley.	|Pierce Jeff
- is that even close?	|Jeff Shirley
- i'd like to know why i had to find out
About this group on accident?	|Annie Group
- - this is getting way more like breakfast club now.	|Abed Group
- there's breakfast?	|Pierce Abed
- okay, um, maybe we should
get started--	|Britta Group
- you know, i've been a part
of a lot of study groups that fell apart
because
of unresolved tension.
Shouldn't we address Annie's concern?
Did we not invite her?	|Jeff Group
- well, annie, sweetie,
it's not behind your back.
- We just didn't think about...	|Shirley Jeff
- can we stop with the "pumpkins" and the "sweeties"?
Being younger does
not make me inferior.
If anything, your age indicates
That you've made bad life decisions.	|Annie Shirley
- shirley has a response to that.	|Jeff Shirley
- no, no, no. i don't.	|Shirley Jeff
- you should. it looks like you do.	|Troy Shirley
- please, shirley.	|Jeff Shirley
- okay, okay.
I'm sure i've made
some bad life decisions
And maybe annie's decisions
will be better.
But i think she needs to decide
Whether she wants to be considered a child
Or an adult, because children get pity
But not respect. And adults,
they get respect,
But they also get the back of they head grabbed
And their face pushed through jukeboxes.	|Shirley Annie
- okay.
Why don't we try learning
"jukebox" in spanish?	|Britta Group
- what are you doing?	|Shirley Pierce
- pierce!
- Let's discuss this creepiness.	|Jeff Pierce
- pardon you?	|Pierce Jeff
- what are you doing?	|Britta Jeff
- i'm certified.	|Jeff Britta
Are you unaware that shirley
Finds your advances inappropriate?	|Jeff Pierce
what advances?	|Pierce Jeff
- you have been sexually harassing me
Since the very first day of class.	|Shirley Pierce
- sexually harassing?
what? That makes no sense to me.
Why would i harass somebody
who turns me on?	|Pierce Shirley
- saying she turns you on
is the harassment, dude.	|Troy Pierce
- hey.	|Pierce Troy
I am a prominent business leader
And a highly sought after dinner guest
And i will not take courting advice
From some teenage boy.	|Pierce Group
well, this teenage boy
is a quarterback and a prom king.	|Troy Pierce
- you're not prom king anymore, troy.
This isn't riverside high.	|Annie Troy
- how'd you know
i went there?	|Troy Annie
- because you're still wearing
your stupid letter jacket.
And more importantly, I sat behind you
in Algebra.	|Annie Troy
Wait, you're that girl that got hooked on pills
and then dropped out.
You're little Annie "Adderall".	|Troy Jeff
Yes, and you are a stupid jock
who lost his scholarship
by dislocating both shoulders
in a keg stand.	|Annie Troy
Keg flip.
They're very hard to pull off.
You don't know--
I'm a legend.	|Troy Annie
You know what I got
for Christmas?
It was a banner year
at the Bender family.
I got a carton
of cigarettes.
The old man grabbed me, he said,
"Hey, smoke up, Johnny!"
"No, dad!
What about you?"	|Abed Group
Well, uh...
that--
That actually was from
The Breakfast Club.	|Jeff Abed
Nobody puts baby
in the corner.	|Abed Jeff
Dirty Dancing.
Hello.	|Jeff Group
It's Professor Duncan.
Come to the parking lot now.	|Duncan Jeff
What's wrong
with your voice?	|Jeff Duncan
I'm disguising it.	|Duncan Jeff
Uh, I'll be right back.
But while I'm gone, you guys need
to hash this stuff out.
No stone unturned.
- Go!	|Jeff Group
- What does that...	|Pierce Group
- I can't feel my...	|Abed Group
Get in the car!
Act as if either you have just finished
or yet to begin driving.
Every answer to every test
in your curriculum this semester.	|Duncan Jeff
I knew you could
do it, buddy. Thank you.	|Jeff Duncan
Whoa there, grabby-grabby.
- What do I get?	|Duncan Jeff
- The satisfaction of being even.	|Jeff Duncan
Even, fairness, right, wrong.
There is no God.
- Booyah, booyah.	|Duncan Jeff
- What do you want from me?	|Jeff Duncan
- Your Lexus.	|Duncan Jeff
- My car for a semester's worth of answers?	|Jeff Duncan
Will it be just
a semester though, Jeff?
Won't you be taking the easy way out
for the next four years?
I want payment in advance.
I want leather seats
with built-in ball warmers.	|Duncan Jeff
You know, bluffs this weak are how
your people lost the colonies.	|Jeff Duncan
Have a nice disbarment
hearing.	|Duncan Jeff
- What am I supposed to drive?	|Jeff Duncan
- Why don't you take this car? It's good for the earth.	|Duncan Jeff
Yeah, so is wiping your butt with a leaf,
but it's not how a man gets around!
A golf kart!	|Jeff
- It is a disaster in there.	|Britta Jeff
- Yeah, untutorable.
- You like Thai food? I love Thai food.	|Jeff Britta
- Wait...
so... this
is a game to you?
You put human beings
into a state of emotional shambles
for a shot
at getting in my pants?	|Britta Jeff
Why can't you see that
for the compliment that it is?
Ok, ok. I'm sorry.
It was an accident.
I did a little bit of lying
to get close to you.
But how was I suppose to know
that you were smart and cool...
I mean, you look like Elisabeth Shue.	|Jeff Britta
- You're unbelievable.	|Britta Jeff
- What do you want me to do?	|Jeff Britta
Oh, maybe one decent thing could be
to go in there and clean up your mess.	|Britta Jeff
Okay, I am the Barack Obama
of this room.	|Troy Group
Okay, if i do that,
then dinner, right?	|Jeff Britta
Yeah, fine, whatever.
As if there's a dinner on Earth that could
make me forget you are a shallow douchebag.	|Britta Jeff
Oh, you're gonna eat those words
when you see my new car.	|Jeff Britta
All right, everybody!
I want to say something.
Everybody, sit down.	|Jeff Group
You don't have to yell.	|Shirley Jeff
You know what makes humans
different from other animals?	|Jeff Group
Feet.	|Troy Jeff
No, no, no, come on.
Bears have feet.	|Pierce Troy
We're the only species on Earth
that observes Shark Week.
Sharks don't even observe
Shark Week, but we do.
For the same reason I can pick up this pencil,
tell you it's name is Steve,
and go like this.
And part of you dies just
a little bit on the inside,
because people can connect
with anything.
We can sympathize
with a pencil.
We can forgive a shark. And we can give
Ben Affleck an Academy Award for Screenwriting.	|Jeff Group
- Big mistake.	|Pierce Group
- He's got a point.	|Troy Pierce
People can find the good
in just about anything but themselves.
Look at me. It's clear to
all of you that I am awesome,
but I can never admit that,
because that would make me an ass.
But what I can do is see
what makes Annie awesome.
She's driven.
We need driven people or the lights go out
and the ice cream melts.
And Pierce.
We need guys like Pierce.
This guy has
wisdom to offer.	|Jeff Group
- The Dalai Lama and I--	|Pierce Group
- We should listen to him sometime.
We wouldn't regret it.
And Shirley.
Shirley has earned
our respect,
Not as a wife, not as a mother,
but as a woman.
And don't test her on that,
because that thing about the jukebox
was way too specific
to be improvised.
And Troy.
Who cares if Troy
thinks he's all that?
Maybe he is.
You think astronauts go to the moon
because they hate oxygen? No!
They're trying to impress
their high-school prom king.
And Abed.
Abed's a shaman.
You ask him to pass the salt,
he gives you a bowl of soup,
because you know what?
Soup is better.
Abed is better.
You are all better
than you think you are.
You are just designed not to believe it
when you hear it from yourself.	|Jeff Group
Soup?	|Pierce Abed
I want you to look
to the person to your left.
Sorry. Look at the person
sitting next to you.	|Jeff Group
Look at her?
Okay.	|Shirley Jeff
- This?	|Abed
- Yeah.
I want you to extend
to that person
the same compassion that you extend
to sharks, pencils, and Ben Affleck.
I want you to say
to that person,
"I forgive you."	|Jeff Group
- I forgive you.	|Shirley Annie
- I forgive you.	|Annie Shirley
- I forgive you.	|Troy Pierce
- You little twerp.	|Pierce Troy
Pierce, I'd like you to say,
"I forgive you."	|Jeff Pierce
He didn't say it?	|Shirley Jeff
I forgive you.	|Pierce Troy
You've just stopped being
a study group.
You have become something...
unstoppable.
I hereby pronounce you...
a community.	|Jeff Group
Oh, that's nice.
I like that.	|Shirley Group
This isn't like
Breakfast Club anymore.
Now it's like Stripes or Meatballs.
Anything with Bill Murray, really.	|Abed Jeff
I agree with Abed that tonight
has been very special.
And now,
if you'll excuse me,
I have a dinner engagement
with Britta.
Britta?	|Jeff Group
I lied.
Thanks for calming
everyone down.
but since you're not a Spanish tutor,
just a lying creep
who purposely upset everyone
in an attempt to get with me,
I'd appreciate it if you left
and stopped wasting all of our time.	|Britta Jeff
Everybody ready?	|Britta Group
Fine.	|Jeff Britta
And I'm happy to report
that one of the benefits
of being a lying creep
is having all the answers
to tomorrow's test.
And I'm happy to share them with anyone
whose time I've wasted more
than they've wasted mine.	|Jeff Group
Uh, Jeff, if you have all the answers,
why the hell did you start this study group?	|Pierce Jeff
I don't have a study group, Pierce.
I made it up.	|Jeff Pierce
- What about the "Look Left" speech?	|Annie Jeff
- Made it up. That's what I do.	|Jeff Annie
I make things up,
and I got paid a lot of money
to do it before I came
to this school-shaped toilet.
I was a lawyer.	|Jeff Group
- Oh, God.	|Group
- That explains everything.	|Shirley Group
You know, I thought you were like Bill Murray in any of
his films, but you're more like Michael Douglas in any of his films.	|Abed Jeff
- Yeah?	|Jeff Abed
- Yeah.	|Abed Jeff
Well, you have Asperger's.	|Jeff Abed
What did he say?	|Abed Britta
"Ass-burger".	|Troy
- It's a serious disorder.	|Annie Troy
- It really is.	|Shirley Troy
If it's so serious,
why don't they call it meningitis?	|Pierce Annie Shirley
- "Ass-burger".	|Pierce
- Burger for your ass.	|Troy Pierce
Jeffrey, before you say anything, you may
want to think about the gift you've been given.	|Duncan Jeff
- An excuse to punch a hippy?	|Jeff Pierce
- No. No, not that.
An important lesson,
my friend. You see,
the tools you acquired to survive out there
will not help you here at Greendale.
What you have, my friend,
is a second chance at an honest life.	|Duncan Jeff
Why are people trying
to teach me things
At a school that has
an express tuition aisle?
- Give me the keys.	|Jeff Duncan
- No, I have to keep your car for--
Don't hit me.
Please, don't hit me.
Jeffrey, Jeffrey!
Are we cool?
We're cool.	|Duncan Jeff
I like you, Jeffrey.
You remind me of myself
at your age.	|Pierce Jeff
I deserve that.	|Jeff Pierce
You know,
I've been divorced
seven times.
Sometimes, I think I'm doing
something wrong.	|Pierce Jeff
You keep getting married.	|Jeff Pierce
I never looked at it
that way.	|Pierce Jeff
Shouldn't you guys
be studying?	|Jeff Pierce Troy
Yeah, things got kind
of boring after you left.
Let me ask you something.
People becloud me for wearing this jacket
ever since I got here, but
If I take it off to make them happy,
That just makes me weak, right?	|Troy Jeff
Listen,
it doesn't matter.
You lose the jacket to please them,
you keep it to piss them off,
Either way
It's for them.
That's what's weak..	|Jeff Troy
Wow.
You just wrinkled my brain, man.	|Troy Jeff
- He's good, isn't he?	|Pierce Troy
- He's really good.	|Troy Pierce
Shouldn't you be rolling around
on a bed covered in test answers?	|Britta Jeff
I don't have any
of the answers.
I'm gonna--
I'm gonna flunk the test.	|Jeff Group
You just, like, study for, like, an hour.
It's not that hard.
You seem pretty smart.
You got a sports coat.	|Troy Jeff
I am me...
Well, the funny thing
about being smart
is that you can get through most of life
without ever having to do any work.
So, uh...
I'm not really sure
how to do that.	|Jeff Group
What's going on?
Can you guys hear me?
Am I deaf?
- Can you hear me talking right now?	|Abed Group
- Yes.	|Group Abed
That's good.	|Abed Group
You know what?
Jeff, actually, we didn't
get that far without you, so
if you want
to come back upstairs--	|Britta Jeff
Really?	|Jeff Britta
Well, it is your
study group, so.	|Britta Jeff
Come on, let's study.	|Shirley Jeff
Sounds good.	|Pierce Group
No pressure.	|Troy Jeff
I'm sorry I called you Michael Douglas
and I see your value now.	|Abed Jeff
Well, that's the nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me.	|Jeff Abed