- good morning,
greendale community college.
This is your dean
reminding you
That among your school's
prestigious alumni
Is mr. luis guzman,
celebrated actor
And model
puerto-rican american.
This friday, we will be
dedicating a statue of guzman
And unveiling
our brand-new school song.
So boy,
i don't know about you,
But this sure feels like
a real college to me.	|Dean All	|01
- greendale, greendale,
Greendale!	|DeanBot	|01
- ah! Jeff, Jeff.
Good morning!
How is student life,
my dry-witted friend?	|Duncan Jeff	|02
- probably the same
as teacher life,
But less tragic,
because i get to leave.	|Jeff Duncan	|02
- very dry.
very witty.
Not a great friend.
Listen, i wanted to ask you
about that young lady
In your spanish class.
You know, the blonde
with the pouty, strident
Cate blanchett sexuality
and the ridiculous name?	|Duncan Jeff	|02
- Britta?	|Jeff Duncan	|02
- that's it, that's it.
Imagine living with that.
can you imagine?
Unbelievable.
Anyway, are you two an item,
and if so,
Would that item be
impervious to sabotage?	|Duncan Jeff	|02
- you know, you have
the savoir faire of a hyena.
How is it that you
and james bond
Come from the same island?	|Jeff Duncan	|02
- message received.
I'll just wait for you
to finish striking out first.
- cheers.	|Duncan Jeff	|02
- m.a.s.h.	|Abed Duncan	|03
- fawlty towers.
game over.	|Duncan Abed	|03
Have a nice day.	|Duncan Jeff	|02
- do you think luis guzman
Will ever come
to visit his statue?
If so, i'd like to ask him
about his movie choices,
particularly carlito's way,
the cowboy way, the hard way,
and q&a.	|Abed Troy	|04
- yeah, luis guzman is
on a private jet from hollywood,
Because he can't wait to have
that conversation with you.	|Troy Abed	|04
- really?
how does he know about me?	|Abed Troy	|04
- because he called me
on my cell phone.	|Troy Abed	|04
- why would a movie actor
call you?	|Abed Troy	|04
- you don't know?	|Troy Abed	|04
- no.	|Abed Troy	|04
- i'm president obama's nephew.	|Troy Abed	|04
- you never mentioned that.	|Abed Troy	|04
- i didn't know
if i could trust you.
But now it's time
to tell you everything--
Starting with me
inventing the ferrari.	|Troy Abed	|04
- so...i guess
the cell phone number
You put on the study group's
contact sheet was fake,
Which i just learned
in the awkward conclusion
Of a month-long text message
affair with a dude from boulder.	|Jeff Britta	|05
- sorry.	|Britta Jeff	|05
- that's okay.
Just give me
your real number.
I'll cleanse my palate while
kevin rethinks his marriage.	|Jeff Britta	|05
I'll give you my number
if you promise not to use it
In any other context
than friendship.	|Britta Jeff	|05
- uh...pass.	|Jeff Britta	|05
- silencio, por favor.	|Chang All	|06
Star burns--
that means you.	|Chang Starburns	|06
- my name's alex, dude.	|Starburns Chang	|06
- well, maybe you should
spend five hours
Sculpting that
in your face.	|Chang Starburns	|06
All right, last night
i graded your tests.
I'm sure you wanna know
how you did, right?	|Chang All	|06
- yes, i would.	|All Chang	|06
- well, i'm not gonna tell you.
Until i find out
who did...this!	|Chang All	|06
- what is that?	|Shirley Chang	|06
- it's a tiny piece of paper,
okay?
That's all it is.
tiny piece of paper.	|Chang Shirley	|06
Containing all the information
covered on the test.
Otherwise known
as a crib sheet.
Who did it, huh?	|Chang All	|06
Marianne?	|Chang Annie	|06
grandpa?	|Chang Pierce	|06
Jackee?	|Chang Shirley	|06
Kumar?	|Chang Abed	|06
There's one asian stereotype
that does apply to me.
Whoever did this
insulted my honor.
And they've got 24 hours
to come forward,
Or mr. miyagi here
will wax off everyone's score
and the whole class
gets a cero!	|Chang All	|06
'cept you, toby.	|Chang Extra	|06
- the only difference between
senor chang and stalin
Is that i know
who senor chang is.	|Troy Group	|07
- did you hear him call me
jackee
Like i'm some black
female caricature?
If the good lord
hadn't been watching,
I'd have slapped him
upside the head.	|Shirley Group	|07
- who do you guys think
cheated?	|Pierce Group	|07
- flattering.
But if i'm gonna cheat,
I'm not gonna write
information from a book
Onto a piece of paper.
That's practically learning,
for god's sakes.
Whoever made that crib sheet
wasn't a real cheater.
Just...insecure and naive.	|Jeff Group	|07
- i may be naive,
but i'm not stupid.	|Annie Jeff	|07
- well, i may be stupid,
But i'm not trying
to look like i'm not.	|Troy Annie	|07
- well, i may be a genius,
but i'm not a lesbian.	|Pierce Britta	|07
Who cares who made
the crib sheet?
The only real cheater
Is the guy who's threatening
everyone with a zero.	|Britta Group	|07
- you're right!
it's so unfair.
And i can't handle
this kind of stress right now.	|Annie Group	|06
I'm already overwhelmed
by my duties
On the school song committee.	|Annie Group	|07
- are you a musician?	|Pierce Annie	|07
- eew. no.
i hired a local composer.
But he's quite a handful.	|Annie Pierce	|07
- well, i guess that's
your fault, isn't it?	|Pierce Annie	|07
- it is?	|Annie Pierce	|07
- you've got an accomplished
Pianist and songwriter
sitting 3 feet away from you.
I wrote the jingle
For hawthorne wipe's
moist towelettes.
I would have done
your song for free.
Smooth move, metamucil.	|Pierce Annie	|07
- troy could do the school song.
Troy invited rap music,
And he's related to danny glover
and president obama.	|Abed Group	|08
- abed, have you been
racist this whole time
While i'm telling
everybody at church
What a sweet little
caramel angel you are?	|Shirley Abed	|08
- hey, man, that stuff
i said this morning wasn't true.
I was just messin' with you.	|Troy Abed	|08
- you were lying?	|Abed Troy	|08
- yeah, as a joke.
You've never had anybody
mess with you before?	|Troy Abed	|08
- yes. just kidding.
no. like that?
This isn't a table.
Ha ha!
that's funny.	|Abed Troy	|08
- remember when we used to
study spanish?	|Jeff Britta	|09
- pierce!	|Annie Pierce	|10
- yo.	|Pierce Annie	|10
- i talked to the dean,
And he said you can write
greendale's school song.	|Annie Pierce	|10
- well, that's more like it.	|Pierce Annie	|10
- you know the statue
dedication is this friday.
So you have to have it done
by then.	|Annie Pierce	|10
- this friday?
this friday?	|Pierce Annie	|10
- if that's not enough time--	|Annie Pierce	|10
- no, no, no!
You really don't know much
about genius, do you?
Yes, i can do it by friday.	|Pierce Annie	|10
- great!
There's a piano
in the rehearsal space,
And i'll help you out
however i can.
You're gonna do
an awesome job!	|Annie Pierce	|10
- i know!	|Pierce Annie	|10
- so...this is the last chance
For the cheater
to be an adult
and face la musica...
Or everyone fails.	|Chang All	|11
- no!	|Annie Chang	|11
- you got ten seconds...
Starting now.	|Chang All	|11
- no!
I've never...
gotten a zero before.	|Annie All	|11
- i did it.	|Britta Chang	|11
- Britta!	|Shirley Britta	|11
- well, you really took your
sweet time with that one, baby.	|Chang Britta	|11
- how dare you terrorize a class
by threatening their grades.
It's not that easy to get human
beings to turn on each other.	|Britta Chang	|11
- turn on her!	|Chang All	|11
- ow!
real mature!	|Britta All	|11
- that's right.
we are mature!
Too mature
to sit in a class
With a cheating,
lying poop-face!	|Chang Britta	|11
Okay. time to learn
some formal greetings.	|Chang All	|11
- so...
Wow.	|Jeff Britta	|12
- yeah, i bet
you're enjoying this.	|Britta Jeff	|12
- yeah, well,
when we first met,
Like you were up here
and i was here, and now...
Oh, wait, i gave a quarter
to a dirty bum today.	|Jeff Britta	|12
- what do you think
they're gonna do to me?	|Britta Jeff	|12
- well, we're not gonna
buy you an ice cream.
Hi. dean pelton.
What an entrance
i got to make there.
You would be Britta perry.
I just spoke with senor chang,
And i'm afraid greendale
takes this kinda thing
Very seriously.	|Dean Britta	|12
much like a university would!	|Dean All	|12
Your case will be reviewed
By a disciplinary tribunal
tomorrow
In borchart hall.
You could be facing
expulsion.	|Dean Britta	|12
- isn't borchart hall
the pool?	|Jeff Dean	|12
- there is an olympic-sized
pool there, yes,	|Dean Jeff	|12
But we will be next to it,
using its $6,000 judge's table!	|Dean All	|12
- uh, is she allowed
to have counsel?
I mean, i may not be
a practicing lawyer anymore,
But relative to this place,
i'm alan dershowitz.	|Jeff Dean	|12
- oh, okay, ouch,
and yes.
If you'd like,
you may represent her.
Dean you later.	|Dean Jeff	|12
- i'm not gonna sit
while some hokey tribunal
Gets its jollies judging me.	|Britta Jeff	|13
- hey, if you show up with me,
follow my lead,
And deny everything,
you'll walk.
That's the winger guarantee.	|Jeff Britta	|13
- i get it.
You think
you're gonna save my bacon
Using your lawyer powers
And send me into fits
of grateful arousal.	|Britta Jeff	|13
- i can neither confirm
nor deny that.
See how good i am?	|Jeff Britta	|13
- hey, troy.
did you hear?
All dogs are blue now.
Every single dog
in the world is blue.
I'm just messing with you.	|Abed Troy	|14
- yeah, i know,
but let me explain to you
A few things
about how this works.
Uh, first of all,
i cannot be got,
Because i am not gullible
like you.
Secondly,
you are not good at this,
Because you are not believable
in your face, okay?
Your face? it's bad.	|Troy Abed	|14
- okay.	|Abed Troy	|14
- um, also...
You gotta ride the line
between believable and--
- what are you writing in?	|Troy Abed	|14
- it's a notepad.	|Abed Troy	|14
- yeah, but what are--
what language?	|Troy Abed	|14
- it's probably arabic.	|Abed Troy	|14
- all right, i am convening
this disciplinary tribunal
At our state-of-the-art
judge's table,
Which has
its own built-in sound system,
So take that yale.
Our judges include myself,
uh, dean craig pelton.	|Dean All	|15
- professor ian duncan.	|Duncan All	|15
- professor ben chang.	|Chang All	|15
- uh, no, you're a teacher.
you're not a professor.	|Duncan Chang	|15
- maybe because
i don't look like ron weasley.	|Chang Duncan	|15
- that's the difference.
That's the qualifying factor.
- gentlemen, point of order.	|Duncan Chang	|15
How can senor chang
be one of the judges?
He's the one
accusing my client.	|Jeff Duncan Dean Chang	|15
- yeah, well, you got
prince charles over here,
Who's your drinking buddy.	|Chang Jeff Duncan	|15
- oh, got me.	|Duncan Chang	|15
- well, it sounds
like there are two biases,
One on each side,
and i go both ways.
Oh, let's strike that.	|Dean Jeff	|15
Lashonda, can we please
strike that?	|Dean Extra	|15
I am impartial,
so it should all work out.
Okay. let's begin.	|Dean Jeff	|15
- fine. the tribunal calls
teacher chang.	|Duncan Chang	|15
- okay, just keep it up
frost/nixon.	|Chang Duncan	|15
- i was planning
on doing that.
Cleared my whole day.
Uh, mr. chang,
could you remind us
Of the events
of yesterday?	|Duncan Chang	|15
- with great pleasure.
it was a tuesday,
Uh, crack of dawn,
5:58 a.m.
I got up,
i took my morning deuce,
I made a breakfast
consisting of..	|Chang All	|15
- * green-dale *
* green-dale *
* slop *
Mm, nah.
* green *
* gree--green *
* greendale
isn't a slop pail *	|Pierce	|16
hi, almost done.	|Pierce Annie	|16
- oh, good.	|Annie Pierce	|16
- you can tell the dean
i'll have a song
That'll make the devil
poop god's pants.	|Pierce Annie	|16
- that's exciting.
Mind if i hear
what you got so far?	|Annie Pierce	|16
- well, uh, yeah, sure.
I, uh--i'll probably open
with something like this. uh...
You know, a note like that.
And end
with a note like that.
Uh, the words,
i can't tell you.
You know, the rest
is really a surprise.	|Pierce Annie	|16
- i'm just a little worried.
I keep hearing
the same two notes,
And your sheet music
Looks like
a chinese takeout menu.	|Annie Pierce	|16
- a musician sees music
in everything, annie.
I mean, it could be...
* moo shoo pork *
* squab with lettuce * *
You see?
i mean, it just comes out.
You know what? you really
shouldn't be here right now.	|Pierce Annie	|16
- what?	|Annie Pierce	|16
- you are inside
a throbbing, cosmic womb
Of creativity,
And when this baby
starts kicking,
I cannot be responsible
for your sanity.
i know it sounds funny,
But let me
play you out, okay?
Playing you out now,
this song.
You know, like on stage?
playing you out, okay?
Thanks for coming.
bye-bye.	|Pierce Annie	|16
- and then she yelled,
"screw you,"
Or, "screw education,"
or something like that,
And then she stormed
out of the room
In her high-heel boots
like it was tampon time...
If you know what i mean.	|Chang All	|17
- objection.
i don't know what he means.	|Jeff All	|17
- please don't
encourage him, winger.
Do you have
any more questions?	|Duncan Jeff	|17
- the defense calls
Britta perry.	|Jeff All	|17
- now, are those
the high-heel boots
He was talking about?	|Dean Britta	|17
- yes.	|Britta Dean	|17
- are they comfortable?	|Dean Britta	|17
- yeah.	|Britta Dean	|17
- i'm just curious.
they're cute.	|Dean Britta	|17
- thank you.	|Britta Dean	|17
- miss perry...
Did you make
that crib sheet?	|Jeff Britta	|17
- no.	|Britta Jeff	|17
- she confessed!	|Chang Jeff	|17
- she confessed to protect
her classmates,
Because you were threatening
to flunk everyone!	|Jeff Chang	|17
- you did what?	|Duncan Chang	|17
- oh, shut your pompous vortex
of overlapping fangs!	|Chang Duncan	|17
- hey, british dentistry
is not on trial.	|Duncan Chang	|17
- dean pelton,
i move this case
Be thrown out of...
The pool area!	|Jeff Dean	|17
- well, it certainly--	|Dean All	|17
Well, it certainly sounds
to me
That this young lady's
only crime
Is being a hero
and wanting to be taller.
This tribunal is adjourned.	|Dean All	|17
- wait! i cheated!	|Britta All	|17
- and we're back.	|Dean All	|17
- objection. my client
did not cheat.	|Jeff All	|17
- yes, i did.	|Britta All	|17
- yes, she did...
But why?
That's the real question,
isn't it?
The world wasn't
the only thing that changed
On september 11th.	|Jeff All	|17
- Jeff, come on.	|Britta Jeff	|17
- five-minute recess?	|Jeff All	|17
- no, no. there's nothing
In the bylaws about recesses,
all right?
The wheels of justice here
don't stop
Just because you--aah!
Time out! time out!
Save the table!
save the table!	|Dean All	|17
Beginning transmission.
The primary purpose seems
to be male bonding,
And the attitude
during conveyance
Of the random deceit is
apparently of great importance.
The humanoid is approximately
5'10" in height.	|Abed	|18
- what are you doing?	|Troy Abed	|18
- oh, hey. troy.
I didn't see you.
Um, how long
were you standing there?	|Abed Troy	|18
- you trying to mess
with me?	|Troy Abed	|18
- yes,
that's what i was doing.
You got me.
I was just messing with you,
but i guess i blew it again.	|Abed Troy	|18
- yeah.
You did.	|Troy Abed	|18
- man, don't turn your back
on me.	|Chang Duncan	|18
- it is on
like donkey kong!
Have you got
a problem with me?	|Duncan Chang	|19
- i don't like the fact
that you're walking around here
Like you're better than me
in front of my students.	|Chang Duncan	|19
- i'm sorry. do you mind if we
have this conversation
In a room with less balls?	|Duncan Chang	|19
You're very confident,
i'll say that.	|Duncan Extra	|19
- but you shouldn't be.	|Chang Extra	|19
- what are you doing
out there?	|Jeff Britta	|20
- you know i have a problem
with dishonesty.	|Britta Jeff	|20
- you're on trial
for cheating!
Fa--look, we'll be fine.
I just have to
go back out there
And make the case
that you're a good person--	|Jeff Britta	|20
- you don't know that.
You're just doing all of this
'cause you want to
sleep with me
I mean,
you said it yourself.
You don't even want to
be my friend.	|Britta Jeff	|20
- wait a minute.
Wait, is that
what you thought i meant?
Britta, look at me.
Look at me!	|Jeff Britta	|20
- i am.	|Britta Jeff	|20
- no, look how handsome
my face is.
If all i wanted was sex,
I could get it
from plenty of women
Without having to go through
all this crap.
I'm here because i like you,
And i--i'd be psyched
to be your friend.
I just didn't want to take
sex off the table
Without doing
my due diligence.	|Jeff Britta	|20
- i actually believe you.	|Britta Jeff	|20
- well, why wouldn't you?	|Jeff Britta	|20
- i don't know.
I guess...same reason
that i cheated.
I...just have more experience
being worthless.
I think i left that
crib sheet on the floor
Because i wanted
to get caught.
I'm so used to
screwing everything up
I just wanted
to get it over with.	|Britta Jeff	|20
- wait.
i think we have our defense.	|Jeff Britta	|20
Gentlemen...
My client is insane.	|Jeff All	|21
- what?	|Britta Jeff	|21
- gentlemen, i'm sure
you suspected...
That ms. perry was pretty odd
before the recess.
But if you could've heard
all the stuff
She just told me
in the shower,
You would realize
she is all the way out
Of her entire damn mind.
She doesn't want to succeed
Because she doesn't think
she can.
So she goes out of her way
to fail.
That's crazy!
But...
Do we really want
to make it a crime
To be crazy at greendale?
I mean, look at us.
I mean, you two are arguing
about status at a college
That correspondence schools
make fun of.
Dean, you want so bad
for this place to be ivy league
That you are putting us
at risk of electrocution.
Everyone on this campus
is nuts.	|Jeff All	|21
- not me!	|Leonard Jeff	|22
- oh, come on, leonard.
If you're gonna argue with me,
put on a bathing suit.	|Jeff Leonard	|22
- busted.	|Leonard Jeff	|22
- if you want to rehabilitate
your fellow inmate,
you need to sentence her
to staying here with us.
Because if crazy people
can't be at greendale,
Where are we supposed to go?	|Jeff All	|23
Wow, well, under the circumstances
I'll recommend
that the accused
Be fully exonerated.
On the condition
that she receives
Psychological counseling
on a weekly basis
From a trained
mental health professional.
Thinking maybe fridays,
nine-ish, something like that.	|Duncan All	|23
All in favor say "aye."	|Duncan Dean Chang	|23
aye.	|Dean Duncan	|23
aye.	|Chang Duncan	|23
- yes!	|Jeff	|23
- wait, what?	|Britta Duncan	|23
- that just happened.	|Duncan Britta	|23
- greetings, abed.	|AbedAlien Abed	|24
- greetings, commander.	|Abed AbedAlien	|24
- t-t-tell me
about the one they call troy.	|AbedAlien Abed	|24
- well, he is
rather arrogant
And has no mercy
for weaker beings.	|Abed AbedAlien	|24
- stop. stop doing this
right now.	|Troy Abed	|24
- whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm not an alien.	|Abed Troy	|24
- i never thought
you were.
But this is insane, okay?
Those are credible
alien hand movements.
You invented
a whole language.
I'm pretty sure
you rented a green screen.	|Troy Abed	|24
- yeah.	|Abed Troy	|24
- it would be less creepy
If you were
actually an alien.	|Troy Abed	|24
- this is what friends do.	|Abed Troy	|24
- no.
From now on, abed,
friends don't mess
with each other.
- okay?	|Troy Abed	|24
- cool.	|Abed Troy	|24
- cool?	|Troy Abed	|24
- cool. bam bam!	|Abed Troy	|24
- garrett, it's over.
he knows.	|Abed Garrett	|24
- we will stick things
in his butt.	|AbedAlien Abed	|24
- you're getting
a little sloppy.	|Troy Abed	|24
- we went over-budget.	|Abed Troy	|24
- mm.	|Troy Abed	|24
I've got it.
* greendale, greendale
little star-- *
Oh!	|Pierce	|25
I'm a fraud, annie.	|Pierce Annie	|25
I'm no more of a songwriter
than you or billy joel.
- but what about
the hawthorne wipes jingle?	|Annie Pierce	|25
- oh, yeah, yeah,
sure, the haw--
You want to hear it?
here.
* you'll be wiping off
that ketchup *
* with our wipes,
hawthorne wipes! *
* you'll be wiping off
that mustard *
* with our wipes
at the picnic! *	|Pierce Annie	|25
- that's she'll be coming
around the mountain.	|Annie Pierce	|25
- i know!
i steal everything.
You backed the wrong horse.
i got nothing.	|Pierce Annie	|25
- pierce, you're musical.
you're creative.
You can do this.
i believe in you.	|Annie Pierce	|25
- well, you shouldn't.
i quit.	|Pierce Annie	|25
- you listen up, pierce!
I'm gonna tell you
what my mother told me
When i wanted
to quit cheerleading.
You're not very pretty,
you have no boobs,
And you can't do a basket toss
to save your life,
But you made a commitment.
So pick up
your pompoms, pierce,
Stuff your bra,
and get ready for the team bus
To forget you at a taco bell,
because life is tough.
But we soldier on,
And that's
just the way it goes.
- gonna play myself out.	|Annie Pierce	|25
- the way it goes.
That's it.	|Pierce Annie	|25
One, two, luis guzman! oh!
oh, oh!
You know, greendale
may never be harvard	|Dean All	|26
- just don't talk to me
for a while.	|Britta Jeff	|277
- no problem.
just glad you're here.	|Jeff Britta	|27
- i'd like to introduce
our student, pierce hawthorne,
Who's written greendale
its own school song.	|Dean All	|28
Pierce, okay.	|Dean Pierce	|28
- thank you, dean,
thank you.	|Pierce Dean	|28
This song goes out
to annie.	|Pierce All	|28
- oh.	|Annie	|28
- for believing in me.
* standing
in the bookstore line *
* waiting for the bell
to chime *
* so you can go to class *
* dancing in your underwear *
* taking
air conditioner repair *	|Pierce All	|28
- is this bruce hornsby?	|Abed Jeff	|29
- yep.	|Jeff Abed	|29
- does he know he stole it?	|Abed Jeff	|29
- i don't think so.
let him enjoy it.	|Jeff Abed	|29
- can we get sued?	|Abed Jeff	|29
- not sure.	|Jeff Abed	|29
- * greendale's
the way it goes *	|Pierce All	|28
- yeah, they got us.	|Jeff Abed	|29
- * some things
are still the same *
* slop pails and pantyhose *
* oh, annie believes
in me *	|Pierce All	|28
- How many?	|Troy Abed	|30
- 36, you win!
- Best of three	|Abed Troy	|30
- Yeah!	|Troy Abed	|30