- Before we wrap up,
i would like to thank you guys
For filling out these
anonymous evaluation cards.
I found your feedback
To be largely constructive
and flattering,
So gracias on that.	|Chang All
- De nada.	|Abed Chang
- You don't have to sign
your name anymore.	|Chang Abed
- Got it.	|Abed Chang
- But there was
one evaluation
That was so harsh
and hurtful
And racist
That i took the time
personally
To analyze that handwriting
against past exams.
And this particular coward
Dots her is with tiny,
Itty-Bitty,
little circles.
Boop. Boop.
Tcch!
Isn't that precious
and cute?
Who's "erratic
and unstable" now,
Princess gringa?	|Chang Annie
- Nice day out today,
isn't it?	|Shirley Jeff
- Yeah. Shoot!	|Jeff Shirley
- You forget something?	|Britta Jeff
- Yeah.
I forgot to stagger the timing
of my exit with shirley's.
We both have a class
across campus, and i can't go
That kind of distance
with "ooh, that's nice."	|Jeff Britta
- That's mean.	|Britta Jeff
- No.
that's not nice.	|Jeff Britta
- I find shirley very easy
to talk to,
And besides,
aren't you supposed to have,
Like, an olympic gold medal
in jibber-Jabber?	|Britta Jeff
- Yeah,
but i'm a sprinter.
I'm at my best during
high-Speed bursts of wit.
On a shirley walk, i'd be winded
by that stoner tree.	|Jeff Britta
- Hey, britta, hi.
What's up?	|Vaughn Britta
- Hey, vaughn, how's it going?	|Britta Vaughn
- No worries.	|Vaughn Britta
- Interesting.
'Cause i might be worried
If i was playing hacky sack
a decade too late.	|Jeff Britta
- My class is that way.	|Britta Jeff
- All right, but i just
wanted to point out
That we easily walked
more than 100 yards
With no awkward pauses,
And that is the sign
of a true friend.	|Jeff Britta
- I'm really glad that you're
not hitting on me anymore.	|Britta Jeff
- There's the awkward pause.	|Jeff Britta
- Excuse me.
Oh, sorry, ladies.	|Annie Extra
Professor duncan!
Professor duncan!	|Annie Duncan
- What?	|Duncan Annie
- Excuse me. Annie edison.
I'm in your 101 lecture.	|Annie Duncan
- Hello.	|Duncan Annie
- I've heard
about your special psych lab.	|Annie Duncan
- Ah. The duncan principle.	|Duncan Annie
- Yes.
And i know it's limited
to second-Year students,
But i had
a 4.0 at riverside high,
And i'm not looking down
on this school at all,
But i'm only here because of
a brief addiction to pills
That i was told
would help me...focus,
But they actually made me lose
my scholarship and virginity.
So--	|Annie Duncan
- Right.	|Duncan Annie
- If you would let me
take your lab early,
It would be a real feather
in my transcript.	|Annie Duncan
- Okay, i've actually been
in this situation many times,
So i'm just
going to be up front.
I'm not allowed to date
students.	|Duncan Annie
- Oh!	|Annie Duncan
- Even though
you're an eight.	|Duncan Annie
- Oh!	|Annie Duncan
- Which is a british ten,
So i'm angry.	|Duncan Annie
- Oh!	|Annie Duncan
- But if, in spite of that,
you are still interested,
Then you may join the lab.
Ah! Okay. You need to bring
two human subjects.
And it would not hurt
your chances one bit
If you could
lend me a fiver.
I seem to have
left my purse in my duffle
And my duffle in the boot
of my lorry, so--	|Duncan Annie
- Oh.	|Annie Duncan
- I asked politely, and then
panda took his pants off.	|Vaughn Britta
I never even knew
that's what asexual meant.	|Britta Vaughn
- I wonder what this
express package could be?
Somebody had to get
something to me very fast.	|Pierce Group
- You brought your mail
to campus?	|Shirley Pierce
- Oh, yes.
My ear-Noculars.	|Pierce Group
- What is that? It looks like
your bluetooth thingie.	|Troy Pierce
- No, no, no, no, no.
This is my cell phone headset.
And this is ear-Noculars.
It's for spies and whatnot.
It gives you sonic hearing.	|Pierce Troy
- All hearing is sonic.	|Abed Pierce
- What's that?	|Pierce Group
- So who wants to be
in a psych experiment?	|Annie Group
- Hey, guys, guys, guys?
Annie is talking about
some kind of experiment.	|Pierce Group
- She's behind you.
Not interested.	|Jeff Pierce
- Please?
You get paid.	|Annie Group
- Do they do stuff to your butt?	|Troy Annie
- No.	|Annie Troy
- Do you get paid more if they
do stuff to your butt?	|Troy Annie
- No.	|Annie Troy
- That's fine.
I'll do it. I'm in.	|Troy Annie
- Yay!	|Annie Troy
- How about you, abed?
It's tomorrow.	|Annie Abed
- Ooh, tomorrow?
They're showing all four
indiana joneses at the vista.
I'm really looking forward
to the first three.
I bought a whip.	|Abed Annie
- This is really important
to me, abed.
Could you please go
as my friend?
My really good friend?	|Annie Abed
- Wow, i didn't realize
we were really good friends.
I figured we were more
like chandler and phoebe.
They never really
had stories together.
Sure, i'll do it,
chandler.	|Abed Annie
- Oh, thank you, abed.	|Annie Abed
- Oh!	|Shirley Abed
- I'm gonna go save britta
from that dude.	|Jeff Group
- Yeah, she looks like
she's in trouble.	|Shirley Jeff
Hope he doesn't try to
"handsome" her to death.	|Shrley Group
- And panda has no pants.	|Vaughn Britta
- Hey.	|Jeff Britta
- Hey, hi, what's up, man?
I'm vaughn.	|Vaughn Jeff
- You in line?	|Jeff Vaughn
- Oh, no, no, no.
We're just, uh,
we're just chillin'.
Hey, you're not gonna
order coffee?	|Vaughn Jeff
- Oh, no, i was just
gonna see if britta--	|Jeff Vaughn
- Hey, no judgment, bro.
I used to do coffee.
Then i made the switch
to green tea.
It's, like--It's, like,
Filled with these antioxidants
and stuff.	|Vaughn Jeff
- Hmm.	|Jeff Vaughn
- It's pretty tight.	|Vaughn Jeff
- Tight. Yes.
I've heard that
about green tea.	|Jeff Vaughn
- I like green tea.
I should make the change.	|Britta Vaughn
- Up top, sugar bear.	|Vaughn Britta
- Yeah, give me some of that.	|Jeff Vaughn
- There it is.	|Vaughn Jeff
- Small coffee, please.	|Jeff Extra
- Britta's making the change
to green tea.	|Pierce Group
- Oh, that's good.
It's good for your skin.	|Shirley Group
- Welcome,
research assistants.
If you turn your attention
to the monitor,
You will see
that our subjects
Are waiting for the experiment
to begin, but...
It's actually
happening right now.	|Duncan All
- Wow.	|All Duncan
You see, the waiting
is the experiment.
The duncan principle
is simple.
Namely, that the more control
lost by the--
Yeah, i'm gonna
write this down too, actually.
That's a good point.
The more control
lost by the ego,
The more gained by the id,
Resulting
in a surprisingly predictable
Emotional eruption
or breaking point,
Known to ma and pa as
a good old-Fashioned tantrum.
Oh.	|Duncan All
Annie, why don't you, uh,
go and tell our subjects
That we're going to be
starting the experiment
In five minutes, okay?
And annie...
It's never actually
going to start.	|Duncan Annie
Ho ho.	|Garrett All
Let's do this.	|Duncan All
- Hi, everyone.	|Annie All
Hi, troy.	|Annie Troy
Hi, abed.
- Hi.	|Troy Annie
Hi, senor chang.	|Annie Chang
- What, a community college
spanish teacher
Can't use 80 bucks?	|Chang Annie
- Well, we're just running
a little bit behind,
So we'll probably start
in about five minutes.	|Annie Chang
- No, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
It's unacceptable,
all right?
You lied to me!
When you say something
starts at 9:00,
It starts at nueve!	|Chang Annie
No!
No!	|Chang All
- Houston, we have an idiot.	|Duncan All
- Did you know we walk
the same way after class?
I'm sure you didn't or else we
would've been walking together,
Unless you're a jerk.
Just kidding.	|Shirley Jeff
- Let's do it.	|Jeff Shirley
- Mm-Hmm.
Don't go too fast for
these dogs. Short legs.
So how do you like--	|Shirley Jeff
- So you've got a kid, right?	|Jeff Shirley
- What's that?	|Shirley Jeff
- Nothing.	|Jeff Shirley
- So pierce isn't exactly
right in the head, is he?	|Shirley Jeff
- I know a lot
of grown men
With radar dishes
coming out of their ear.	|Jeff Shirley
- he's like inspector gadget.	|Shirley Jeff
- Yeah, go, go,
gadget incontinence.	|Jeff Shrley
- And how about that guy
that's always around,
flirting with britta?	|Shirley Jeff
- I know!
He's the worst! Vaughn?	|Jeff Shirley
- I know, and what is it
with his hair?	|Shirley Jeff
- It's perpetually moist.	|Jeff Shrley
- Okay, we're three hours in,
so let's review what we've seen.
And pay close attention to
every subject's breaking point.
We've got a shouter.
- That one's a stomper.
Bye, hippie.
There's a generic whack job,
bouncing up and down
Like a six-Foot child.
Shaking.
Write that down.
Visible shakes.
Look at the little one
chase the big one.
Look at him go. I'm gonna
make him go quicker.
It's like benny hill looks.
Whoo, ooh, ooh, get him.
Come back again. Whoo,
ooh, ooh, get him.
All right?
There's a bit of fun.
It lightens the mood.
And back to the present.
And then there were two.
Break.	|Duncan All
No, no, no! Annie!
What is going on
in there?
Why--?
What is taking so long?
I've wasted all day
here for you.
The soul train awards
were tonight.
You promised butt stuff!	|Troy Annie
- And he's out.
We got him.
strike three.
You're gone.	|Duncan All
- There's so much dust
in here.	|Troy
- Do you know what?
The longer they wait,
the harder they break.
Buckle up, students.	|Duncan All
- Do you see how often
hacky sack takes his shirt off?
He'd play shirts and skins
in a game of checkers.	|Shirley Jeff
- I'm so glad to be able
to talk to someone about this.
I wanted to say
something to britta about it,
But we're supposed to be
friends now,
And she'd think
i was jealous.	|Jeff Shirley
- I don't see why you
and britta aren't together.
Two cute white people,
going to school together,
Just seems right.	|Shirley Jeff
- Shirley,
we're not pandas in a zoo.	|Jeff Shirley
Oh. Oh, dear.	|Shirley Jeff
- That is not
what i want to see.	|Jeff Shirley
- There goes the shirt.	|Shirley Jeff
- Hey.	|Britta Jeff
- Hey, i'm fine.
How are--
Want me to, uh,
Want me to check you
for grass stains?	|Jeff Britta
- I wasn't sure how or when
to bring up
That i was hanging out
with vaughn.
I figured that you'd
make fun of him...and me.	|Britta Jeff
- Uh, first of all,
Friends do not make
fun of each other,
Even if they're being tackled
in the quad by a hippie,
And secondly,
vaughn seems cool.	|Jeff Britta
- Well, you guys should
hang out sometime.
I gotta go.
I--Uh, that was tacky
out there.
You won't ever
see that again.	|Britta Jeff
- Oh, no worries, brah.	|Jeff Britta
- Shirley, did you see
senor chang's socks today?
Tiny bullfighters.	|Jeff Shirley
- I can top that.
Did you see that
hacky sack wears an anklet?
Since when won't you
talk about vaughn?	|Shirley Jeff
- Look, i'm trying to be
a good friend to britta.
She thought i was gonna
make fun of him,
But i want to be
unpredictable.
I'm gonna show her that i am not
the jerk she thinks i am
And friend the hell out of
That green-Tea-Drinking
drum circler.	|Jeff Shirley
- Okay,
but tell me you've noticed
How small his nipples are.	|Shirley Jeff
- Not engaging.	|Jeff Shirley
- What?
It's not gossip
when it's fact.
My kids have got hamsters
with bigger nips.	|Shirley Jeff
- No!	|Jeff Shirley
- Oh, well.	|Shirley Jeff
- Jeff!	|Shirley Jeff
- Is it on pause?	|Duncan Annie
- No, that's just him.	|Annie Duncan
Sorry you've been waiting
26 hours.
It's just gonna be
another five minutes.	|Annie Abed
- Okey-Dokey.	|Abed Annie
- Oh, my...
Why won't he leave?	|Duncan
- Professor.	|Garrett Duncan
- What?	|Duncan Garrett
- I'm sorry,
but this guy's not moving.
I have classes
to go to.	|Garrett Duncan
- Go! Fine!
Go kill john lennon again,
you loser.	|Duncan Garrett
He's ruined my study!
He has--He has warped
the duncan principle.
Damn you,
you outlying piece of datum!
ow! Aah!	|Duncan
It's you!
It's your fault!	|Duncan Annie
- But you told me
to bring subjects.	|Annie Duncan
- Yeah, subjects!
Not rain man!
I should never
have let you into this lab,
Miss annie fanny
panties in a bunch!	|Duncan Annie
- Oh! Oh,
that's so hilarious!
Did you think of that
The last time you
skipped a trip to the dentist?	|Annie Duncan
- Oh, let me answer that
question with another question.	|Duncan Annie
It's not--It's not fair!
It's not fair!
Why, why, why?
What are you doing?
Put your--
Stop writing!
Put your pen--
Give me that!
Get out!
Get out, you dorks!
Get out!	|Duncan All
You have destroyed
the duncan principle!	|Duncan Annie
- Go home!	|Annie Troy
- Cool.
See ya.	|Troy Annie
- So britta said that you did
a lot of community service.	|Jeff Vaughn
- Ultimate frisbee
at the senior's center.
It is amazing.	|Vaughn Jeff
- And what makes frisbee
ultimate?	|Jeff Vaughn
- Aw, man,
if i had a nickel
For every time i wished
somebody asked me that.	|Vaughn Jeff
- I'm gonna get dessert.
Want anything?	|Britta Vaughn Jeff
- Carrots.	|Vaughn Britta
- Oh, i'm good.	|Jeff Britta
- Hey, you two.	|Shirley Jeff Vaughn
- Hey.	|Vaughn Shirley
- Well,
that's a cool shirt.	|Shirley Vaughn
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.	|Vaughn Shirley
- Where's it from?	|Shirley Vaughn
- Oh, uh,
i don't even know.
I guess it's--
Well, uh--
Hey, look at that.
"Hanes classic."	|Vaughn Shirley
- Oh, that's nice.	|Shirley Vaughn
- You know, people
underestimate the elderly,
You know, but you
see these guys out there
And they're
throwing the bee
And they're just loving life.
It's just inspiring.	|Vaughn Jeff Shirley
- You know, i'm gonna really--
I'm gonna think about it.	|Jeff Vaughn
- All right. I'm gonna go
check on britts.
See ya.	|Vaughn Jeff Shirley
- See ya.	|Shirley Vaughn
- You are the devil.	|Jeff Shirley
- I know.	|Shirley Jeff
- Donde vaughn ustedes
los sabados?	|Jeff Shirley
- Domingo, pl--
Oh, okay, I--	|Britta Jeff
- Where do we go
on saturdays?
You said sunday.	|Jeff Britta
- I have a question for you.
You like vaughn, right?	|Britta Jeff
- Oh, he--He's very cute.	|Jeff Britta
- I'm just worried
That he's thinking
a little bit more intensely
About this thing
than i am.
He says stuff,
you know, after...	|Britta Jeff
- School?	|Jeff Britta
- After...	|Britta Jeff
- Dinner mints?	|Jeff Britta
- Not having sex?	|Jeff Britta
- Ahh...	|Britta Jeff
- How was that?	|Jeff Britta
- What? Forget that.
The problem right now
is that he's calling me "babe."
He's trying to hold my hand.
It's getting a little
relationship-Y.
And he gave me something.	|Britta Jeff
- Herpes?	|Jeff Britta
- No. This.	|Britta Jeff
- A poem?	|Jeff Britta
- How do i respond
to something like that?
"Thank you"?	|Britta Jeff
- Well,
it's a very good question.
And it's one
i will answer. Uh--
Ooh, i'm getting a text.
I'm just gonna read it,
if you don't mind.
I am reading it,
and it is read.	|Jeff Britta
"Did you ever notice where
the ocean meets the sky, did ya?
It's the same wizard blue that
i see in your eye, brit-Ta."	|Jeff Shirley
- Oh, no, no.
"Wizard blue"?	|Shirley Jeff
- Yeah.	|Jeff Shirley
- Thank you so much.
You just brightened my day.
I'm so glad we can rip on
that dude again.	|Shirley Jeff
- Look at this, look at this.
That is the stain of a teardrop
over the word "rad."	|Jeff Shirley
- Oh, he said "rad"?
I thought he said "bad."
Oh, that makes it worse.	|Shirley Jeff
- I'm surprised he can read.	|Jeff Shirley
- Oh!	|Shirley Jeff
- You know?	|Jeff Shirley
- I know.	|Shirley Jeff
- Hey, sorry about bailing
on the psych experiment.	|Troy Annie
- That was
the experiment, troy.
We were testing to see how long
people would wait in the room.	|Annie Troy
- Whoa.	|Troy
- Oh, gotcha.	|Abed Annie
- "Gotcha"?
That's all you have to say?	|Annie Abed
- Yeah.	|Abed Annie
- You sat in a room
for 26 straight hours.
Didn't that bother you?	|Annie Abed
- Yeah, i was livid.	|Abed Annie
- Then why didn't you leave?	|Annie Abed
- Because you asked me to stay
and you said we were friends.	|Abed Annie
- Wait. Is this still
part of the experiment?	|Troy Annie
- He's more like a puppy
with a fish mouth.	|Jeff Shirley
- Right, right.
It's more like this.	|Shirley Jeff
- That's right.
Laugh it up.
You guys want to know
what they're doing?	|Pierce Group
- Yeah.	|Abed Pierce
- Sure.	|Troy Pierce
- Making fun of all of us.	|Pierce Group
I heard you with my own
ear...noculars.	|Pierce Jeff
- Pierce, we are not
making fun of you.	|Jeff Pierce
- Uh-Huh.
Calling me "hacky sack"
And ripping my--My six pack abs
and my moist hair.	|Pierce Annie
And that face you made?
Well, i think
it's pretty obviously annie.	|Pierce Shirley
- Okay, this is definitely still
part of the experiment.	|Troy
- Pierce, we were not
making fun of you.	|Jeff Pierce
- Yeah.	|Shirley Pierce
- We're making fun britta's
boyfriend, vaughn.	|Jeff Pierce
- Oh, good.
Well, in that case.
But if we're gonna do something,
let's do it as a team.
I'll get the ball rolling.
Maybe he has a tiny penis.	|Pierce Jeff Shirley
- Who is this guy?	|Troy Group
- You all have got
to see him.
Everything's all,
"no worries, no worries."
And he always says hello
three times in a row.
Hello, good evening,
how are you?
And--Here, look!
He wrote a poem!	|Shrley Group
- Oh!
- Can i read it?
- We shouldn't show that.
- Oh, no, it's fine.
- So i'll be done in,
like, an hour.
- Yeah. No worries.
- He just said it!
- Guys,
you've met vaughn, right?
- Hey. What's up? Hi.
[Laughter]
This troop's got a case
of the giggles, huh?
Is that--?
Did you give them
my poem?
- No.
- Okay, well,
Why is the dinosaur rocking
a picture of my poem?
- Here, read it.
- Oh, you guys are--
Right?
You guys are laughing at me,
aren't you?
- Yeah.
- No.
- That's uh, wow.
This is the least tight thing
that's ever happened to me.
- I can't believe you.
- Honestly, jeff,
how dare you?
- He's crying.
Now he's barking.
- Jeff, wait!
I'm sorry i sold you out.
- Britta is never
gonna forgive me.
I can't believe
i showed you that poem.
Oh, my god, my life
is degrassi high.
- Oh, jeff.
I have a gossip problem.
I stir the pot, jeff.
I'm a pot stirrer.
This isn't even the only study
group i've had this year.
You see
those ladies over there?
I used to be in their group
till they kicked me out.
They call me "tattle-Ina."
It's a bumblebee nickname.
It's--It's cute,
but it stings.
- Hey, look at the size
of that woman's earrings.
It's like little dogs
should be jumping through them.
- Mmmmmmm!
- [Laughs]
- This is never going to work.
- Look at them.
- This has to end.
Mm-Mm, mm-Mm.
- Shirley, don't do this.
Look, we can still hang out.
It's just, you know,
we won't bag on people.
- Come on, jeff.
What are we gonna talk about?
My kids?
Your--Your doctor career?
- I was a lawyer.
- See? I'm already bored.
- [Sighs]
Well, we'll always have
"tiny nipples."
- [Laughs]
they were tiny.
Okay.
Jeff, wait. Wait.
I know i shouldn't do this,
But one last
little piece of gossip.
Britta told me she had
a sex dream about you.
You still have a chance.
[Squeals]
mm-Hmm. Mm-Mm.
- Details.
- Mmmmmm! Mm-Mmm.
- Details!
- Mm-Mmm!
- Abed, here.
I wanted to say sorry
for yelling at you.
- Indiana jones.
Cool.
- I just got the first three
because...
Together:
the fourth one blows.
- We're cool.
- I do not
want to talk to you.
- No, i know,
and i'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm really, really sorry,
And i will go talk to vaughn
if you want me to.
With me.
- Oh.
Oh.
- You broke my trust.
You suck.
- I know, and i'm sorry,
But i was
in a tough position.
I couldn't handle
just being one of the girls.
- What do you want to be?
- Is there a spot on
the friendship spectrum
Between total stranger
And having to hear
about the guys you date?
And ideally,
just a notch underneath
Driving you to the airport
and painting your kitchen?
- How about the friend level
Where you sometimes
have to cat-Sit?
- Done.
And if i'm occasionally naked
in your dreams,
I won't complain.
- Shirley.
- I know.
She's got a problem.
She stirs the pot.
She's a pot stirrer.
- Sorry, dudes.
- No worries, man.
- Yeah, some worries, man.
Some worries.
- * now there was a time *
- Whoa.
* when you loved me so *
* i couldn't run *
- Shirley would have said
something funny about that guy.
* *
- [Laughs]
and so i told him...
Oh, hey--Hey, jeff.
- Shh shh shh shh.
- Oh, no.
Pierce! Pierce,
give me your ear-Thing.
- Got rid of it.
You see, jeff,
there are certain things
Man was not meant
to hear.
We were designed,
by whatever entity you choose,
To hear
what's in this range,
And really,
this range alone.
Because you know who's
talking to us in this range?
The people we love.
- * how you like me now? *
* how you like me now?... *
- He must have heard us
call him inspector gadget.
[Imitates a stoner]
- Oh, i think it's time
For burning man.
[Dorky voice]
- Ew, i'm saddam hussein. Ew.
[Imitates a stoner]
- Nice to meet you, dude.
[Imitates woman]
- Ooh, wow. I love reading and
being a desperate housewife.
[With jamaican accent]
- Hey, man, coming through.
I love
de desperate housewives.
[Snotty guy voice]
- I'm dr. Doogie seacrest.
I think i'm better than
everyone else because i'm 40.
- I'm not 40.
I can hear you through
the window, morons.
- Just pretend
like you're asleep.