So I booked a sketch artist,
an improve troupe,
and there'll be a laser
projecting a burning pelvis
onto the ceiling.	|Annie Dean
A laser!
Well, this isn't gonna be your mother's
sexually transmitted disease
awareness fair.
You've been quite
the little helper, Annie.	|Dean Annie
Oh, STD fair, guys.
Catch knowledge.	|Annie Troy Abed
You think you're better than me?	|Troy Abed
No.	|Abed Troy
You stick to quotin' movie lines.
I'll stick to sports.	|Troy Abed
I'm trying to reduce
my pop-cultural referencing.	|Abed Troy
Well, you're not moving into sports.
You and I are playing
real basketball, right now.	|Troy Abed
Sounds fun.	|Abed Troy
No, it doesn't! And it won't be.	|Troy Abed
- Catch knowledge.	|Annie Jeff Britta
- Sorry, not interested...	|Jeff Annie
in ignoring your very important cause.
Hi, I'm Jeff Winger.	|Jeff Secretary
Oh, Sabrina is my new secretary.	|Dean Jeff
"Secretary" is a little
degrading to women.	|Secretary Dean
I help the dean do officey things.	|Secretary Jeff
Oh, gender saved.	|Britta Secretary
My casual friend and I are gonna have
a non-romantic breakfast
if you'd like to join us.	|Jeff Secretary
The cafeteria's closed
while we set up for the fair.
Fortune cookie?	|Annie Jeff
Isn't it great?
Greendale is the latest
campus to catch a case
of public health fever!	|Dean Jeff Britta
You know the toilets
in the women's bathrooms
don't have seats, right?	|Britta Dean
Because they keep getting stolen.	|Dean Britta
Sabrina, take a note.
I want hidden cameras in every stall.	|Dean Secretary
Problem solved.	|Britta Annie Jeff
- "You will get aids."	|Jeff
- Flip it over.	|Annie Jeff
"Unless you go to the STD fair."	|Jeff
I wrote that.	|Annie Jeff
Congratu... horrible!	|Jeff Annie
See you later.	|Annie Jeff
Jeff... you and I are friends, right?	|Pierce Jeff
Okay.	|Jeff Pierce
You may have noticed a
recent change in my demeanor.	|Pierce Jeff
I haven't.	|Jeff Pierce
Well, I have a new girlfriend.
And she is super smart,
if you know what I mean.	|Pierce Jeff
Unfortunately, I always
know what you mean.	|Jeff Pierce
Can't wait for you to meet her.
You know, when you catch a big fish,
you want to stuff her
and put her on the mantle.
How 'bout tonight?	|Pierce Jeff
I doubt it.	|Jeff Pierce
Troy and I played basketball.
It was fun.	|Abed Jeff Pierce
Don't gloat.
It's impossible to guard you.
Your eyes are too gentle and mysterious.	|Troy Abed
Hey, guys, Jeff and I are
double-dating tonight
with my new girlfriend.	|Pierce Group
Ooh...	|Shirley Pierce
You got that from "I doubt it"?	|Jeff Pierce
Pierce has got a girlfriend!	|Shirley Pierce
That's great. What does she do?	|Britta Pierce
- She's an escort.	|	Pierce Group
- Oh...	|Shirley Pierce
Some mysteries solve
themselves, don't they?	|Jeff Group
No, no, no, that's just her profession.
She doesn't escort me. No, no.
I met her in my marketing class.
And I'm taking Doreen
to Annie's mixer tonight.	|Pierce Group
You mean the STD fair.
Catch knowledge.	|Pierce
Taking a call girl to an STD fair.
There's a joke here.	|Troy
So, Jeff, dust off that black book
and rustle up a honey, huh?	|Pierce Jeff
Is there a pill that makes
the word "no" clearer?	|Jeff Pierce
Well, I guess it is pretty short notice.
Probably couldn't get a date anyway.	|Pierce Jeff
- Oooohh...	|Group
- I'm sure you're right.	|Jeff Pierce
Oooohh...	|Group
Maybe it has something to do with crabs.
They're like a food,
but they're also a disease.	|Troy
You know, I wonder, Jeffrey,
for all your feather flashing,
when was the last time
you actually scored?	|Pierce Jff
Well, I don't know the
precise date, Pierce,
because I'm not you,
so there's no receipt.	|Jeff Pierce
Ooohh...	|Jeff Group
Meh...	|Group Jeff
Oh, come on.	|Jeff Group
Jeff, you shouldn't take
potshots at some poor woman
just because you can't get a date.	|Shirley Jeff
I can get dates anytime I want.	|Jeff Shirley
What is this, some kind of joke?	|Jeff Group
No. This is.
"Don't eat the crab dip."
Yay-yay!	|Troy Group
Ah... You hear that, Annie?
That's the sound of STDs screaming,
"No! Stop being so aware of us!"
Aah!
And it's all thanks to you.	|Dean Annie
I was voted most likely to
succeed at my rehab clinic.	|Annie Dean
Well, in recognition
of all your hard work,
I have decided that you should conduct
the condom demonstration.
You're gonna be center
stage showing everyone
how to put a condom on a, well,
what my dad called a Jimmy Carter.	|Dean Annie
Um, I don't know if I'm
the right person for that.	|Annie Dean
Don't worry, not a real one.
No, it's an anatomically
correct model, you know.
But trust me, eyes closed,
you can't tell the difference.
Okay.	|Dean Annie
Hey, it's Jeff Winger.
Well, I wanted to see what
you were doing tonight.
What do you mean, do I know your name?
What kind of a question is that?
Of course I know.
Well, if I answer now,
you'll never learn a
valuable lesson about trust,
Jennifer.	|Jeff Extra
Crap! Ahh...	|Jeff
Pierce really got to you, huh?	|Britta Jeff
It has been a dry spell.
But that's only because it's
been a while since I've tried.
So I'm trying.	|Jeff Britta
Yeah, I can see that.
This is a lot of outgoing calls.
"Car wash redhead. Tube top,
REM Concert."
"Juror number six."
That sounds aboveboard.
At least you have "mommy" in here.
It's not my mom.	|Jeff Britta
Dude, not cool.	|Britta Jeff
You saying "dude" is not cool.
What are you doing?	|Jeff Britta
Heh!
"Hot blonde, Spanish class"?	|Britta Jeff
You're welcome.	|Jeff Britta
This is the phone book
of a man in his 20s.
The women literally have no identities.
It's pretty shallow.	|Britta Jeff
You're right.
I can't believe I haven't
seen it before now.	|Jeff Britta
Whatever.
I'm gonna go study with Shirley.	|Britta Jeff
Well, I'll be here...
Rethinking my way of life.	|Jeff Britta
Mm.	|Britta Jeff
Call mommy.	|Jeff Britta
Guys... I have a problem.
The dean wants me to demonstrate
the proper use of a
condom at the stupid fair
by putting one on a
mannequin's stupid...
Thingamabob.
It's a big honor...
But I'm gonna screw it up.	|Annie Britta Shirley
Well, it's easy enough to practice.	|Shirley Annie
Britta, do you have a banana?	|Shirley Britta
This is an anatomically
correct model I'll be handling.
Real... whatchamacallits...
are nothing like bananas!
Are they?	|Annie Britta Shirley
Have you never seen one?	|Britta Annie
- Shh!	|Annie Britta
- Annie...
being a virgin in this day and age
is something to be proud of.
You're like a unicorn.	|Shirley Annie
I am not a unicorn.
I had relations with my
high school boyfriend.
We did it to Madonna's erotica
on the floor of his walk-in closet.
But he wouldn't let me look at it.
And he cried after. And during.
He's gay now.	|Annie Shirley Britta
I think he was gay then.	|Britta Annie
So you, uh, you never seen
one when you were growing up?
Like, you know, on the
Internet, in a picture,
or Harvey Keitel's?	|Shirley Annie
I've caught glimpses,
but I've never got a
real good look at one.
What I need to do is
practice on the actual model,
but the dean has it
locked in his office.	|Annie Shirley Britta
Okay, that's easy enough.
We'll go to him
and we'll ask him...	|Britta Annie
No! This is really embarrassing.
I don't want anyone to know.
I just want to figure out how to do it
and get it over with.
The dean is counting on me,
and I want him to know that
I'm someone he can trust.
We have to break into his office.	|Annie Britta Shirley
I actually have no problem with that.	|Shirley Britta Annie
I think I could do that. Mm-hmm.	|Britta Annie
- Oh, hello, Jeffrey.	|Pierce Jeff
- Hi, Pierce.	|Jeff Pierce
I was just going into the fair
to wait for my smokin'-hot date.	|Pierce Jeff
- That's nice.	|Jeff Pierce
- How 'bout you?
Were you ever able to, you know,
come up with a, you know, date?	|Pierce Jeff
No, no. Because I didn't try.
Because taking a date to
an STD fair would be lame.	 |Jeff Pierce
Don't worry about it, kid.
What you're going
through is a dry spell.
From my experience,
they don't last any more
than 12, 13 years.	|Pierce Jeff
Excuse me.	|Pierce Jeff
Step right up.
Get a prize, not an STD.
Oh, no, syphilis.
Please, please, no, syphilis.
Ow, it burns!
Oh, that's gonna hurt.	|Dean Extra
Gross. Dean, your assistant.
Is she single?
What are her likes and dislikes?	|Jeff Dean
Uh, yes on single.
She likes hip-hop and horses.
Dislikes beards and... yeah,
I was done talking.	|Dean Jeff
Is it me, or are horses the
most beautiful creatures?
They're so majestic.	|Jeff Secretary
Totally.	|Secretary Jeff
I mean, just this morning
when I was shaving
and listening to the new Jay-Z,
I was thinking about
how I want to squeeze in
a quick gallop this weekend.	|Jeff Secretary
Do you own a horse?	|Secretary Jeff
Can you ever really own a horse?	|Jeff Secretary
Pierce.	|Jeff Pierce
Yeah.	|Pierce Jeff
This is Sabrina.
About 30 seconds after you walked away,
I asked her to be my date for the fair,
and she said yes.	|Jeff Pierce
Oh, you must have a great personality.	|Pierce Jeff
Thank you.	|Secretary Pierce
Congratulations, Jeff.
You proved me wrong.
You got a girl.	|Pierce Jeff
Yeah, I did.	|Jeff Pierce
Oh, this is Doreen.
Ready for our double date?	|Pierce Jeff
Yes, I am. Wait, how'd you do that?	|Jeff Pierce
Is this the best safe sex fair or what?
Check out these condoms.
All along the side it says "Greendale"!
Exclamation point, my idea.	|Dean Chang
Wow, me in a dune buggy.
With syphilis.
This is going on the fridge.	|Jeff Pierce
Hey, look how gorgeous
Doreen is tonight.
Hey, can we...
Let's lay out our plans for the evening.
You wing man me, I wing man you.
Maybe we split up for a little hoo-ha.
And then meet in the morning
for eggs and... details.	|Pierce Jeff
That sounds like the worst
combination plate ever.	|Jeff Pierce
Ugh! I can't believe you beat me again!	|Troy Abed
- You want my stuffed animal?	|Abed Troy
- Aah!
We're arm wrestling. Ugh!	|Troy Abed
Oh, like Stallone in over the top.
But I'm not sure of all the rules.
Don't I need a semi truck
and a ten-year-old son?	|Abed Troy
The rules are you suck! Let's go!	|Troy Abed
Uh, I want to wait for
a more inspiring song.
This score isn't right.
There we go.	|Abed Troy
Aah!
You broke my hand, you bastard.	|Troy Abed
I can't do anything with this.	|Britta Shirley
Hmm, let me see that.
Ooh, I can see through the door.
Oh, yeah. Thar she blows.	|Shirley Britta Annie
Ooh, I wanna see! I wanna see!	|Britta Shirley
- Okay, go, go, go.	|Shirley Britta
- Shh.	|Annie Britta
Oh!	|Britta
I'm the one that needs to see.	|Annie Britta Shirley
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.	|Britta Annie
It's okay.	|Shirley Annie
Oh, boy.
Oh, I had it wroooong!
Is that considered large?	|Annie Britta Shirley
- Yes.	|Britta Annie
- No.	|Shirley Annie
What in the reverse
porky's is going on here?	|Security Annie Britta Shirley
You know, Doreen speaks six languages.
You should hear her
order wine in French.	|Pierce Jeff
Hey, honey, say caber-net
sauv-a-gong-da-nun.	|Pierce Doreen
Pierce, you're embarrassing me.	|Doreen Pierce
Do you know a lot about wine?	|Jeff Doreen
Well, I did have a client
who owned a vineyard in Napa.
He was into S&M and Merlot,
so we called it S&M&M.	|Doreen Jeff
Honey, you're boring
the crap out of Jeff.	|Pierce Doreen
Be right back.
I have to make tinkles.	|Secretary Jeff
Well, then, I'm gonna go
get us another round.	|Pierce Jeff Doreen
You know, you are not what I expected.
You're smart, you're classy.
You're not wearing go-go boots.	|Jeff Doreen
They're in the shop.
You know, despite
what most people think,
I actually spend most
of my time talking.
As men get older,
they want to spend their time
with someone they can have
a real conversation with.	|Doreen Jeff
That is going to suck.	|Jeff Doreen
"Going to", Jeff?
Look, Sabrina's cute,
but she thinks that Monty Python
is the evil snake
from Harry Potter.	|Doreen Jeff
Trust me, I know girls
I can converse with
who are way more annoying.
I will take "tinkles" over
"we need to talk" every time.	|Jeff Doreen
Hey, babe.
Ready to show me that Lexus?	|Secretary Jeff
I thought you'd never ask.	|Jeff Secretary
Doreen... it was very nice to meet you.	|Jeff Doreen
You can do better.	|Doreen Jeff
Here. Rrrrr...
Oh, they already left?
What a couple of nincompoops!
Uh, before I buy dinner,
I have to ask...
is there any lovemaking on the table?	|Pierce Doreen
We're through, Pierce.
I'm gonna go to the bar,
and you can join me if you'd like.
And we can still have a lovely evening.
But it will cost you 200 bucks.	|Doreen Pierce
That is a pretty big discount.	|Pierce Extra
I had no idea alcohol
would make people horny.
Makes me sleepy. I don't...	|Dean
- Dean.	|Security Dean
- Yeah.	|Dean Security
We have a 597 currently
going on in your office.	|Security Dean
A 597?
There's a dog-fighting
ring in my office?	|Dean Security
Okay, I'm just gonna turn him around,
and we're gonna cover him up.
Okay, ladies, I am shocked
at the reverse porky's
that has happened here tonight.	|Dean Annie Britta Shirley
I don't see what the big deal is.
Annie just needed to look
at the model of the pe...	|Britta Dean
Oh, okay, the "p" word
has entered into play.
That's exactly why I wanted Gail,
our school counselor, here,
and Monique, who's keeping record,
to ensure we discuss
these sensitive topics
in a legally appropriate manner.	|Dean All
I think everyone should say penis
so we can take away the
negative power of the word.
Yeah? So, everybody...	|Gail All
Penis.	|All
She didn't say it.	|Security All
Now, why did you break
in to see the penis?	|Dean Britta Shirley Annie
Wow, I really do feel
more comfortable saying that now, Gail.	|Dean Gail
I just want to focus on the girl
who won't say penis.	|Gail All
This is a judgment-free zone,
so express yourself.	|Gail Annie
You know what?
I don't want to express myself.
I don't want to sit in
a room full of people
and say the "p" word.
I like being repressed.
I am totally comfortable
being uncomfortable
with my sexuality.
And maybe, just maybe,
if everyone were a
little bit more like me,
we wouldn't have to have an STD fair.	|Annie All
- You go, girl!	|Britta Annie
- That's my pumpkin!	|Shirley Annie
By the way, now that
I've gotten a good look at one,
I don't see what all the fuss was about.
A giant thumb in a turtleneck.
Whoop-dee-do!	|Annie All
You have a really awesome body.
You probably hear that all the time.	|Secretary Jeff
Not as much as I should.	|Jeff Secretary
Oh... professor...	|Secretary Jeff
What?
I'm not a professor.	|Jeff Secretary
But you're at Greendale...
And you're old.	|Secretary Jeff
I'm a student.	|Jeff Secretary
Yikers.	|Secretary Jeff
Yeah, it's pretty much
Yikers for me too.	|Jeff Secretary
Well, I guess I can make
an exception... professor.	|Secretary Jeff
Mmm...
You know, uh...	|Jeff Secretary
- Huh?	|Secretary Jeff
- I can't do this.	|Jeff Secretary
What?
But this is your car.	|Secretary Jeff
- Keep it.	|Jeff Secretary
- But...	|Secretary Jeff
Yeah! Yes!
Yes!
How you like those apples?	|Troy Abed
I don't like those apples.
I'm so upset.
It was just a fluke
I won those other games.	|Abed Troy
Troy!	|Troy
Wow, this may be the only STD fair
to actually spread STDs.	|Chang Dean
Shut up, Ben!	|Dean Chang
Condom water balloon fight!
What the hell?
Dude, these are leaking.	|Extra All
Oh, my God.
That's why you don't
print things on condoms.
Everyone's getting preggers,
and it's all your fault.
Oh, God, I love it.	|Chang Dean
Oh, man!	|Dean
Troy! Troy, all the condoms are faulty.
As the best athlete on campus,
I need you to run to my office
and make an announcement
before everyone leaves.	|Dean Troy
Dean, I am not the
best athlete on campus.
Abed is.	|Troy Dean
I know you let me win the race.	|Troy Abed
But you didn't say anything.	|Abed Troy
That's because...
I wanted it to be true.	|Troy Abed
You're a really good friend.	|Abed Troy
No, Abed...
You are.	|Troy Abed
For the love of God, run!	|Dean Abed
Okay.	|Abed Troy Dean
Go, Abed, go, before
people sex one another!	|Troy Abed
There he is.
Back already. Detail time?	|Pierce Jeff
I stopped.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I mean, she's hot.
I think this place is
sapping my life force.	|Jeff Pierce
Oh, it's not Greendale, Jeff, it's you.
You're becoming more mature.
I mean, a man reaches
a point in his life
where he stops looking for a place
to hang his underwear
and starts looking for
a place to hang his hat.	|Pierce Jeff
Oh, I'm sorry, I was waiting for that
to become inappropriate or racist.
What happened to Doreen?	|Jeff Pierce
Oh, uh, she said if
I wanted to continue the night
I'd have to pay.	|Pierce Jeff
Oh, man, that... that is rough.	|Jeff Pierce
Oh, no, it was a wake-up call.
Doreen's a very special lady.
I did not treat her right.
I have stuff to work on, you know?	|Pierce Jeff
You'll get there.	|Jeff Pierce
We're both gonna get there.
Here's to being better men.	|Pierce Jeff
Cheers.	|Jeff Pierce
So could I borrow 200 bucks?	|Pierce Jeff
Tell Doreen I say hi.	|Jeff Pierce
You know, for 220 I can get the...	|Pierce Jeff
I'll give you 250 if you
don't finish telling me.	|Jeff Pierce
Ooh, I can get it twice.
Ah, college. Best years of our lives.	|Pierce Jeff
Attention, Greendale students.
Don't use the condoms!
If you're going to have sex tonight,
don't use condoms.	|Abed All
The characteristic of an acid to donate or accept a proton cannot be quantified for individual species, comparing two donor acceptor systems, the proton transposition H8 plus H20...	|Abed Troy
Abed?	|Troy Abed
Yeah Troy?	|Abed Troy
Can you give me a glass of water?	|Troy Abed
Sure.	|Abed Troy