Happy last day before
winter break, Greendale!
Time to visit our loved ones.
Some of you will travel
as far as three Miles!
Don't forget to visit our
winter wonderland in the quad,
where we're giving away catalogues
of next semester's classes.
Whoa, what's that sound?
Is that the tippy-tapping
of secular boots on the roof?
Oh, well, it must be yet another sign
that it tis the season,
because rumor has it that
non-denominational Mr. Winter
is on his way to the student lounge!
Unh!
I'm so sick of the Dean jamming his PC
down my throat.
Pierce, I'd like to commend you
for letting that one go.
"PC-ness."
Now I get it.
It sounds like "penis".
I just got it too.
Well, it's still Christmas to all of us,
and I made you all a little gift,
because you're like my new family.
"W-W-B-J-D"?
If this stands for
"What would Billy Joel do",
I'll tell you right now...
he'd write another crappy song.
Yeah, in your face, Billy Joel.
Who is that?
It stands for
"What would baby Jesus do?"
And it's to remind us
that the real meaning
of this season is Christmas.
Oh, well, thank you, Shirley.
I'm gonna put that in the
pocket closest to my heart.
No, no, no, it's a bracelet.
You put 'em on.
Everybody put 'em on.
Hey. Hey!
You took all the winter-doodles.
What are you, a douche bag?
They're for my friends.
There's a lot of other cookies left.
No, there's only macadamia
nut cookies there, okay?
I have a tree-nut allergy.
You should probably stay away
from Christmas-tree-shaped cookies.
Ha ha! That did not even
make allergic sense.
What are you, an idiot?
Okay, we get it.
You and the A-team are awesome.
Now beat it.
Oh, look at that.
Pretty boy standing up
for bird face over here.
Give me a winter-doodle.
If you're trying to be menacing,
maybe don't call the cookie by its name.
Oh, you're funny. You're a funny man.
Want to hear something funny, funny man?
Knock, knock.
My fist up your balls!
Who's there?
Ha ha ha! Merry happy!
This ain't over.
There won't always be a Dean around.
All right?
Still waiting on those cookies, Abed.
Sync by YesCool - Corrected by 4be1
www.addic7ed.com
Jeff protected my honor.
It was like my bodyguard,
but I was the kid from meatballs,
Jeff was the guy from full metal jacket,
and the moustache guy was the brother
of the guy on entourage.
Thanks for dumbing that down for us.
- You got it.
- So what's the deal, Jeff?
You leave your stones
in your other suit?
Why didn't you rap that guy in the face?
For the same reason that I floss,
have a bed frame, and keep
my guitar in its case...
I'm over 23.
I'm proud of you for
handling it peacefully, Jeff,
like a certain little birthday boy.
Real men turn the other cheek.
Let's see 'em. Nonsense.
Men were wired to fight each other
so that women could
choose the right mate.
No, the real reason men fight
is to release their pent-up gayness.
That guy wasn't gay.
He had a moustache.
You know what I have? Finals.
Are we cramming for Spanish or not?
I need a 65,
or I'm gonna flunk the class.
Why didn't you do the
extra-credit assignments
if you knew that you were...
failing?
Because doing more than the minimum work
is my definition of...
failing.
Quick question... Are you all coming
to my Christmas party
right after the final,
or are you stopping home to change
into your Christmas outfits?
I guess I could wear one
of my Hanukah sweaters.
Uh, Annie...
I... I didn't know you weren't,
um, Christian.
Yep.
One might even say I'm Jewish.
Oh, t... that's good for you.
T... that's wonderful.
I respect all religions of the world.
- I'm Muslim.
- Jehovah's witness.
- Atheist.
- The Lord is testing me.
Guys, this is a subject
that breeds conflicts.
- Can we please do...
- What religion are you, Jeff?
I'm agnostic.
Agnostic... lazy man's atheist.
- I'm born-again.
- Oh.
Yeah, we had a re-birthing ritual
in my friend's hot tub.
I'm now a level-five laser
lotus in my Buddhist community.
Uh, that does not sound like Buddhism.
Are you sure you're not in a cult?
Just by asking me that question,
you've put me back down to a level four.
You now owe me 2,000 Energon cubes.
Do you know how foolish
you sound right now?
What else do you believe in,
blood transfusions?
Jehovah's witnesses are a
type of Christian, right, Troy?
Yeah, but we don't celebrate
birthdays or Christmas,
and we can't drink.
But it helps.
So you're like a Muslim.
Salaam alaikum.
Shama-lama-ding-dong.
Wow, don't we have a
diverse little family.
I say we open up this...
this party to all faiths.
I brought my star of Bethlehem,
which led the wise men to
the savior of all mankind.
And you guys can bring a
little trinket or doodad
from your philosophies.
Sounds good?
As an agnostic,
I'm gonna bring my winning smile.
That's not enough.
Ugh! So boring.
Done. Hee hee.
Hee hee.
Hmm. Feliz Navidad.
"True or falso or none of the above?"
That doesn't make any sense.
Hey, look at that.
Forehead's taking a test.
Why don't you get going, Chuck Norris?
Did you just shoo me?
Why don't you just kiss him already?
Dude, I will shoo your
nose down your throat!
Senor Chang,
can you do something about this?
I'll allow it.
Que pasa here, huh?
It's usted, dude. Even I know that.
You picked the wrong day to
correct my Spanish, no sleeves.
It's on!
He's doing this for me.
He's my bodyguard.
- You wanna dance?
- Maybe to some show tunes?
No, I want to beat the crap out of you.
And I'm gonna enjoy it,
because you're just like this school.
You're obnoxious,
you're cramping my style,
and you smell like French-fry oil.
I don't get it!
But not the one by the parking lot!
Right! The one by the trash
cans near the orange cones
where they're building
the wheelchair ramp!
Yeah.
Best exam ever.
That guy's awesome, man.
So help me if that
jerk-weed made me fail.
Well, I aced it, amigo.
That means "cousin".
So what's my role going
to be in the fight?
Is there a key moment where
I finally stand up for myself
and take revenge on the villain?
Uh, maybe you should just hang back.
Yeah I will. In his face!
Whatever you do,
don't tell Shirley about the fight.
She'll start in with all her mother-y,
guilt-inducing powers.
- You know what I mean?
- No.
I'm wearing this Jesus bracelet
'cause it gets me chicks.
I know guys like this Mike.
He used to be a nerd.
Now he's a meathead.
Dangerous combo.
Tyson, Lou Ferrigno, Rosie O'Donnell.
You're a pretty big dude.
Probably got some moves.
Yeah, I got some... theories.
- You've never been in a fight?
- Technically, no.
I guess I'm too charming and likable.
Call me a name.
I can't.
Are you telling me you've
never been punched in the face?
No, thank God. This is the moneymaker.
First time I got punched in the face,
I was like, "Oh, no!"
But then I was like, "This is a story".
And a good one.
Yeah.
Every man should be punched in the face.
It's a rite of passage.
In my day, Friday night was
smoke a doobie, feel up a gal,
and then get your teeth
knocked out by a republican.
Guys the plan here
isn't for me to get hit.
It's for me to hit him.
Oh, then it's settled.
We have to teach Jeffrey how to fight.
I know a few moves.
Troy, I assume you're
handy with a switchblade.
Abed, you get back to the family tent,
try to find a chicken for Jeff to Chase.
Guys, I appreciate the enthusiasm,
but, uh, I think I got this.
Oh, well, look who it is.
We got forehead, old head,
dumb head, and, uh... the other head.
See you at 3:00, forehead.
Give me a snowman, dork!
See this, funny guy? Huh?
Huh?
Classic Rosie.
Fight lessons in a half an hour?
Good plan.
Hello. Oh.
Is this your Hanukkah holder?
It's, uh... it's pretty.
We'll just, uh...
Let's just put it...
There we go. That's nice.
So I can't believe
I never knew you were a Jew.
I'd say the whole word next time.
So, uh, do you think everyone
will start arriving soon?
I think they're gonna
come after Jeff's fight.
After Jeff's what now?
Jeff wants to fight that bully.
On Christmas?
Um, will you excuse me for a moment?
And can you finish the manger scene?
We know you were one of us.
'Sup? 'Sup?
'Sup!
No, it's a question.
'Sup? 'Sup?
Not a real question, a rhetorical one.
You have the answer. He does not.
Okay, then you give him
the forest Whitaker eye.
- That's pretty good.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, hold that stare.
There you go. Hold it.
Then you look straight through his eyes
and deep into his soul.
And then you move to Vermont.
I am sick and tired
of you saying that fighting is gay!
She's got a point.
You know, in boxing,
you fight for the purse and the belt.
I've gotta write a paper about that.
All right, I've seen enough.
Let's see what we're working with.
Go ahead, throw a few at the old paws.
What are you,
a North Korean seamstress?
Not if that's bad.
Get mad! Come on!
If it helps, think of me
as somebody who annoys you.
Ooh, that's it! That's... that's good.
Britta, put your blouse back on.
Oh! Ow!
Boys, this is not a game.
You gotta be ready for anything.
Dude, that is not cool!
Well, that foxy Black girl thinks it is.
Hmm? Ow!
- What are you doing?
- Why does she have to be black?
What is going on?
We're trying to get Jeff
ready for the fiiiii...iiight.
I couldn't think of another word.
Idiot.
He meant we were figh...
...ting.
It is hard to think of another word.
You realize there's no
other way for me to take this
than as a giant middle finger
to the most important day of the year.
December 10th?
It's our Christmas,
and I'm having a party.
Due to my divorce and my
relatives picking sides,
this will be the only Christmas party
I throw this year.
Will you be there, or
will I have another family
letting me down?
I told him not to fight.
He wouldn't listen.
I don't know what that is.
Jeffrey,
I have two boys.
And when we have a serious discussion,
I find that a brownie
helps them to relax.
So why do you hate me and Jesus?
I don't think my brownie's working.
Please don't do something so ugly
on a day so important to me.
Again, it's December 10th.
You think religion is stupid?
No, no.
To me, religion is like Paul Rudd.
I see the appeal, and I would
never take it away from anyone.
But I would also never
stand in line for it.
And look, Shirley,
the die has been cast
with this crazy bully guy.
He picked on Abed,
and he corrected my Spanish.
So you go to your party,
and I'll see you soon.
Jeffrey, I forbid you from fighting.
Well, you don't get to.
You're not my mom.
You're right.
But if you show up for the fight,
don't show up for my party.
Oh, come on, Shirley, don't be mad.
I'm not mad. I'm disappointed.
That's "mom" for mad.
Oh, hash browns and applesauce...
That's nice.
Oh, what is that interesting smell?
It's a traditional Muslim dish.
It looks delicious.
I'm guessing as a woman
I won't be allowed to eat that.
That's too bad.
Oh, look, Britta brought
what she believes in...
nothing.
Where should I put my
Buddha incense holder?
I'm pretty sure that's a bong.
Where's Jeff?
I guess he made his choice.
I want to go to Jeff's fight.
As I told Jeff,
no one that goes to the fight
can come to my party.
He's dead to me.
And if any of you leave,
you'll be dead to me too.
Let's sing.
# Jesus is a friend of mine #
everybody!
Come on, everybody.
You don't know it?
You're banning Jeff from the party?
That doesn't seem very Christian.
Well, that's an
interesting point of view
coming from an atheist.
I did my best to create
a special Christmas
for my one intact family, and...
this is the thanks I get.
Shirley, you are a guilt machine.
And Annie knows a thing
or two about guilt.
Am I right, Jew?
Say the whole word!
Jewie?
You would never catch
a Jehovah's witness
saying "Jewie".
Tell it to the birthday
cake you never got.
You know, there's an old Buddhist saying
in my vision group.
You are not a Buddhist.
You are in a cult.
Suck it, Nietzsche!
Guys, everyone's faith is weird.
Let's just not talk about it.
There's nothing weird
about Christianity.
Guys! Guys! Guys! Guys!
Are we really gonna let
religion divide us like this?
I think there's one
thing we can all agree on.
- I get 72 virgins in heaven.
- No.
That we would all like to
have Jeff at this party.
- Mm-mm.
- He can't come.
- Shirley.
- Mm-mm.
Shirley, listen.
I get that this is your first Christmas
since your husband left you,
and I don't know,
maybe that's why you're
being so stubborn,
because you're trying so
hard to re-create something
that you're afraid that
you've lost forever.
But if you really want us
to be your second family,
then you've gotta start
treating us like one,
even if that means supporting us
when we do things that
you don't agree with.
You can start by rooting for Jeff
while he rolls around on the ground
groping another man.
That's what I'm gonna do.
The cranberry sauce
has real cranberries.
Look, if he doesn't show up,
We're definitely going
to Applebee's, right?
Yeah.
I'm getting into a fight
no matter what today, dude.
No matter what!
Look who showed.
Oh, check him out. Ahh...ahh!
What's up, dude? No backup today?
Huh? Looks like grandpa and weirdo
couldn't show up to get
their teeth knocked out, huh?
Can I ask you a question?
Are you perpetually
on your way to the gym?
Dude, my life is a gym!
- Well, 'sup?
- 'Sup, man?
- 'Sup?
- 'Sup? 'Sup?
'Sup? 'Sup?
Whoa.
Dude, what is that?
All right, just one sec.
These are very expensive.
All right...
Dude, you wear a bracelet?
Your name's Mike, right?
So?
Mike, I'm not gonna fight you.
I have a friend that believes
this is the time of year
where you put aside your differences,
and you make peace.
Me... I don't believe in any of that,
but I do believe in friendship.
And as much as I hate you
and the cast of breakin',
I have to ask myself,
what would Shirley do?
- Oh!
- What would Shirley do?
- I think...
That she would shake your hand
and wish you a Merry Christmas.
Daa!
Jeffrey...
Kick his ass!
Cavalry's here. Shirts off, boys!
Come on, I'm being punked, right?
Come here. Come here.
Please, it's Christmas.
It's December 10th!
Not the moneymaker.
Not the moneymaker!
Ow! Ow!
Aah!
You're welcome!
Yeah! That was really good.
- Yeah!
- That was nice.
Thank you, thank you. I get it, yes.
It is I, Senior Chang.
Shakira, hold this.
So... I have finished
grading everyone's finals,
and all of you are moving on.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yes.
Heh heh heh, except... for Jeff.
Turns out you...
pause for dramatic effect...
will be seeing me next semester.
Noooooooo!
In Spanish 102! Heh heh heh.
Because he passed, you know.
And I'm the only Spanish teacher.
Yay!
I meant about Jeff passing.
You being our Spanish teacher...
Eh.
Whoa.
Man, Mike got you good.
Actually, uh,
that was my present to Jeff.
I don't care.
I got a Mountain to shred.
Jeffrey, you're a man now.
How's it feel?
I got hit in the face, like, four times
before you punched me.
Some people just don't know
how to say thank you.
Pierce, thank you.
And thanks to all of you
for showing up and having my back
when we fought those fly dancers.
So, uh...
- Merry...
- No, no, no, no, no.
Holiday.
Actually, I was gonna say merry semester
and happy new one.
Here we go. Here we go.
- Switch.
- Switch, switch glasses.
Sync by YesCool - Corrected by 4be1
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net