Okay, you can
hear this? okay.
Good morning.
I'm here to kick off
the first day of new tradition
At our school called
"green week."	|Dean All	|01
- what?
First, we give a month
to black history,
Now we're blowing
seven days on the irish.	|Pierce Group	|01
- all this week,
greendale college
Is becoming so earth-smart
That we're changing
our name to envirodale!	|Dean All	|01
- but we were already
called greendale.	|Starburns Dean	|01
Well, there's, um,
also going to be
A free
rock and roll concert
By a certain band
called green day.
Huh?
that make you happy?	|Dean All	|01
- eh, no. not really.	|Starburns Dean	|01
- okay,
we need to redo these.	|Dean Assistant	|01
- we printed 5,000.	|Assistant Dean	|01
- well, print 5,000 more.
I'm trying to save
the planet, here.	|Dean Assistant	|01
- pencils down.	|Chang All	|02
I want you all to write
a one-page essay,
in espanol, entitled,
annie's mistake.	|Chang All	|02
- why doesn't annie
have to write it?	|Pierce Chang	|02
- okay, two pages,
entitled,
the consequences
of questioning authority.	|Chang All	|02
- this is spanish 101.
I know how to say
"hello," "tomorrow,"
And that tables
are female.
That's the only spanish
you taught us.	|Shirley Chang	|02
- oh, six pages
on ignorance.	|Chang All	|02
- guys,
put your hands down.	|Britta All	|02
Senor chang, please continue.
we respect your authority.	|Britta Chang	|02
- thank you, britta.	|Chang Britta	|02
20 pages on ass kissing!
Due on monday.	|Chang All	|02
- this monday?	|Annie Chang	|02
- you know, if senor chang
gets any crazier,
He's gonna win
one of those grammy awards.	|Pierce Group	|03
- i've already
reported him to the dean.
He said they've been trying
to fire him for three years,
But nobody wants his job.	|Annie Group	|03
- mm-mm, i can't write
a 20-page paper.
I got a presentation
in my marketing class on friday
And public speaking gives me
the nervous sweats.	|Shirley Group	|03
- i can help you
with that.	|Pierce Shirley	|03
- i accept.	|Shirley Pierce	|03
That's how messed up
things are.	|Shirley Group	|03
- well,
we're screwed too.
We're three days behind
on our biology lab.	|Troy Group	|03
- the reason it's taking so long
is because troy's afraid--	|Abed Group	|03
- i'm not afraid, abed.
I choose not to be around rats
because they are unpopular.
Same goes for centipedes
and lakes.	|Troy Abed	|03
- there's only one solution.
Someone has to go to chang
and talk to him.	|Britta Group	|03
- i vote we all look at jeff
at the same time.	|Annie Group	|03
- in a way,
all of you are right.
Okay, what
was i tuning out?	|Jeff Group	|03
- you have to get chang to
call off some of this homework.
You're the one
with the silver tongue.	|Annie Jeff	|03
- yeah, go tongue chang.	|Pierce Jeff	|03
- guys, what makes you think
i can convince chang of anything
If i can't even convince you
not to make me do it?	|Jeff Group	|03
- i guess it sounds crazy.	|Britta Group 	|03
- oh...	|Annie Group	|03
- jeff does raise a good point.	|Troy Group	|03
- i don't get it.	|Pierce Group	|03
- wait,
you are convincing!	|Troy Jeff	|03
- you just made us change.
you could do it.	|Shirley Jeff	|03
- you want me
to risk the "c"
That i'm pulling
in that psycho's class
By putting myself
on his radar?
I mean, that guy
goes any more nuts,
He's gonna win a grammy.	|Jeff Group	|03
- you are hilarious.	|Troy Jeff	|03
- that's very funny.	|Abed Group	|03
- he's funny.	|Shirley Group	|03
- what is it,
the chair?	|Pierce Group	|03
- jeff, how do you think
You're gonna keep pulling
a "c" in that psycho's class
If he keeps assigning
this much work?	|Britta Jeff	|03
- because
i have you guys.	|Jeff Group	|03
- well, guess what,
handsome hobo.
Your gravy train's
leavin' the station.	|Annie Jeff	|03
- ignore what she's doing.
we are serious.	|Troy Jeff	|03
- fine. i'll do it.
But when you find my body,
don't believe the suicide note.	|Jeff Group	|03
- hmm. this better not
awaken anything in me.	|Dean	|04
- green day's here.	|Assistant Dean	|05
- oh, wow.
Okay,
what's this about, now?	|Dean GreeneDaeye	|05
- we're greene daeye.	|GreeneDaeye Dean	|05
- oh.	|Dean	|05
- what do you want,
winger?
Here to complain
about the homework
On behalf of the class?	|Chang Jeff	|06
- can i ask you a personal
question, senor chang?	|Jeff Chang	|06
- okay, freud.
Sure. you try to penetrate
my psychological armor, and--	|Chang Jeff	|06
- did your wife
leave you?	|Jeff Chang	|06
- holy--
How did you know?	|Chang Jeff	|06
- well, when you
pick juries,
You learn to read
the little stuff.
Same shirt
twice in one week.
teaching us the word
"esposa" means "liar."
The picture of you
with a woman
With a post-it note
dialogue balloon above her head
That says, "enjoy it
while it lasts."	|Jeff Chang	|06
- we met at a salsa club.	|Chang Jeff	|06
- mm.	|Jeff Chang	|06
- and, um...
she loved
the way i danced.
But...i mean,
you know how it goes.
Just--get a job...	|Chang Jeff	|06
- stop salsa dancing.
of course i know.	|Jeff Chang	|06
- you make no mistake
about this, winger.
I pleasured
that woman greatly.	|Chang Jeff	|06
- yeah. you look like
you would have to.
I'm not surprised
you said that.	|Jeff Chang	|06
- i like you, winger.
Pickled bull testicle?	|Chang Jeff	|06
- uh, are you offering
or collecting?	|Jeff Chang	|06
- * mary had a little lamb
* little lamb,
little lamb... **	|Extra Rat	|07
- * row, row,
row your boat *	|Garrett Rat	|07
- * somewhere out there *	|Abed Rat	|08
Troy, sing.
The assignment is to train a rat
to respond to a specific song.	|Abed Troy	|08
- yeah, did you
have to pick a duet?
Hmm?	|Troy Abed	|08
- hmm?	|Abed Troy	|08
* somewhere out there *
* beneath the pale moonlight *	|Troy Rat	|08
* beneath the pale moonlight *	|Abed Rat	|08
- he did it!	|Abed Troy	|08
good boy, fievel.	|Abed FievelRat	|08
Commencing reward.
i have to open the cage.	|Abed Troy	|08
- yeah, you don't have
to warn me; i'm not afrai--	|Troy Abed	|08
- fievel.	|Abed	|08
- everybody shut up!
I'll kick all your asses!
But y'all have
to come up here!	|Troy All	|08
- dude, you are gonna be fine.	|Jeff Chang	|09
- ah. yeah.	|Chang Jeff	|09
- you just have to move on.
And if you hang out
with me sometime,
You will see how great
single life can be.	|Jeff Chang	|09
- yeah?	|Chang Jeff	|09
- yeah.	|Jeff Chang	|09
- what about tonight?	|Chang Jeff	|09
- absolutely.
Oh, shoot.
My spanish study group has to
get together every night now.
You know,
you have been really
Letting us have it
with this homework.	|Jeff Chang	|09
- i really have,
haven't i?	|Chang Jeff	|09
- yeah.	|Jeff Chang	|09
- tell you what.
For my new buddy jeff,
essay canceled. sha-clackey.	|Chang Jeff	|09
- fantastic. that is fantastic.
everybody will be so happy.	|Jeff Chang	|09
- oh, oh,
i didn't say everybody.
It's for
my new friend jeff.
I mean, you're the one
coming out with me, right?	|Chang Jeff	|09
- right. yeah.	|Jeff Chang	|09
- i suppose it will put you
in an unenviable
And uncomfortable
position, and want to be--	|Chang Jeff	|09
- here's your jacket.
let's do this.	|Jeff Chang	|09
- is there a rat in here?	|Abed Chang Jeff	|10
- i have no idea
what you're talking about.	|Jeff Abed	|10
- abed.	|Chang Abed	|10
- el tigre.	|Abed Chang	|10
- well, did you
talk to chang?	|Britta Jeff	|11
- yeah, but it didn't
do any good.
My head still hurts
from all the yelling.
And my pupils are
more sensitive to light
Because he yelled
at me so much.	|Jeff Britta	|11
- oh, now i feel bad
that we made you do that.
Maybe we can help
with your essay.	|Annie Jeff	|11
- oh, that's okay.
i'm working on mine by myself.
You could do
my homework next time.
See you in class.	|Jeff Annie	|11
- he's hiding something.	|Britta Annie Troy	|12
- britta, jeff suffered for us.
give him a little credit.	|Annie Britta	|12
- yeah. you can be
pretty cold.	|Troy Britta	|12
- troy?	|Abed Troy	|13
Damn. Here comes Abed.
he needs my help.
I got to get out of here.	|Troy Abed	|13
- troy?	|Abed Troy	|13
Have you guys seen a rat?
Troy knocked over
fievel's cage and he escaped.	|Abed Britta Annie	|13
- oh, abed, i'm sorry.
He probably
found more rats
And is very happy
living with them.	|Britta Annie	|13
- try to join the rest of us
in reality, britta.	|Abed Britta	|13
- i believe that, uh,
Fusing brownies
with the, uh, internet
Is going to create
the next napster
for brownies.	|Shirley	|14
- yawn!	|Pierce Shirley	|14
- can't i just
write it on cards?	|Shirley Pierce	|14
- no.
Do you know anybody
who reads from cards?
No, you don't,
and that's why.
Also you might
consider a darker top.	|Pierce Shirley	|14
- note taken.	|Shirley Pierce	|14
- oh, and
Don't--don't, uh,
lock your knees.
Never lock your knees.
You know what happens
when you lock your knees?
You die.
Second,
When you want
to drive home a point,
Hand them a sandwich.
Try it.
hand them a sandwich.	|Pierce Shirley	|14
- hand them a sandwich.	|Shirley Pierce	|14
- yeah, except you just dropped,
uh, the sandwich,
As opposed
to handing it to them.	|Pierce Shirley	|14
- hand them--oh, okay.	|Shirley Pierce	|14
- right. so yeah.
And try attention-grabbing words
to wake up the audience
Such as, uh,
"multiple orgasm."	|Pierce Shirley	|14
- oh, no, no,
i don't think that would
Really fit into my message.
Maybe we should focus,
uh, more on, um, uh...	|Shirley Pierce	|14
- yeah, and about these
filler words of yours.
I mean, nobody wants to buy
brownies from somebody who says,
"um," and "like."
I have a method for fixing that.
start from the top.	|Pierce Shirley	|14
- okay.
These brownies are, um--	|Shirley Pierce	|14
- uh!	|Pierce Shirley	|14
- they, um--	|Shirley Pierce	|14
- these brownies are...
Delicious.
They taste like--	|Shirley Pierce	|14
- like!	|Pierce Shirley	|14
- that's not a filler word.	|Shirley Pierce	|14
- whatever, valley girl.	|Pierce Shirley	|14
- the difference
between usted and tu
Is a matter of formality.	|Chang All	|15
pepe, usted es viejo.
"you are old."	|Chang Pierce	|15
alberto, usted es feo.
"you are ugly."	|Chang Abed	|15
- no, you're not, abed.	|Shirley Abed	|15
- thanks.	|Abed Shirley	|15
Shakira...
Shakira...	|Chang Shirley	|15
y tupaco...	|Chang Troy	|15
ustedes estan sucios.
"you are dirty."	|Chang Troy Shirley	|15
- dirty?	|Shirley Chang	|15
- dude	|Troy Chang	|15
- still formal,
but plural.
Because,
while both are dirty,
Neither are my friends.
Okay?
And, on another subject,
Hope you guys are working hard
on your essays.
Because that's gonna be
30% of your grade.	|Chang All	|15
- no.	|Annie Chang	|15
- no.	|Shirley Chang	|15
- jeff...already turned in
his essay.	|Chang All	|15
Great job.	|Chang Jeff	|15
- thanks.	|Jeff Chang	|15
- as soon as you turn in
your essays on monday,
There's gonna be
a big-ass quiz.
So study hard.
class dismissed.	|Chang All	|15
Ahh.	|Chang	|15
- hey, dude.
crazy night
last night, man.	|Chang Jeff	|16
- hey, when you go out with me,
it gets crazy.
That's the winger guarantee,
huh?	|Jeff Chang	|16
- dude, let's do it again.	|Chang Jeff	|16
- ooh, yeah, i want to.
It's just the quiz,
you know?
Study, study.	|Jeff Chang	|16
- well, how 'bout this?
Bling.
A-plus.
Nice work, winger!	|Chang Jeff	|16
- you know, i knew i could do it
if i applied myself.	|Jeff Chang	|16
- cher--cherry daiquiri.	|Jeff Chang	|17
- cherry daiquiri!	|Chang Jeff	|17
- daiquiri.	|Jeff Chang	|17
- uh-huh.	|Jeff Group	|17
- Later.	|Chang Jeff	|17
- you devious clump
Of overpriced fabric
and hair product.	|Annie Jeff	|18
- speaking
as one of the meek,
As soon as i inherit
the earth, you a dead man.	|Shirley Jeff	|18
- you got a weird forehead.	|Troy Jeff	|18
- we're all
very disappointed.	|Britta Jeff	|18
- all right, dial it back
a little, britta.	|Pierce Britta	|18
- if anyone should
be disappointed, it's me.
What kind of a group
threatens to kick someone out
Unless he helps them?	|Jeff Group	|18
- what kind of a person
is asked to help other people
And then helps himself!	|Pierce Jeff	|18
- yeah.	|Annie	|18
- mm-hmm.	|Britta	|18
- helps himself?
I don't think i like
being talked to that way!	|Jeff Group	|18
- he's using fake outrage
to justify leaving.	|Britta Group	|18
- fake outrage?
justify my--
Yeah, that's it.
i'm out of here.	|Jeff Britta	|18
- oh, you're breaking up
with the group?	|Annie Jeff	|18
- that's what you guys want.	|Jeff Group	|18
- it's all right,
i've been divorced seven times.
Don't answer your phones
And bury all your money
in the backyard.	|Pierce Group	|18
- here you go.
Look at pierce's paragraph
from unit two.	|Chang Jeff	|19
- let's see. "I took a computer class..."
The apple store.
Adorable.	|Jeff Chang	|19
- keep going, keep going.	|Chang Jeff	|19
- and the saleswoman
had manzanas gigante.
Ruined it.	|Jeff Chang	|19
- can you imagine
being married to him?	|Chang Jeff	|19
- seven times!
Seven different women
agreed to marry that guy.
- it's cra--	|Jeff Chang	|19
I'm so alone.
I'm so lonely!
I want to die.	|Chang Jeff	|19
- come on man, it--
come on, don't do that.	|Jeff Chang	|19
I...
Just miss her so much.	|Chang Jeff	|19
- yeah.	|Jeff Chang	|19
- i'm sorry.
This is so stupid.	|Chang Jeff	|19
- no, no, it's fine.
It's just--buddy,
you know...	|Jeff Chang	|19
- it's dumb!	|Chang Jeff	|19
- i can see that you're hurting.
Um, but i have to get
to accounting.
And it's not like i'm hitting
strip clubs
With professor whitman.	|Jeff Chang	|19
- you better not be!	|Chang Jeff	|19
- what?	|Jeff Chang	|19
- all i ask
Is for you to keep
filling the void in my soul.	|Chang Jeff	|19
- well, i'll have
to think of something.
Let me rest gently on your pecs.	|Jeff Chang	|19
- best closer to a presentation,
a nicholson quote.
Uh, you take a phrase
from one of his films
And you tailor it
to your product.
You can't handle
a moist towelette!
Something like that,
you know?
But you can't use that one.
that's--that's mine.	|Pierce Shirley	|20
- thanks, pierce.	|Shirley Pierce	|20
- sure.	|Pierce Shirley	|20
- i'm just gonna
write it on some cards.	|Shirley Pierce	|20
- okay.
Just don't let anybody know
i was involved.	|Pierce Shirley	|20
- why do you care so much?	|Troy Abed	|21
- i don't.	|Pierce Troy	|21
- because fievel's
going to die.	|Abed Troy	|21
- i'd rather die than listen.	|Pierce Abed	|21
- who's going to die?	|Annie Abed	|21
- yeah.	|Shirley Abed	|21
- the dean says
the exterminator is coming
Because of our rat.	|Abed Shirley Annie	|21
- i'd like to exterminate
this conversation.	|Pierce Abed	|21
- what are you doing?	|Britta Pierce	|21
- he's sitting
in jeff's chair,
So he's trying
to act like jeff.	|Abed Britta	|21
oh!
ohh.	|All	|21
- oh, an email.	|Pierce	|21
- i thought you might
want to help me out
Because we are friends.	|Abed Troy	|21
- abed, take it from
a former prom king.
real friends
help me with things.
Not vice versa.	|Troy Abed	|21
- i would face my fears
to help you.	|Abed Troy	|21
- exactly!
'cause you're my friend.	|Troy Abed	|21
- am i?
* somewhere *
* out there *	|Abed Troy	|21
- oh, abed.	|Troy Abed	|21
- * beneath the pale... *	|Abed Troy	|21
- he gets any nuttier,
they're gonna
put him on the view.	|Pierce Group	|21
- that works, yeah.	|Troy Pierce	|21
- what are we gonna do?
we gonna study?	|Pierce Group	|21
- oh, my--	|Shirley	|21
- fievel?
Fievel?
fievel.	|Abed Fiebel	|22
- whoo! whoo! whoo!
okay, thank you.
Green week
was a rousing success
Here at greendale.
And now for our band,
greene daeye!
By the way, they're not
the real green day.
Thought we should just
rip that band-aid off quickly.
Okay!	|Dean All	|23
- hey! what's up?
Just got your text, man.
Wanna hang out?
'cause if you don't,
i will fail you.	|Chang Jeff	|23
- actually, i had an idea
for an extra credit project.	|Jeff Chang	|23
- we've been asked
To dedicate
our first song
To senor and senora chang.	|GreeneDaeye All	|23
She said she didn't
want to talk to me.	|Chang Jeff	|23
- i didn't tell her
you wanted to talk.	|Jeff Chang	|23
- estimation
of market value
Of--of--of brownies has--
Ahem! i, uh--
target group--	|Shirley All	|24
- ms. bennett, i'm afraid
i have to ask you
To put down the cards.	|Professor Shirley	|24
- * somewhere *
* out there *
* beneath the pale moonlight *	|Abed Fievel	|22
- uh...
I--i--	|Shirley All	|24
- * someone's *
* thinking of me *
* and loving me tonight *	|Abed Fievel	|22
- * somewhere *
* out there *
* someone's saying a prayer *	|Troy Fievel	|22
- they are...wonderful.
We all love...brownies.
- if you love brownies,
you love life.	|Shirley All	|24
- * somewhere out there *	|Troy Fievel	|22
* and even though i know *	|Troy Fievel	|22
* how very far apart we are *	|Troy Fievel	|22
* it helps to think we might be wishing *	|Abed Fievel	|22
* on the same bright star *	|Abed Fievel	|22
* and when the night wind starts to sing *	|Abed Fievel	|22
* a lonesome lullaby *	|Abed Fievel	|22
* a lonesome lullaby *	|Troy Fievel	|22
* it helps to think we're sleeping *	|Abed Fievel	|22
* underneath that same big sky *	|Abed Fievel	|22
- AAH!	|Chang	|23
- * somewhere *	|Troy Fievel	|22
- * somewhere *	|Abed Fievel	|22
* out there *	|Troy Fievel	|22
* out there *	|Abed Fievel	|22
* if love can see us through *	|Troy Fievel	|22
* if love can see us through *	|Abed Fievel	|22
- here's brownie!	|Shirley All	|24
* then we'll be together *	|Troy Fievel	|22
* then we'll be together *	|Abed Fievel	|22
* somewhere out there *	|Troy Fievel	|22
* somewhere out there *	|Abed Fievel	|22
* out where dreams *	|Troy Fievel	|22
* out where dreams *	|Abed Fievel	|22
* come true *	|Troy Fievel	|22
* come true *	|Abed Fievel	|22
- aah, it's on my leg!
It's on my leg!
it's on my leg!
Aaaaah!
Disgusting!	|Troy Abed	|22
- thank you.	|Abed Troy	|22
- what's chang doing?	|Britta Jeff	|25
- uh...
He's getting a refill
on his void.	|Jeff Britta	|25
- i got an "a"
on my presentation,
And a lot of the credit
goes to pierce.	|Shirley Jeff	|26
- heh.
and i had a great sandwich.	|Pierce Jeff	|26
- we found the stupid rat.
And abed's gonna
shut up about it now.	|Troy Jeff	|27
- it's true.	|Abed Jeff	|27
- i have something to say.
I've been
a horrible husband.
And i've been
a horrible teacher.
And i'd like to thank
my student jeff winger
For showing me that
And helping me
fix my marriage.
No more 20-page essays
due on monday!	|Chang All	|28
- oh, that's nice!	|Shirley	|28
- thank you.	|Jeff Chang	|28
- although, winger,
You should write
a one-page essay called
taking advantage
of the emotionally-vulnerable.
booyah.	|Chang Jeff	|28
- you did that for us?	|Britta Jeff	|28
- mm, kinda.	|Jeff Britta	|28
You know, i thought
hanging out with you guys
Was the worst way
to pass spanish.
I was wrong.	|Jeff Group	|28
- uh, we're the best.	|Pierce Jeff	|28
- jeff, i'm sorry i called you
a handsome hobo.
If you need help
with that essay,
You can rejoin the group.	|Annie Jeff	|28
- thanks.
What are you guys
talking to me for?
You go dance!	|Jeff Group	|28
- i know your secret.
I know about the chair.	|Pierce Jeff	|28
- whoa, what model
did you get?	|Troy Abed	|29
- it's the tsunami 3000
anniversary edition.
You?	|Abed Troy	|29
- the devil's drench xj-11.
This is gonna be awesome.
We should establish
base camps.
What part of the library
do you want?	|Troy Abed	|29
- i'll take the northeast.
Northeast is closest
to the drinking fountain--	|Abed Troy	|29
- all right, guys,
are we gonna do this thing?	|Pierce Abed Troy	|29
- pierce.
I hope that's the tiny gun
That you throw at us
to confuse us
While you grab
the giant gun
That's duct-taped
to your back.	|Troy Pierce	|29
- seriously, this hardly
seems like a fair fight.	|Abed Pierce	|29
Oh, it's pepper water!
oh, it's pep--
Who puts pepper in water?	|Troy Pierce	|29