- a small fading remnant
of a star.	|Annie Troy
- a white dwarf.	|Troy Annie
- that's right!	|Annie Troy
- i used a memory technique.
dwarves hate being called
midgets,
and midgets are small.	|Troy Annie
- and...
what does a star turn into
after it collapses?	|Annie Troy
- a movie of the week.	|Jeff Troy
- black hole.	|Troy Annie
- right!
troy! you could be
an astronomer.	|Annie Troy
- as far as i'm concerned,
there's only one black hole
worth studying.
it's called sagittarius a,
it's located in the center
of our galaxy,
and it has the density
of 40 suns.
just like my weiner.	|Pierce Group
- ha ha.
you said weiner.
that's funny.	|Troy Pierce
- pierce and troy
didn't get along at first,
but now they're bonding
through mutual adolescence.	|Abed Group
- shut up, boo-boo head.	|Pierce Abed
- will you shut up, fart head?	|Troy Abed
- hi, everybody.
well, look at this group
having some kind of meeting
and being so diverse.
there is just--boy!
there is just one of
every kind of you, isn't there?	|Dean Group
- well, we are missing
a pipsqueak,
but we don't want one,
so beat it.	|Pierce Dean
- um, pierce, that's the dean.	|Britta Pierce
- are you kidding?	|Pierce Britta
- mm-mm.	|Britta Pierce
- sorry.
just my luck.	|Pierce Dean
- it's all right.
don't let me interrupt.
sometimes i just roll around
campus like a little football.
i can't believe this.
here i am in a random
conversation about football,
and i'm talking
to troy barnes,
star quarterback
from riverside high...whoa.	|Dean Group
troy, did you know that
greendale has a football team?	|Dean Troy
- did you know
they had a football?	|Jeff Troy
- ha. that's very funny.	|Dean Jeff
troy, i was so sorry
to hear about your injury.
but now that you have
recovered,
we would love for you to play
for the human beings.	|Dean Troy
- the team's name
is the human beings?	|Shirley Dean
- yeah. my idea.
it was
the greendale grizzlies,
but i thought that, um...
well, a lot of these students
have been called animals
their whole lives.
unfortunately, i don't know
what to do about the mascot.	|Dean Shirley
- oh, i can help you
with that, your honor.
i have
a wealth of experience
in image management,
icon development,
and y2k preparedness.	|Pierce Dean
well, aren't you found money	|Dean Pierce
troy, all of your friends
are lining up
to turn greendale around.
how about you?	|Dean Troy
- troy isn't interested
in football anymore.
getting injured
in that keg stand
was the best thing
that ever happened to him.	|Annie Dean
- whoa! yoko ono much?	|Dean Annie
bros before hoes, troy.	|Dean Troy
listen, man.
no offense,
but i was the best,
and i finished on top.
i wouldn't play for this school
with a 10-foot pole.	|Troy Dean
- dean, i'm sure troy
will sign up for football
if and when some accident
damages the part of his brain
that feels pride.
until then,
would you excuse us?	|Jeff Dean
- all right, well, uh...
if you change your mind,
the field is always open.
oh, figuratively speaking.
you know,
wednesdays and sundays
it's used as parking overflow
for the mega-church.
okay.	|Dean Troy
- now let's meet
the minimum requirements
for a language credit,
shall we?	|Jeff Group
- yes, but i need to go
to the bathroom first.	|Shirley Group
uh, britta?	|Shirley Britta
- oh, no, i don't have to go.	|Britta Shirley
- i'll go with you.	|Annie Shirley
- what?
she's offended?	|Britta Jeff
- girls go in groups.
did you learn nothing from
stand-up comedy in the '90s?	|Jeff Britta
- i'm familiar with the concept.
i'm just-- fine.
if it's important to shirley,
i'll go with her next time.
i'm willing to try some more
mainstream feminine stuff.	|Britta Jeff
- well, then you should know
that nothing says "i'm a woman"
like doing it with me.	|Jeff Britta
- nothing says, "i'm a pig"
like you.	|Britta Jeff
- will they or won't they?
sexual tension.	|Abed Group
- abed, it makes the group
uncomfortable
when you talk about us
like we're characters
in a show you're watching.	|Jeff Abed
- well, that's sort of
my gimmick.
but we did lean on that
pretty hard last week.
i can lay low
for an episode.	|Abed Jeff
- you sure you made the right
call on the football team, troy?
it looks like
they won something once.
"most valued customer.
henderson trophy cases."	|Jeff Troy
- so we should still study
a little more astronomy
later, right?
maybe over some milky ways
or some mars bars.	|Annie Troy
- or pancakes!	|Troy Annie
- "i'm jeff. and i'm a student
at greendale."
that's not good.	|Jeff
- wood undergoes
rapid oxidation
because it reacts
spontaneously to--
okay, guys, seriously,
we've talked about this, okay?
you have got to turn off
your cell--
that's mine.
my bad.	|Extra All
i'm going to the bathroom.
- would you like
to come with me?	|Britta Shirley
- well, yes, yes, i would.
oh, that's nice!	|Shirley Britta
- okay, what's it called?
antoni--an--hold on.
does anyone have a pen?
pen?	|Extra Extra
no one has a pen.
why would you not bring
a pen to class?
idiot.	|Extra All
no, you're not an idiot.	|Extra Extra
- i had my blinker on
about five minutes,
and this no-good,
clearly bald
but trying to hide it
with a bandana loser
swooped right in.
i couldn't believe it.	|Shirley Britta
- maybe he didn't see you.	|Britta Shirley
- he saw me!	|Shirley Britta
- maybe he had
his blinker on too.	|Britta Shirley
- maybe. so you...
got any family, britta?	|Shirley Britta
- yeah, whatever.	|Britta Shirley
- think my mom might visit
this weekend.
she and i are gonna get
makeovers at that spa--	|Shirley Britta
- makeovers.
they sure have us programmed,
right?
i am a female pleasure unit.
i require a new
coat of paint.	|Britta Shirley
- just something
i thought might be fun.	|Shirley Britta
- here's something i think
might be fun.
let's find out the number
of makeup companies
that are owned by women.
i'll save you the trouble.
it's zero.
but of course you're saying,
"britta, aren't you a hypocrite?
"you're plastered with glitter
and goo from head to toe,
just like the rest of us."
well, i also pay income tax
and pull over for cops,
but that doesn't mean
i support--	|Britta Shirley
- thanks for offering to help
design the new mascot.
i, uh, have been
a little stumped.	|Dean Pierce
- that's no problem.
by the way,
i took the liberty
of thumbnailing
a human being prototype
which i modeled after da vinci's
vitruvian man.
- the penis is a little
small, i think.	|Pierce Dean
- oh, i think it's--
oh. okay.
it...looks a lot like you.
um, here's the thing.
if we are the human beings,
you know,
and we have a mascot
that's just a white guy,
what message are we sending?
our symbol needs to reflect
the diversity of our school
and our species.	|Dean Pierce
- so...black?	|Pierce Dean
- no. no, because we're not
the greendale blacks,
mr. hawthorne,
or the greendale asians
or any other creed.
we are the greendale
human beings.	|Dean Pierce
- sorry to disturb you guys...
who are clearly looking
at a naked drawing
of pierce
doing jumping jacks.	|Jeff Pierce Dean
dean, a quick download, please?	|Jeff Dean
- uh, absolutely.	|Dean Jeff
excuse me.	|Dean Pierce
- okay. fill me in later.	|Pierce Dean
ah.
whoa-oh.
i'll go with a pencil.	|Pierce
- first of all...	|Jeff Dean
- mm-hmm.	|Dean Jeff
- i'm flattered.	|Jeff Dean
- oh, well.
you're a very photogenic man.
is that real bed head, or do you
put something in there?
can i?
oh, it's crispy.	|Dean Jeff
- i was thinking about the four
disembodied heads,
and i thought,
where's the heart?
where's the soul?
where's the different
poster design?	|Jeff Dean
- you know, i did think
those were less than personable,
which is why i went with
the full bodies
in these mailers
we have going out.	|Dean Jeff
- mailers? i didn't give
permission for this.	|Jeff Dean
- jeffrey, did you not read
the release agreement
on the back
of your registration form?
i'm starting to see why
someone used to be a lawyer.
ha ha! up top!	|Dean Jeff
- if someone from the outside
were to find--
okay, if someone from
the outside were to find out
that i am a student
at a community college,
that could have a negative
impact on my future career.	|Jeff Dean
- oh. goodness.
look what we have
stumbled onto--
an opportunity
to help each other out.
i suppose i wouldn't need
this promotional campaign
if i could announce
to the press
that troy barnes
is playing football here.	|Dean Jeff
- i think he's been
pretty clear
about declining that offer.	|Jeff Dean
- i think if you said, "jump,"
he'd say, "how high?"
if you said, "stop,"
he'd say, "hammertime."
you starting to get
what i mean?	|Dean Jeff
- no. i need another example.	|Jeff Dean
- you know, i didn't...
realize before,
but we should send those out
to local businesses.
hmm?
law firms.
lawyer...
companies?
legal...
gatherings?	|Dean Jeff
- are you trying to
blackmail me?	|Jeff Dean
- i think so.	|Dean Jeff
- gentlemen...
i present to you
the greendale human being.	|Pierce Jeff Dean
- that's a falcon with a gun.
now it's a falcon
with an erection.	|Jeff Pierce
Hi Abed		|Shirley Abed
hi	|Britta Abed
He's just laying low	|Britta Troy Annie
Wait, are you going to the bathroom?	|Britta Shirley
uh, yes	|Shirley Britta
I'll go with you	|Britta Shirley
blue bird day
to shred some pow.
you know what? I'm good	|Shirley Britta
She probably just... you know... had to go number two	|Britta Annie Troy
Ok, what's the closest planet to Earth?	|Annie Troy
Planet Hollywood	|Troy Annie
That's not the right answer, but it shows how fun the astronomy can be!	|Annie Troy
Hey Troy, can I talk to you for a second?	|Jeff Troy
We are studying, so Troy is busy	|Annie Jeff
Well the galaxy is not going anywhere, I'll bring him back	|Jeff Annie
Do you ever miss being a quarterback, Troy?	|Jeff Troy
I miss being the best at something, miss having a coach
I miss knowing what to think	|Troy Jeff
You still know what to think, Troy	|Jeff Troy
Oh good	|Troy Jeff
For instance, after Dean talked about you playing football, you and I were thinking the same thing	|Jeff Troy
That dude looks like Moby	|Troy Jeff
You were thinking, what if Troy did play for Greendale
You'd be surprised how many of your favorite football players got started
at community college	|Jeff Troy
Oh really? Name one	|Troy Jeff
Who's your favorite player?	|Jeff Troy
Me. Woah	|Troy Jeff
Maybe you and I should checkout the Greendale Thunderdome	|Jeff Troy
the dome arrives later.
it comes with thunder.
let me tell you a little
secret about me, troy.
every day
on my way to school,
i drive through downtown
past the courthouse
just to get a glimpse
of the world that i once ruled.
and i just wanna jump
out of my car,
run up the steps and...
exploit the legal system
for profit.
but i can't.
i'm locked out of
my old kingdom.
you're not.
you see what i'm saying?	|Jeff Troy
- you're saying
i could be a lawyer.	|Troy Jeff
- i'm saying
you're a football player!
it's in your blood!	|Jeff Troy
- that's racist!	|Troy Jeff
- your soul.	|Jeff Troy
- that's racist.	|Troy Jeff
- your eyes?	|Jeff Troy
- that's gay?	|Troy Jeff
- that's homophobic.	|Jeff Troy
- that's black.	|Troy Jeff
- that's racist!	|Jeff Troy
- damn.	|Troy Jeff
- when you played,
you were a god.
now you're not playing,
and you're not.
i'd tell you to do the math,
but math isn't important.
the only thing that's important
is this.	|Jeff Troy
- yeah, but annie said--	|Troy Jeff
- annie said that
benjamin button was compelling.
look, she's a smart girl,
but sometimes she's just wrong.	|Jeff Troy
85--go long!	|Jeff Extra
it's like a drug, isn't it?
feel it, troy.
throw it!
the scoreboard lights up.
there will be a scoreboard
there.
it's complete!	|Jeff Troy
nice catch!	|Jeff Extra
the girls, the glory,
the scouts, the career!
it starts
when you join this team.	|Jeff Troy
- is that linebacker
a pregnant woman?	|Troy Jeff
- look,
you can meet them later.
but this decision
has to be yours, t-bone.
and this decision
has to be yes.	|Jeff Troy
- how did you know
my nickname's t-bone?	|Troy Jeff
- because you're
a football player,
and your name
begins with "t."
your name begins
with "t."	|Jeff Troy
- britta?	|Shirley Britta
- oh. are you finished?
i mean, i have to go,
but apparently,
i failed yesterday's tryouts
for the position
of bathroom companion.	|Britta Shirley
- oh, britta, i wasn't trying
to hurt your feelings.	|Shirley Britta
- you didn't hurt
my feelings, shirley.
i don't need to go to
the bathroom with other people.
i was just trying to throw you
a bone because i like you.	|Britta SHirley
- oh. you can keep that bone.
listening to a story about
a stranger pissing me off
and taking
the stranger's side?
and then you can't talk
about your own business,
but you insinuate
my mama's a robot
because she and i
want makeovers.
that is the ladies' room,
britta,
a place where ladies
go to share, listen,
support each other and...
discreetly eliminate waste.
and i like you too.
even like that
you're a little hard.
but if you can't learn
to be soft in there,
you need to pee alone.	|Shirley Britta
- i've peed alone
my whole life.
women have always hated me.
i don't even know
how it started.
maybe it was when i got boobs
before everyb--	|Britta Shirley
- shh, shh, shh.
not out here.
in there.	|Shirley Britta
- whoo!
ha ha!
troy, troy, the wonder boy!
you dropped your books,
poindexter. yeah!	|Troy Extra
- troy, i've been waiting
for an hour.	|Annie Troy
- it's all right, i'm worth it.
* hip, hop, body don't stop *	|Troy Annie
- troy.
why are you doing
a politically conservative
high school shamefully
outdated fight rap?
have you been playing
football?	|Annie Troy
- threw the skin around
a couple of times.
still got it.
eh...eh...eh...eh...
doosh!	|Troy Annie
- but you knew we had
an astronomy test tomorrow.	|Annie Troy
- class blows.
what i need to know
about the universe
is that i'm at the center
of it.	|Troy Annie
- troy! stop!
don't become
this person again.
this isn't the real you.
this is the arrogant jock
that totally ignored the only
people that truly liked him
for non-superficial reasons
but weren't allowed
to say anything
because their parents
are bigots!
football is bad for you,
troy.	|Annie Troy
- jeff said you'd say that.	|Troy Annie
- jeff...what now?	|Annie Troy
- troy!
troy, troy, troy.
that's my name.	|Troy
- i think if we add in
a little bit of phylicia rashad
we'll be in better shape.	|Pierce Dean
- yeah, you're right.
that beige is a little light.	|Dean Pierce
wow.	|Jeff Dean Pierce
- yeah. yeah.
we are developing
the perfect mascot.
no stereotypical identifiers
from any race or gender.	|Dean Jeff
- see, jeff, this is
a chart of the features
we're staying away from--
pan-asian eye folds,
irish chins,
women's breasts.	|Pierce Jeff
- is that seal?	|Jeff Dean Pierce
- that is our human color wheel.
it goes from seal
to seal's teeth.
- what do you think?	|Dean Jeff
- i think not being racist
is the new racism.	|Jeff Dean
- whoa, whoa, whoa--
what happened to the prototype?	|Dean Pierce
- ooh! i left the nose
in the kiln.	|Pierce Dean
- so...troy is gonna
play football.	|Jeff Dean
- yes!	|Dean Jeff
- which means i'll be getting
rid of these.	|Jeff Dean
- no. i won't mail these out,
but they are staying with me
until the press announces
that troy is a part of the team.
and i want him
at that pep rally tonight.
reporters are gonna be there.
we're gonna unveil
the new mascot.
and things are finally going
to start turning around.
oh, and...my ex-therapist
is gonna think twice
before he makes fun of my job!	|Dean Jeff
- here it is.
still hot.	|Pierce Dean
- ooh. ow.	|Dean Pierce
- oh, dean, i'm gonna get
some more coffee.
you want anything?	|Pierce Dean
- oh, yeah, a desmond tutu
with just enough cream to
make it a lou diamond phillips.	|Dean Pierce
- la bamba.
got it.	|Pierce Dean
i've been following you.
how much did the dean pay you
to make troy play football?	|Annie jeff
- i'm not having a conversation
with someone
who emerges from a bush.	|Jeff Annie
- because i'm right?	|Annie Jeff
- no. because i'm not in a
commercial for breakfast cereal.
look...the dean has pictures
of me, okay?
horrible pictures of me...
attending his school.	|Jeff Annie
- and for that
you'd convince troy
to flush his life down
football's toilet again?
britta's right, you are the most
selfish person alive!
and all that
is gonna end right now.
because i'm telling him what
kind of friend you really are.	|Annie Jeff
- maybe you should tell him
you're hopelessly in love
with him.
high school
must have been tough, huh?
waiting for a superstar
to notice you.
but here...here...
he's all alone,
and he needs so much help!
did you enroll
in all of his classes,
or were you worried
that might freak him out?
the important thing is that
you are there for him.
the important thing is that you
are the only one there for him.
and you don't really care
what he wants...
just as long
as you don't have to
share him with
the rest of the world.
because, really, you are
just as selfish as i am.
you're just not
as good at it yet.	|Jeff Annie
- you're right.
i could never be
as good as you.
probably because
i actually care.	|Annie Jeff
- profound, but technically
meaningless.
and don't bother trying
that thing that women do
where they walk away and make
the guy feel like crap,
because it won't happen!
yeah!	|Jeff Annie
damn it.	|Jeff
- shirley, will you please come
to the bathroom with me?	|Annie Shirley
where's shirley?	|Annie Britta
- shirley's not coming.
but i'm here...
to listen...girl.	|Britta Annie
- why do we inflict
so much pain on ourselves
for men?	|Annie Britta
- i don't--
know...sweetie.
maybe...it's because men
make the world go round?
kleenex?	|Britta Annie
i've been...
infatuated with troy.
now he's joining football.
now he'll have
his pick of the litter and...
i'll never get
to be with him!	|Annie Britta
- oh, annie, screw him!
there are guys out there
that would kill to be with you.
and if troy
isn't one of them,
that's him failing
your standards.
you got that?	|Britta Annie
- you're right.
i can't control him.
and if i truly cared
about him,
i wouldn't want to.
thanks for talking to me,
britta.
it really helped.	|Annie Britta
- seriously?	|Britta Annie
- yes.	|Annie Britta
- who's my girl?	|Shirley Britta
'scuse me!	|Shirley Annie
- i did it, i did it!	|Britta Shirley
- oh, yes, you did!	|Shirley Britta
- troy! troy!
don't go in there, man.	|Troy Jeff
- what?	|Jeff Troy
- you got the most you were
ever gonna get out of football
in high school.
a life of disillusionment
and depression
begins on the other side
of that door.	|Jeff Troy
- hey, man...is this your
first pep rally or something?	|Extra Jeff
- you told me
football was the most important
thing in the world.	|Troy Jeff
- well, buckle up, troy.
i was exaggerating.
it's kinda my gimmick.
let me tell you something--	|Jeff Troy
- no, let me tell you
something.
you know that keg flip
that cost me my scholarship?	|Troy Jeff
- yeah.	|Jeff Troy
- i hurt myself on purpose.	|Troy Jeff
- what?	|Jeff Troy
- there was a scout coming
to the final game at riverside
and...i couldn't
take the pressure,
so i took the easy way out.
but when you showed me
that field,
i saw there was nothing
to worry about here.
i could just play football
for the fun of it.
i mean,
have you seen these guys?
there is nowhere
to go but up.	|Troy Jeff
- dude, we have feelings.	|Extra Troy
- i don't know about you,
but i know i ended up here
because things weren't
that great out there.
you should try accepting
where you're at, man.
take a pottery class
or something.	|Troy Jeff
greendale, we're number one!
nancy pelosi is no fun!	|Troy All
- hey.	|Jeff Annie
- hey.
i've decided
to support troy.
they deploy things
in football, right?
i went for rhyme
over clarity.	|Annie Jeff
- look, i'm, uh...i'm really
sorry about before.
i just think
we were both wrong.	|Jeff Annie
- really? because
i'm an 18-year-old girl,
and you made me cry
in public.	|Annie Jeff
- mm. okay, maybe i was
a little more wrong.
i should grow up
and make peace with being here.
i mean, it's not like
greendale's gonna kill me
or anything.	|Jeff Annie
- holy crap!	|Jeff HumanBeing
- aah!	|Annie HumanBeing
- oh, sorry.
hey, say hello to our
ethnically neutral mascot--
the greendale human being.
the costume makes it
difficult for him to see.	|Pierce Jeff Annie
- he can't move his mouth
either.
but take it from me,
that's human for "hello."	|Dean Jeff Annie
let's get you
into the pep rally!	|Dean HumanBeing
- great idea.
let's do it!	|Pierce HumanBeing
we've solved racism.
what's next?	|Pierce Dean
- uh, let's do something
for little people.
ooh! or albinos!	|Dean Pierce
- little albinos.	|Pierce Dean
- this has the potential
to be a uniquely
greendale experience.
milady.	|Jeff Annie
- milord.	|Annie Jeff