Sync by honeybunny
Corrected by YesCool and by 4be1
www.addic7ed.com
The Bernoulli distribution
is the number of successes
in a sequence of independent
yes-no experiments.
Okay.
Uh, for the Quiz Monday,
brush up on chapters three and four.
Bernoulli's one of my favorites.
Little-known fact,
statistics were not his only love.
He's also famous for his French sauce
used on meat and poultry.
That's Bearnaise.
Oh, we may need
to settle this at a restaurant.
It's cute.
A little aggressive,
but as a busy,
confident woman of authority,
I'm attracted to men who take charge.
Are you being sarcastic,
or am I nailing it?
You were nailing it,
until you had to ask.
Oh, damn it. Starting over.
Hey, you in the skirt, date me.
I'd like to, Mr. Winger.
You're tall, you dress nice,
and I've graded enough of your tests
to know I'd never feel
mentally inadequate.
Thank you.
Only problem, I don't date students.
You know if you agree
to go out with me...
Oh, hey.
Awkward.
How small is this campus?
Bastard.
It's fine. I don't care.
It's disgusting the way men behave.
Did you ever see that
Katherine Heigl movie poster
where Gerard Butler had
that heart over his weiner?
That resonated with me.
Okay, fine.
But just to repeat,
I don't care what Jeff does.
Bastard.
I'm barely a student.
I'm older than you.
I drive a Lexus.
I saw "Ghost Busters" in the theater.
Look, my gums are receding.
It's uncanny how many
of my buttons you're finding,
but I have a personal rule about this,
and I stick to it.
Have a cup of coffee with me.
I bet I can change your mind.
Oh, I know you can.
That's why you're not
getting the chance.
Ooh, whoo.
Are you coming to my
Dias de los Muertos party?
I'm definitely gonna try to swing by.
Then I can mark you down
as definitely being there
from 7:00 sharp till upside-down
Spanish question mark?
- Here's the thing...
- No, here's the thing.
I am putting my foot down.
You understand?
I am being assertive,
and I am making eye contact,
and it is achieving results.
Are you trying to get
formidable with me?
It worked on Pierce.
Infomercials work on Pierce.
Jeff, you're the cool guy, okay?
If you show up,
it'll be the first party I host
where everyone doesn't say
they need to get home
in time for the news.
This won't work.
The last time you did this,
I saved a vial of your tears
and have been slowly
building up an immunity.
I was so unpopular in high school,
the crossing guard used to
lure me into traffic.
This party is a second chance
to be...
Hip.
Cool!
Laidback!
Look, I will come to your party.
Thank you.
I'm putting you down for two bags of ice
and a sleeve of paper cups.
Taking a pill?
- Yes, I am.
- Xenolovaden.
My grandpa took that
when he was around your age.
Fantastic.
But by the time grandpa got up in years,
his memory wasn't great.
He'd mix the wrong pills.
You know how old people are?
Heard stories about it, yeah.
One time he started hallucinating
and ran down the street
with no pants on.
Which in the Gaza Strip
is considered a real party foul,
so you should probably be careful...
Look, I really don't need your advice,
and I'm not your pantsless grandpa.
Pantsless grandpa.
Hola!
Scary.
Oh, cute! Cute.
Oh, Britta.
You look adorable.
Thank you.
I hate when women use Halloween
as an excuse to dress up
like sluts, you know?
Yeah.
Okay, everyone.
I think we can begin.
I've got everyone's
personalized cookie tombstones,
por tradicion,
and in a few minutes,
we're going to start
the dance of the dead...
La danza de los muertos.
You don't have to keep doing that!
Party on.
It's nice of you to be here.
Sure you'd rather be out
with your hot professor.
Well, it's funny,
I enrolled here as selfish loner,
but you and the group have given me
a crash course in friendship.
- She blew you off, huh?
- She's grading papers.
Professor Slater?
She's not grading papers.
She's at the faculty party
in the cafeteria.
Oh, look, it's the eavesdropping matador.
Are you saying my people are sneaky?
What?
There's a storm
building on the horizon,
but you and I will save the night.
Chex mix, pretzels, baby carrots,
predictable but appetizing.
- Hey.
Can I ask you something
I always wanted to ask
- the real Batman?
- Yeah.
Am I good looking?
You're a very attractive young man.
I knew it.
Let's get this party started!
Who are you?
I am the Beastmaster.
From the movie Beastmaster.
What rock have you been living under?
What are you going as?
A gay douchebag? Just kidding.
Nice one. I'm not much
of a costume guy.
I know, you're not much
of a liking the ladies guy either, huh?
Oop. Body blow. Is that liquor?
Hello.
Here's your drinks, mates.
Oh, thanks, Urkel.
I'm Harry Potter.
Really?
What up, Urkel?
Hey.
Oh...
All right. What are you taking?
You know, the usual cool stuff.
I've got 'ludes, uh, dreamers...
Johnny boys.
Tell you what.
I'll trade you one of mine
for two of yours. Hmm?
I don't know, Star-Burns. I'm...
Oh, sorry.
I thought I was dealing
with the Beastmaster.
Hey, hey, who said you weren't?
Saddle up, fruit pie.
I don't mind if I do, may I?
Here. take this.
Give anyone that shows up
their stupid credit.
You going to the faculty party?
Make me your plus one.
Ah, give it up, Winger.
Professor Slater doesn't date students.
Or married Asians who drive Mopeds.
Give you 20 bucks.
I'll bring the hog around.
Okay, it's time for the
"dance of the dead".
Everyone form a circle.
Lights. Music.
Is it under genre or
on a specific playlist?
Hey, uh, man?
What'd you slip me?
I keep grinding my teeth,
and I want to kiss everybody.
What'd you slip me, man?
My heart stopped racing,
and I can't pee.
Now for the first dance,
I'd like to invite a very
special guest to the floor.
Jeff Winger?
Jeff?
Where's Jeff?
Is Jeff gone?
You know, I'm gonna go.
I don't want to miss the news.
News!
He just stepped out.
He's gonna be right back.
He's going to the faculty party.
To be with professor "short skirt"?
We hate her.
No, it's not about her, Shirley.
I can't believe that
Jeff would do this to Annie.
Yes, absolutely. It's about Annie.
We should go find that bitch's car
and snap off her antenna.
It's like high school all over again.
Everyone's leaving.
Not me.
I could do this all night.
There you go, pretty lady.
What are you doing here?
Showing you my non-student side.
I have to admit,
this outfit's doing it for me.
I may or may not
have been deflowered
by a junior rodeo champion.
You're reminding me
of my first time too.
You lost your virginity to Robin Hood?
No, with an attractive woman at a party.
We seem destined to repeat history.
I told you no students.
It's unseemly.
I go out with you,
you tell your friends,
- it gets around the school...
- What friends?
I have no friends.
I hate everyone here but you.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
You should be over
at the library with Annie...
Whoa.
Yippy ki yay.
Thought you weren't a costume guy.
You had to have one
to get in here, Squirrel.
Oh, so where did you get it?
'Cause I wouldn't think
that any costume stores
would be open this late.
I don't know what you're getting at.
I think the words that you're looking for
are "I own a cowboy outfit."
And it is tight too.
Did you buy it like that?
Your toy gun to my head, I'd say yes.
Hi. Michelle Slater, PHD.
Britta Perry, GED.
Oh, are you a classmate of Jeff's?
Oh, well, when you say "classmate",
It sounds like we take naps
together and eat paste,
but what's great about
community colleges
is that a lot of the students
are just as mature as the teachers.
Jeff, you must return to Annie's party.
She's feeling unpopular.
Jeff, Pierce took something,
and he is tripping balls.
He is touching people and dancing weird.
it's like grumpy old men
but not hilarious.
Okay, uh, guys?
I'm at a grownup
Halloween party, all right?
You're all being unseemly.
- Oh, no.
- How are we unseemly?
Why is Urkel ripping the antenna
off professor Slater's car?
That's right, professor Slim Calves.
This is what you get when you
steal Jeff from a good woman!
No, Abed!
- Is he meowing?
- Yeah.
Enough. I want you guys out of here.
Britta, I don't care about
your high school soap opera.
Abed, you're not Batman.
Pierce. Pierce. Pierce.
Stop grinding on
the women's studies department.
You are too old to be tripping.
I'm old?
What do you mean old?
Whose hands are these?
Help me!
Way to go.
I know I'm not Batman.
You could try not being a jerk.
She's pretty hot.
Well, where were we, little doggie?
- Unseemly.
- Yeah. Crap.
Shirley?
Shirley!
This is professor Robin Hood's office.
So what are you doing?
I'm putting this hose in her desk,
and you going outside
to turn the water on.
Why?
To teach that long-neck
weave-having bank teller
she can't steal another woman's man!
That's why.
I have a confession to make.
I think some of what I just said
may have more to do with my situation.
Yeah, the long-neck,
weave-having bank teller
didn't feel universal.
My ex-husband came by this morning,
and he, uh, he asked for his ring back.
It was his mother's,
and he wants to give it
to his new girlfriend.
Shirley, that sucks.
Don't get me wrong.
Best thing ever happened to me
was him leaving.
I just... I always thought
he'd come crawling back,
and I'd get to tell him, "go to hell."
He couldn't even give me that.
You know what the crazy thing is, Britta?
Everything you've done tonight?
It's like I was too proud
to admit I was hurt,
so I had to pretend that you were.
I totally get that.
I feel better now.
Let's go check on Annie.
Can you believe
I targeted this poor lady?
Look at all these awards.
I bet she's nice.
Yeah.
Nice and pretentious.
Pierce?
Pierce, are you okay?
Hey, man, what's going on?
You have a full-on erection.
Just rela... Just relax.
Pierce, relax. Just relax, okay?
Pierce!
You are too old to be tripping!
Pierce...
You are too old to be tripping.
Tell me about the Beatles, Pierce.
Tell me about Woodstock
and Sputnik, Pierce.
Gee, do I feel a breeze here?
Because someone just struck out.
She blew you off too, Chang.
Is that what you had to fall back on?
Look at me, bro. Look at me.
I've got the body
of a fifth grader, okay?
If I was working with what you've got,
she'd be at the comfort inn right now
giving me a Mexican Halloween.
It's this campus.
It feeds on my coolness.
I... I got no moves anymore.
Moves?
Everything's a game to guys like you.
I know one move I bet
you've never tried in your life.
What is it?
Please sleep with me. Please.
Pretty please. I'm so lonely.
I haven't slept with anyone
in a very long time,
and you are so good looking.
Please do me the favor
of having sex with me.
Okay, stay three steps behind
and promise you won't tell anybody.
I promise.
Everybody, stay out of the library.
Pierce, it's okay. Come out of there.
No, I'm not ready to die!
Pierce, you're not gonna die!
Just... Just keep walking.
Don't make eye contact.
Jeff. Jeff! Jeff.
Pierce is freaking out.
You're the only one that can help.
What makes you think that?
Is Jeff out there?
He's the only one who can help.
He says he's gonna kill himself,
but he doesn't want us to call 911,
because he doesn't want
to get in trouble
for taking drugs.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I, uh...
I think I have to say goodnight.
Are you, like,
a court-appointed guardian
for these people?
Uh, no.
Um, they're my classmates.
Goodnight, Jeff.
Loser!
What in the Pink Floyd?
I'm gonna crush myself to death
with desks and tables, Jeff!
Is that a death befitting a Beastmaster?
I never saw Beastmaster.
I just wanted to be cool.
I'm coming in there, Pierce.
Those floating
Mexican skeletons were right.
My life is over.
Well, when we go to floating skeletons
with our problems,
we get what we pay for, don't we?
I'm old, Jeff.
Pierce, I don't know how
you spent the first 60 years,
but I know in the last two months
you've probably doubled
the national average
for amount of life lived per lifetime.
well, I do have a young,
African-American friend.
Yeah.
And, more importantly,
you're dressed like a gladiator
in a desk fort that you
built during a bad trip.
If life is just a series
of ridiculous attempts
to be alive,
you're a hero
to everything that's ever lived.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah!
- Batman?
- Yeah?
Are you staying for the party?
If I stay,
there can be no party.
I must be out there in the night,
staying vigilant.
Wherever a party needs to be saved,
I'm there.
Wherever there are masks,
wherever there's tomfoolery and joy,
I'm there.
But sometimes I'm not,
'cause I'm out in the night,
staying vigilant, watching,
lurking, running, jumping,
hurtling, sleeping...
No, I can't sleep.
You sleep. I'm awake.
I don't sleep. I don't blink.
Am I a bird? No.
I'm a bat.
I am Batman.
Or am I?
Yes, I am Batman.
Happy Halloween.
- I'm Batman.
- You sound like cookie monster.
- That's Batman.
Candy corn looks like tiny traffic cones.
Yeah, it sure does.
At, like, a candy traffic school.
Like, a little gingerbread man
at the wheel,
and he's drunk.
Look out.
You'd be driving,
But you keep wanting to eat yourself.
All day.
That's one of my biggest fears.
What is?
If I ever, like, woke up as a donut.
You would eat yourself?
I wouldn't even question it.
That'd be tasty.
It's cool to know other people
think about this stuff too.
Yeah.
www.tvsubtitles.net