- Missed you at lunch today.
Did you slip out for a quickie
with professor hot stuff?
- Her name is Michelle,
and how did you know?
- There's a gold star
on your fly.
- [Gasps] You weren't kidding.
You know, it's nice to have
a girlfriend
with a sense of humor and one
who recognizes good work.
- Oh, it'll change your life.
Let me teach you the chords.
See, that's "g."
that's the most important chord.
In my mind,
it... it stands for "God."
- Why is Annie talking
to micro-nipples?
- Vaughn?
Whatever.
- But not like a bible God,
because I think that God
is in everything.
- You're complicated.
- * Annie *
* Annie,
where are you going today? *
- Spanish class.
- * Spanish *
- you know what I don't get?
He never wears a shirt.
He never wears shoes.
Why hasn't he died
from lack of service?
- You watching another movie
in your dorm tonight?
- Kickpuncher, starring
don "the demon" Donaldson
as a cyborg cop whose punches
have the power of kicks.
- That sounds awful.
I'll bring the popcorn.
- Cool.
- Uh, you... you watch bad movies
on purpose?
- Yeah.
We make fun of 'em.
- Shirley, don't embarrass yourself.
I'm sure they don't want
to invite a housewife.
- Actually, if she doesn't mind
reinforcing the stereotype,
I bet Shirley would have fun
talking smack at a movie.
Care to join us?
- Usually when a movie's bad,
I stop watching,
but this sounds college-y.
- What time
do you want us there?
- Pierce, you don't want
to watch a cyborg movie
in Abed's dorm.
You want to lay
on your twin bed
and think
about what you used to be.
- What?
You think I'm too old
to make monkeyshines
at a picture show?
Come on. I'm younger than
the three of you put together.
- Yeah, you know, everyone talks
about his nipples,
but his feet freak me out.
- Britta!
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Can I ask you something...
About Vaughn?
- Oh, yes.
I still don't know if that's
his first or last name.
- [Chuckles]
He's sweet, actually.
I mean,
you must have thought so.
- He has a sincerity
I found attractive
in a simpler time.
- Would you...
um, I haven't...
we haven't...
anything.
I mean...
- wow, you and Vaughn.
- Would it bug you?
- Well, what
about you and Troy?
- Troy...
The other day after Spanish,
I thought he was trying
to hold my hand,
but he'd just mistaken me
for abed.
He'll never think of me
that way.
- Well, Annie,
I would have to be a villain
to tell you who to date,
which I am not.
- [Shrieks] Britta!
Thank you.
You're the coolest girl
I've ever met.
- Damn right.
Give me some fivesies.
Whoo.
Turning it into a snake.
- Cool.
[Rock music]
- * I can't count the reasons
I should stay *
- hey.
How's it going?
Did you hear?
It's cute... Annie and Vaughn.
- Get to the cute part.
- She's into him.
She asked for my blessing.
- And you gave it?
- Yeah.
I'm done with him.
- Look, this isn't about you,
you groovy hipster.
It's about Annie.
We're like
her Greendale parents.
You got to say no
to that stuff.
- He's not that bad.
- Yeah, not if you're 28
and you're fooling around
with him.
She's 18.
Her taste in men
is still being established.
Creepier and creepier dudes
will start thinking of her
as an option,
and it all starts with Vaughn.
He's a gateway douche bag.
- People collide.
Things happen.
It can't be controlled, right?
- And that can be your toast
at her shotgun wedding
to star-burns.
Oh, yeah, turn to your left.
Oh, now turn to your right.
Yes, we can see both of them.
It's like a constellation
on your face.
Oh, what's up, dude?
Yeah.
- That guy over there,
he's a douche bag.
- Hey, guys.
- hola.
- Hey, I hope you don't mind.
I invited senor Chang.
We're Netflix friends.
- Oh, that's cool
that you're hanging out,
drinking beers
with your students.
- Yeah.
Clearly, none of my other plans
fell through.
- Let's get to the movie.
[Stammers]
Oh, I'm sorry, Shirley.
I'll wait if you want
to serve beverages.
- You gonna be waiting
a long-ass time.
- Ooh, FBI warning...
I'm so scared.
[Laughter]
- Hey, that's not fair.
I didn't know we started.
- It is the year 2006 AD,
and nuclear war
has ravaged the planet.
- I must have missed that.
- Nice.
- The wasteland between cities
is a free-fire zone
ruled by scavengers,
drug dealers, and terrorists.
- Sounds like a Thanksgiving
at my house.
[Laughter]
- That's pretty crazy.
- He did it, though.
- They just come to me.
- You guys want
to buy some mega dope?
It gets you mega High.
- Will it get me
through this movie?
[Laughter]
- Shirley, that was good.
- Freeze!
Police.
- Freeze police?
Don't do that.
They'll get cold.
[Laughs]
- You have done so much
for our city.
Kickpuncher, is there anything
that we can give you?
- Yeah, two hours
of my life back.
[Laughter]
- Nice.
- Don't call me kickpuncher.
Call me David.
- "Directed by Kim Yang."
Asian...
Can't direct, can't drive.
[Laughs]
- Dude, I'm right here.
- So...
Clearly we're all a bunch
of funny people.
When are we doing this again?
- Well, actually, tomorrow
we were all gonna get together.
[Overlapping statements]
Tomorrow night
we're all gonna get together
to watch kickpuncher 2:
Codename Punchkicker.
- Well, I was just
warming up tonight.
Tomorrow you better foam
the runways,
'cause I'm bringing
my "a" game.
- Awesome.
[Annie giggling]
- [Laughs]
Oh, my God.
He's got her
in some kind of hippie collar.
I can hear her armpit hair
growing from here.
We got to do something.
- Okay, even if I agreed
with you, what are we gonna do?
- That's nice.
- Well, I know
if we say we disapprove,
we'll just drive her further
into his hemp-braceleted arms.
We need to be smart.
We need to hatch a scheme.
- Mm, hatching schemes
is not really my wheelhouse.
- Let's not confine ourselves
to your wheelhouse.
This problem won't respond
to tap dancing
or casual revelations
that you spent time in new York.
- Okay, if you're gonna get
all upper East side
about this, I think we're done.
- Hey, winger, check out Annie.
Somebody just went to the top
of my "to do" list.
- [Groans]
- Okay, we need
to hatch a scheme.
- Thank you.
- It's all very simple.
In Annie's world,
long before Vaughn,
she only had eyes for Troy.
- So if Troy becomes
a real option,
Annie will drop Vaughn
in a hippie's heartbeat.
- Crash course
in manipulation...
you don't actually tell the
person what you want them to do.
You help them realize
they want to do it
so it can't be traced
back to you.
- Chemistry... sexy.
You know what else is sexy?
Annie.
- [Scoffs]
I know chemistry is sexy.
But Annie?
I don't see it.
- Well, every other guy
on campus does.
- You really don't see
how pretty Annie is?
- Maybe it's 'cause I knew her
back in High school,
before she dropped out.
She had braces
and acne and a pill addiction
and a nervous breakdown
ending with her running
through a plate-glass door,
screaming, "everyone's a robot!"
- I see what's happening here.
Troy, I want you
to clear your head.
- Done.
- I'm gonna describe to you
a complete stranger
who happens to be
in our study group.
Would you excuse us
for a moment?
- Annie?
No kidding.
Come on,
you got to be exaggerating.
Oh, man.
- [Clears throat]
- And she's Jewish?
I can't believe
I didn't see that.
Well, I guess she deserves
another shot.
Oh, wait, never mind.
It's too late.
I Heard she's hooking up
with Vaughn.
- Only to make you jealous.
Both: What?
- She's helplessly in love
with you.
She's only with Vaughn
to get your attention.
And you have to give it
to her now, right, Jeff?
- Sure.
But the point is,
we're not telling you
what to do.
- Oh, yeah,
you didn't hear it from us.
- I have the weirdest boner.
- I saw you die.
How can you be alive?
- I guess it's just a bad day
for drug-dealing terrorists
and a good day for...
Kickpuncher.
- All right, guys,
you hear that pause
right after he says,
"and a good day"?
What do you got for me there?
- And a good day
for a nutritious breakfast.
- I don't get it.
- It's a good day
for a terrible movie.
- A good day for hair products.
- Oh, buzz, how many times
can you keep going to that well?
Come on, guys.
I'm starting to wonder
if you even deserve
to call yourselves a community
college sketch comedy troupe.
I told you, on movie night,
I need to blow these punks
out of the water.
I need
Phyllis Diller-grade stuff.
- Wouldn't you rather
just watch a movie
with your friends
and have a good time?
- What are you,
my third wife's therapist?
- What if he said,
"it's a good day for..."
And you said, "for being gay"?
- [Laughing]
You're a genius.
- He likes gay jokes.
- What?
- I said we write great jokes.
- Don't flatter yourselves.
- Whoa.
Hey...
Annie.
It's me, Troy.
- Oh, I don't know
where abed is.
I could try calling him
if you want.
- Nah, I'm not looking
for my other half.
I'm looking for you, girl.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Let that sink in for a second.
You know,
I never noticed how...
Beautiful you are.
- Troy, you're being weird.
- Sorry it took me so long.
They made me find a shirt.
- Vaughn, you remember Troy.
Um, we went
to High school together,
and he's in my study group.
- Hey, what's up, man?
Hi, bro.
- [Laughs] I'm not your bro...
Bro.
- Oh, actually,
everyone is my bro
in the whole entire universe,
you know,
because everything's connected...
rocks, eagles, hats.
- Yeah, well some things
are more connected than others,
like tarantulas
and me peeing my pants...
Or me and Annie.
- What? Wait.
Troy, what?
- Tell him.
Tell him that you've been in
love with me since High school.
- What?
Wait a minute.
Is that true, mountain flower?
- No.
I mean...
I never want to lie to you,
so I will tell you
I did have feelings for him,
but it's over, I swear.
- You're swearing?
Like Britta swore
that she didn't like Jeff
and then gave him a copy
of my poem
so he could laugh at me
with that Sherri Shepherd Lady?
Oh, it's happening again.
Your study group is evil.
And you don't deserve
ice cream.
- [Gasps]
- [Inhales sharply]
Well, he's a baby.
Now, where were we?
- I like him.
Why would you do that?
- Come on.
Everybody knows you want a cut
of the t-bone steak.
Jeff and Britta told me
how you feel.
- Wait, Jeff and Britta
did what, now?
- Oh, you're even hotter
when you're angry.
Let's do this.
Red shoe diaries...
I think you know
I have a thing for butt stuff.
- To Annie's inevitable breakup
with Grodie j. McConaughey.
- And to her and Troy.
We did the right thing.
They belong together.
Plus, their babies
will be so cute.
- Why would you say that?
- Come on.
You know that babies
are extra cute
when their parents are...
- Both cute?
- Do you want kids?
- We'll see.
Put on something nice,
and find me after lunch.
- Hey, guys, thanks for getting
involved in my love life.
That was super cool
and mature of you.
Oh, and since you're both
clearly idiots,
I should probably let you know
that I'm being sarcastic.
- Hey, guys,
thanks for taking ugly Annie
out of the palm of my hand
and turning her
into yet another hottie
that will never get with me!
- Hey, guys, thanks for eating
all the macaroni!
- Shut up, Leonard.
Nobody even knows
what you're talking about.
I did eat all the macaroni.
It's messed up that he knows.
- let's light this candle.
Who's ready
for some kickpunching?
- Actually, we decided
to watch runaway instead.
Tom selleck fights
mechanical spiders.
- What?
No, no, you can't do that.
We just watched kickpuncher.
We have to see kickpuncher 2.
I have
so many unanswered questions.
- No, I want
to watch tom Selleck
fight mechanical spiders.
- Yes.
- Me too.
- My brother died
on the set of that movie.
One of the mechanical spiders
just went haywire
and tore him to pieces.
Tom Selleck just stood there.
He just stood there
and... and watched him die.
- Okay, then let... let's watch
kickpuncher 2, then.
- Yeah. Okay.
- I'm sorry for your loss, man.
- I'm sorry, Pierce.
- Yeah, that's messed up, dude.
[Music swells on television]
- kiCkpuncher 2.
- My punches were only as strong
as my punches,
and then things changed.
- Change?
Time to change the channel.
This guy's gonna be begging
for change,
he keeps making movies
this bad.
They should change this movie
to something good.
I wish this crap-apillar
would change into a butterfly
and fly away.
That's change
we can believe in.
- Okay, obviously something
strange is happening here.
- What do you mean?
I'm making jokes
during the movie.
- Yeah, but you're doing it
with the speed
and the determination of the
incomparable Robin Williams.
- Yeah.
- Maybe I'm just that brilliant.
- I think you came prepared.
- Dude, even I know
you're lame,
and I'm a tenured professor
sitting in a beanbag chair.
- You're not a professor.
- Shut up, man.
- Fine!
You got me.
I did a little advance work.
Pathetic?
No, I'll tell you
what's pathetic...
you all sitting there making fun
of other people's work.
You don't feel good
about yourselves,
so you have to tear down
everything around you.
What's the matter?
Mama Chang didn't breast-feed?
- She read in a book that
it wouldn't make a difference.
- You all sicken me!
And I will
no longer participate
in your destructive,
negative behavior.
- Pierce, that was deep
and total BS
- Yeah, this isn't about us.
This is just a deflection
because you can't get
a genuine laugh.
- Mm-hmm.
- That in itself is a laugh.
I know I'm funny.
I don't need any of you people
to validate me.
- Mm.
- Oh! Oh!
[Crash] [Laughter]
- Biggest laugh of the night.
[Laughter]
Then I was gonna say,
"it's a good day to be gay."
[Troy laughs]
- Annie...
We're sorry.
We were worried
about your well-being.
- I guess we feel
like we're sort of all a family,
and Jeff and I are
like your Greendale parents.
- You're not my mom, Britta.
She would never wear boots
that go up that High.
And what about respecting me
as an adult and as a friend?
- Oh, you want to be treated
as an adult and a friend?
Try not dating
your friend's ex-boyfriend.
Find your own man.
- Oh, my.
- Oh, boy.
- But you don't like Vaughn.
- No, I don't,
but I also don't like seeing him
with anyone else.
Ta-da!
- I asked you if you cared,
and you said no.
- Fine. I cared.
I'm a girlie-girl.
I like boys, and I don't like it
when they're mean to me,
and I don't like it
when they stop kissing me
and start kissing my friends.
I'm not that cool.
I'm not Juno, okay, homeslice?
- This is what it was about
for you?
You were jealous?
- Oh, please, you can't tell me
that you weren't jealous
that Vaughn had his hippie hands
all over
your debate/make-out partner.
- What are you insinuating?
I took that kiss for the team.
- What?
Yeah, that kiss
wasn't for pleasure.
It was strategic and joyless.
- What?
Yeah.
- You did get weirdly specific
when you were describing
Annie's body.
- More specific than the stuff
you told me about Britta?
Both: What?
- Does anyone get specific
about me?
- Check your email.
- I'll mark you as spam.
- Who the hell is Pam?
- When you guys first came in,
we were as wholesome
and healthy
as the family
in the Brady bunch.
And now we're as dysfunctional
and incestuous
as the cast
of the Brady bunch.
- I agree with abed.
This is getting creepy.
- No more creepy
than when Jeff wears tight jeans
and you say, "I'd like to slap
those buns on the grill."
both: What?
- First of all,
I don't talk like that,
and second of all,
where I'm from,
it's perfectly normal for women
to talk about
their male friends' backsides.
And you don't see me
saying anything crazy
about abed and Troy's
weird little relationship.
Both:
They're just jealous.
- All right, all right,
maybe we're not a family.
Maybe it's more complicated,
because unlike a real family,
there's nothing to stop
any one of us
from looking
at any of the others
as a sexual prospect.
- [Gasps]
- Why are we even talking
about this?
- Because you started having sex
with Britta's ex-boyfriend.
- What?
We haven't even kissed.
- That doesn't mean
you're not having sex.
- Vaughn told me
he would take things
as slowly as I wanted.
He likes me for who I am,
and I like him.
[Distant singing
and guitar playing]
- Do you guys hear that?
[Singing and guitar playing
continues]
* *
- Annie.
- Vaughn.
- Britta.
- Hi.
- Old man river.
- Eat me.
- Did you get my messages?
- No.
I threw my phone
into the river.
I thought that, you know,
if I can't be with her,
who am I gonna call?
And then I thought, you know,
well, my landlord, my sister,
and...
You.
Anyway, I've been doing
a lot of soul-searching,
and, uh, this is something
I really need to say.
* *
* I see you when you smile *
* and I want to sing a song *
* but then I write the words *
* and they always
come out wrong *
* they come out wrong *
* I feel it in my fingers *
* I feel it in my toes *
* but then the words
get frozen *
* in my mouth like Eskimos *
* I like your nose *
* ooh ooh ooh *
* ooh *
* Annie *
* ooh ooh ooh *
* ooh *
* Annie's song *
- his songs are dumber
than he is.
- Yeah, but they're honest.
- Okay.
[Giggles]
Vaughn wants to show me a cloud
that looks like a Pumpkin...
If that's okay.
- Annie, it's more than okay.
Please date Vaughn.
- Or anyone else
outside this creepy circle.
- I wouldn't hang out
with you guys
if you were creepy.
Trust me.
I have good taste.
- So just to be clear,
I don't have a shot
with any of you?
- [robotic voice]
I am kickpuncher.
My cyber punch
have the power of kicks.
[Imitates robot noises]
[Kick/punch sound effect]
- Agh!
Aha. Oh!
Oh!
[Chuckles]
[Both groan]
I am Punchkicker.
Meet your match.
[Thud, warbling]
[Electricity crackling]
[Moans]
I love you, kickpuncher.
- The only thing
beyond the reach of my fists
is humanity.
[Normal voice] You're sure
Britta couldn't do your part?
- I asked her.
She wasn't available.
Let's go film the sex scene.
www.tvsubtitles.net